<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 02:18:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello world!</title><link>/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 02:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</description></item><item><title>Joe Grey Soup</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/joe-grey-soup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 02:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/joe-grey-soup/</guid><description>Traditional Gypsy Stew Joe Grey is a traditional Gypsy stew often made with sausage and bacon but can be modified to fit whatever flavor profile, or ingredients in your refrigerator, that you might desire.
Joe Grey History A popular dish in the Romany community, no one is sure of its origins. This recipe takes its inspiration from the wondering nature of the people who created it. It has a superb umami flavor due to the combination of meats and tomatoes.</description></item><item><title>Quick E Recipes Site Map</title><link>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/quick-e-recipes-site-map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/quick-e-recipes-site-map/</guid><description>[wp_sitemap_page]</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:44:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact-us/</guid><description>Festive meals are family, fun, and tradition Thank you for visiting quick-e-recipes. Our mission is to give you all the information you need to be successful in the kitchen. We invite questions about home cooking, institutional cooking for 20-300, Gourmet dishes, special diets(including vegan, no gluten, lactose intolerant, peanut and food allergies). Also we invite questions on techniques, and methods of anything specific. So don’t hesitate, write today!
[contact-form-7 id=”980″ title=”Contact form 1″]</description></item><item><title>Onion Smell Tips</title><link>/onion-smell-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:39:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>/onion-smell-tips/</guid><description>Having a hard time getting the onion smell off your hands? Try running your hands in cool water for a few seconds, then grasp the neck of the faucet and slide you hands quickly back and forth on the chrome causing some friction. Rinse and Voila! No smell.</description></item><item><title>Clean As You Go!</title><link>/clean-as-you-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/clean-as-you-go/</guid><description>I keep a sink full of soapy hot water hand so I can wash dishes between tasks. This helps keep your area free of clutter, and if guests are coming they don’t see a big mess.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Crowd Me!</title><link>/dont-crowd-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dont-crowd-me/</guid><description>I was thinking about crowding the other day as I sat on bleachers in the gym waiting to hear our grandson sing for his class Christmas concert. It was uncomfortable and hot, with little room to relax your arms or stretch your legs. It was all worth it when our grandson was on stage singing and shyly smiling as he noticed us in the audience. After the concert I started thinking about food crowding and how it challenges the quality of a recipe.</description></item><item><title>Why I Became A Cook</title><link>/why-i-became-a-cook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/why-i-became-a-cook/</guid><description>&lt;p>I remember as a small child of 4or5 years old sitting in front of our black and white TV. On the screen was a lady pouring in a powdery substance, then adding a liquid. She started stirring the mixture up and all of a sudden it was something totally different, a doughy mound. ” Wow”, I thought, ” I wish I could do that”. I can’t explain why I was so mesmerized by something so simple, but I knew I wanted to what that lady did on TV.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chef’s Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:36:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Quick Au Jus</title><link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/quick-au-jus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/quick-au-jus/</guid><description>Au Jus, Quick and Easy on the Stove or From Drippings, Great for Prime RibDuring Holidays or Special Function Dinners. This Quick and Easy Au Jus is Made With a Touch of Wine!
Au Jus Recipe 4 c water 4 tsp beef base 1 c red wine 1/2 onion(remove after finished) 1 tsp garlic, chopped 1/4 tsp white pepper Au Jus Directions In sauce pan place water, beef base, garlic, white pepper, and wine.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Barbecue Sauce</title><link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Prepare this wonderful barbecue sauce on the stove. Great for grillingoutside or in. Use our sauce for chicken, ribs, pork, or barbecue sandwiches. Chef Frank finishes this recipe off with red wine for an added kick!
Barbecue Sauce Recipe 2 c ketchup 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Barbecue Sauce Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Easy No Bake Cookies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-no-bake-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-no-bake-cookies/</guid><description>Quick Easy No Bake Cookies Recipe are a standard for Holidaysor any day. No Bake cookies in your lunch bag put a smile on your face. There’s chocolate in it ya know!Skippy Loves No Bake Cookies!No Bake Cookies Recipe 1/2 c margerine 1/2 c milk 1/2 c cocoa 2 c sugar 1/2 tsp salt No Bake Cookies Directions place these ingredients in sauce pan and heat to a slow boil.</description></item><item><title>Easy Egg In A Basket</title><link>/recipes/sandwich-recipes/easy-egg-in-a-basket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:27:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/sandwich-recipes/easy-egg-in-a-basket/</guid><description>Quick Easy Egg in a Basket Recipe is fun for the kids to eat and help make. Pictures to guide you when making egg in a basket, a great fun breakfast.
Egg In A Basket Recipe 1 slice bread 1 egg 2 pats butter Egg In A Basket Directions Butter bread lightly on both sides. Place small fry pan on stove and turn on low heat. Lightly grill bread on both sides.</description></item><item><title>Apple Smackers Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-smackers-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-smackers-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Apple Smackers are a baked Michigan Applewith cinnamon and sugar, So easy to prepare. Apple Smackers are a kids favorite snack.
Apple Smackers Recipe Serves 4
3 tart apples 3 tbsp sugar 1/2 tbsp cinnamon 2 0z. butter, melted Apple Smackers Directions Peel apples and cut in wedges. Place wedges on microwaveable plate. Brush melted butter over apples. Combine sugar with cinnamon, then sprinkle over apples. Cover with wax paper or plastic wrap and place in microwave for about 5 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Sugar Cookies Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/sugar-cookies-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:09:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/sugar-cookies-recipe/</guid><description>Sugar Cookies are Quick and Easy with this Versatile Recipe. Make Thumbprints with the Same Sugar Cookie Recipe using Strawberry Preserves or any Fruit Jam.Festive Sugar Cookies For The HolidaysUse this recipe and strawberry preserves to make thumbprint cookies, just place a ball of cookie dough on the pan and press a dimple in with your thumb and fill with preserves. Same bake time as sugar cookies.
Sugar Cookies Recipe 3 c flour 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 1/2 c sugar 2 sticks butter, soft 2 eggs 1 tsp vanilla 1 tbsp lemon juice 1/2 tsp salt Sugar Cookies Directions Combine flour, baking soda, baking powder together and set aside.</description></item><item><title>All Sweet Nut Cookies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/all-sweet-nut-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/all-sweet-nut-cookies/</guid><description>Sandy’s allsweet nut cookies are fun and easy to make. A great snack for kids after school or anytime. Get the kids to help make these delicious cookies.
Sandy’s Allsweet Nut Cookies 1/2 c. margerine softened 2 tsp sugar 1 c. chopped pecans 1 tsp. vanilla 7/8 c. sifted flour 2 c. powdered sugar set aside (for rolling cookies after baking) Allsweet Nut Cookies Directions Cream margarine and sugar together.</description></item><item><title>Peanut Butter Oatmeal Cookies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/peanut-butter-oatmeal-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/peanut-butter-oatmeal-cookies/</guid><description>Delicious Peanut Butter Oatmeal Cookies, Quick and Easy for any Occasion. Kids love them for After School Snacks, or Dessert after Supper or Lunch.
Peanut Butter Oatmeal Cookies Recipe 3/4 c. margarine or butter 1 c. peanut butter 1 1/2 c firmly packed brown sugar 1/2 c water 1 egg 1 tsp vanilla 3 c. quick oats 1 1/2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda Peanut Butter Oatmeal Cookies Directions In large mixing bowl beat together margerine, peanut butter, and brown sugar.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Oatmeal Cookies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/homemade-oatmeal-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/homemade-oatmeal-cookies/</guid><description>Scratch Oatmeal Cookies with raisins or dried fruit or nuts is a real treat, and only Takes 5-7 Minutes to Prepare. Oatmeal Cookies are a Great After School Snack.Holy Smokes! Check out those awesome oatmeal cookies!Oatmeal Cookies Recipe 2 sticks butter, softened 3/4 c brown sugar 3/4 c sugar 1 1/2 c flour 3 c quick oats 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1 tsp vanilla ext. pinch salt 2 eggs 2 c dried cherries or raisins 1 c chopped nuts (optional) Oatmeal Cookie Directions Cream sugar and butter together.</description></item><item><title>Monster Cookies Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/monster-cookies-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/monster-cookies-recipe/</guid><description>Monster Cookies are Easy to Make and Quick to disappear. Kid’s love them and Monster Cookies are great for Christmas or Everyday.
Monster Cookies Recipe 2 sticks margarine or butter 2 c. sugar 1 lb. brown sugar 3 c. peanut butter 4 tsp baking soda 2 tsp corn syrup 1 1/2 tsp vanilla 9 c. oatmeal 2 c. chocolate chips 1 c. candy coated chocolates Monster Cookies Directions Cream butter and sugar together.</description></item><item><title>Peanut Butter Yummies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/peanut-butter-yummies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:06:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/peanut-butter-yummies/</guid><description>Kids are always looking for an after school snack. This recipe is so easy and quick to prepare your kids can help, and enjoy the fruits of their labors. Have a cold glass of milk handy.
Peanut Butter Yummies, Quick and Easy Recipe 1/2 c. butterscotch chips 1/4 c. peanut butter 1 1/2 c. corn flakes Peanut Butter Yummies Directions Melt butterscotch in saucepan over medium heat. remove pan to hot pad.</description></item><item><title>Easy Peanut Butter Cookies Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-peanut-butter-cookies-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:06:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-peanut-butter-cookies-recipe/</guid><description>Scratch Peanut Butter Cookies take only ten minutes to prepare and ten minutes to cook. The hardest part is waiting for them to cool. Make these for Christmas or any Holiday and place chocolate stars on top of the cookies as soon as they come out of the oven.Check out these awesome homemade peanut butter cookies!Peanut Butter Cookies Recipe About 48 cookies
2 1/2 – 3 c flour 2 sticks butter, softened 2 eggs 1 28oz.</description></item><item><title>Jubilee Cookie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/jubilee-cookie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:05:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/jubilee-cookie-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Jubilee Cookie Recipe is a light Vanilla Cake Cookie topped with Vanilla and Coconut Frosting. Jubilee Cookies will Quickly become a Family Favorite Treat or Dessert.
Jubilee cookies About 48 cookies
1/2 c shortening 1 c brown sugar 1/2 c sugar 2 eggs 1 c evaporated milk 2 3/4 c flour 1 tsp vanilla ext. 1 tsp salt 1 c coconut 1/2 tsp baking soda Jubilee Cookie Directions Mix shortening, sugar, and eggs thoroughly.</description></item><item><title>Gingerbread Cookies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/gingerbread-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:04:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/gingerbread-cookies/</guid><description>Quick Easy Gingerbread Cookies Recipe for the Holidays or Anytime. Gingerbread Cookies or Gingerbread Men are Easy and Make a Great Food Gift for Any Cookie Lover.
Gingerbread Cookies 3 c flour
1 1/2 c brown sugar
1/2 tsp baking powder
1/2 tsp baking soda
2 eggs
2 sticks butter, soft
1/3 c mollasses
pinch ground ginger/li&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>Easy Chocolate Chip Cookies</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-chocolate-chip-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-chocolate-chip-cookies/</guid><description>Chocolate Chip Cookies are easy to make with this Quick Easy Recipe. Use real Chocolate Chips with these Cookies and let the Kids help.
Chocolate chip cookies Ingredients Serves about 48
1/2 lb butter( room temperature) 3/4 c brown sugar 3/4 c sugar 2 eggs 1 tsp vanilla 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 2 1/2 c flour 3 c chocolate chips (semi-sweet) Chocolate Chip Cookies Directions Cream together in mixer, butter and sugar, then add vanilla and eggs.</description></item><item><title>Blueberry Pie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/blueberry-pie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/blueberry-pie-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Blueberry Pie Recipe is made from fresh or frozen blueberries, (preferrably from Buchan’s Blueberriesin Traverse City, Michigan out on the Old Mission Penninsula), sugar, lemon juice, and quick tapioca for thickening. Blueberry Pie is a nice dessert for any occasion.
Quick Blueberry Pie Ingredients 1 pkg. pie crust (2-9″) 4 c blueberries (Buchan’s Blueberries are the best!) 3/4 c sugar 1 tsp lemon juice 3 tbsp quick tapioca 1/8 tsp salt 1 tsp vanilla ext.</description></item><item><title>Peach Pie With Fresh Peaches</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/peach-pie-with-fresh-peaches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/peach-pie-with-fresh-peaches/</guid><description>Quick Easy Peach Pie Recipe with Fresh or Frozen Sliced Peaches, Quick Tapioca, Lemon, and Sugar. A Quick Pie Crust and Peach Pie is Ready for Dessert.
Quick Peach Pie Recipe 1 pkg pie crust(2-9″) 3 c fresh peeled cut peaches 3/4 c sugar 3 tbsp quick tapioca 1/8 tsp salt 1 tsp lemon juice Peach Pie Directions Place bottom crust in pie pan and press. In large mixing bowl place ingredients and mix well.</description></item><item><title>Traverse City Cherry Pie</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/traverse-city-cherry-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/traverse-city-cherry-pie/</guid><description>Traverse City Cherry Pie is the best in Michigan and so easy to make. Your family will go wild over this.
Traverse City Cherry Pie 1pkg pie crust (2-9″) 4 c pitted tart cherries 3/4 c sugar 3 tbsp quick tapioca 1 tsp lemon juice 1/8 tsp salt 1 tbsp butter, melted Cherry Pie Directions Press bottom crust in pan. In large mixing bowl combine ingredients ans mix well.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-pie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-pie-recipe/</guid><description>Apple Pie with Michigan Apples is Quick to Prepare and Easy to Eat. Using Fresh Apples for This Apple Pie Recipe, Tops off any Meal, Top that with Vanilla Ice Cream or Cheese.
Quick Apple Pie Ingredients 1 pkg Pie crust for 2 crust pie, 9″ 6-8 Michigan spies, or granny smith apples (peeled and thinly sliced) 3/4 c sugar 1 tsp lemon juice 3 1/2 tbsp quick tapioca 1/8 tsp salt 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1/8 tsp ground nutmeg 2 tbsp butter, melted Apple Pie Directions Press one crust in pie shell, don’t trim</description></item><item><title>Apple Crisp Pie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-crisp-pie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:45:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-crisp-pie-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Apple crisp recipe with Michigan Apples. Use Michigan Spy Apples for this Apple Crisp Recipe. With a Hint of Cinnamon and Quick Tapioca, it’s Wonderful Served Warm.
Apple Crisp Ingredients serves 8-10
6 tart apples, peeled, sliced 1 c sugar 1/2 c brown sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 2 tbsp quick tapioca dash salt 4 oz. butter, melted 1 c corn flakes 2 c quick oats Apple Crisp Directions Apple Part In mixing bowl combine apples, 1/2 tsp cinnamon, white sugar, salt, tapioca.</description></item><item><title>Vanilla Frosting Recipe With Cinnamon</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/vanilla-frosting-recipe-with-cinnamon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:41:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/vanilla-frosting-recipe-with-cinnamon/</guid><description>Cakes and Sweet Rolls are finished with this Vanilla Frosting with Cinnamon Recipe. Quick and Easy to make, this Vanilla Frosting with Cinnamon tops any Cinnamon Roll!
Vanilla Frosting with Cinnamon Ingredients 3 c powdered sugar 2 oz. soft butter pinch salt 1/4 c milk 1 tsp vanilla Frosting Directions Mix together with electric mixer, sugar salt butter vanilla, then slowly add milk and whip until desired thickness is achieved.</description></item><item><title>Easy Brownie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-brownie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-brownie-recipe/</guid><description>Quick-e-Brownies Ingredients serves 20
1 1/2 c flour 2 c sugar 1 tbsp salt 4 eggs 8 tbsp baking cocoa 2 tsp vanilla 2 tbsp corn syrup 1 c oil 1/2 c hot water Quick Brownies Directions Place in large mixing bowl, salt, sugar, eggs, oil, vanilla, and corn syrup. Mix well. In seperate bowl whisk together flour and cocoa. Put in wet mixture, add hot water and mix.</description></item><item><title>No Egg Chocolate Cake</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/no-egg-chocolate-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/no-egg-chocolate-cake/</guid><description>Quick Easy Chocolate Cake Uses no Egg and only Takes 5 Minutes, Then In The oven It Goes. Great for Egg Allergies. Make Cupcakes and Frost For Birthdays or any Party.Can you believe that this beautiful chocolate cake has no egg?Quick Easy No Egg Chocolate Cake Ingredients 2 1/2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1 1/2 c sugar 1/3 c oil 1/2 c baker’s cocoa 1/2 tsp salt 1 tsp vanilla ext1 1/2-2 c water add gradually No Egg Chocolate Cake Directions In large mixing bowl, combine all dry ingredients with wire whisk.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate Frosting Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/chocolate-frosting-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/chocolate-frosting-recipe/</guid><description>Chocolate Frosting made Quick and Easy with a Five Minute Recipe. Chocolate Frosting for Birthday Cakes or Cupcakes, A Favorite for Parties or After School Snacks.
Chocolate Frosting Ingredients 3 c powdered sugar 1/2 c bakers cocoa 3 oz. soft butter pinch salt 1/4 c milk 1 tsp vanilla Chocolate Frosting Directions mix together with electric mixer on low speed, sugar and cocoa. Then add, salt, butter, and vanilla.</description></item><item><title>Easy Chocolate Cake Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-chocolate-cake-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-chocolate-cake-recipe/</guid><description>Chocolate Cake is made quick and easy for birthdays or any occasion. A five minute scratch recipe for Chocolate Cake is truly quick, easy, and fun for Parties.A beautiful and easy chocolate cake.Quick Easy Chocolate Cake 2 1/2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/3 c veg oil 1 1/2 c sugar 2 eggs pinch salt 1 tsp vanilla 1/2 c bakers cocoa 1 1/2 – 2 c water add gradually Easy Chocolate Cake Directions Mix together in large bowl with electric mixer, sugar, oil, eggs, salt and vanilla.</description></item><item><title>Easy Frosting Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-frosting-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/easy-frosting-recipe/</guid><description>Mom’s Quick Easy Frosting Recipe Makes any Cake Better. Mom’s Frosting is from Scratch and Easy to Make, and Top any Cake, Cupcakes and Birthday Cakes.
Here is a simple recipe that will wow everyone!
Easy Frosting Ingredients 1/2 c milk 2 1/2 tsp flour Step 1 Directions cook in sauce pan to make thick paste, set in refrigerator to cool
1/2 c sugar 1/2 c butter or margerine dash salt 1 tsp vanilla ext.</description></item><item><title>Cinnamon Rolls From Scratch</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/cinnamon-rolls-from-scratch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/cinnamon-rolls-from-scratch/</guid><description>Cinnamon Rolls from scratch are indeed memorable especially with caramel sauce or frosting. Homemade cinnamon rolls are a fun project for the whole family. Let the kids help too!
Sweet Dough Cinnamon Rolls Homemade from Scratch In Sauce Pan: scold – 1/2 c milk stir in 1/2 c sugar 1 1/2 tsp salt 1/2 c shortening Cool to lukewarm Measure Into Large Bowl: 1/2 cup warm water 3 pkgs quick rising yeast stir until dissolved then add ingredients from saucepan (lukewarm) Add: 2 eggs beaten 3 c sifted flour Beat until smooth then add: 2 c flour and stir in until smooth.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Cinnamon Caramel Sauce</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/homemade-cinnamon-caramel-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:37:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/homemade-cinnamon-caramel-sauce/</guid><description>Cinnamon Caramel Sauce is a must for any Cinnamon Roll or many Dessert Recipes. Cinnamon Caramel Sauce takes 5 minutes on the stove, very quick and easy!
Cinnamon Caramel Sauce 4 oz. butter 2 c brown sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 1-2 c heavy cream Directions Place butter and sugar in sauce pan and heat on medium heat stirring constantly with whisk until mixture starts to boil. Add cinnamon and slowly add cream while whisking until desired consistancy is reached.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Carrot Cake Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/homemade-carrot-cake-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/homemade-carrot-cake-recipe/</guid><description>There’s nothing better than fresh carrot cake with cream cheese frosting. A hint of cinnamon tops this easy recipe from Northern Michigan
Carrot Cake, Homemade and Delicious 2 c. flour 2 tsp. baking soda 1 tsp. salt 1 1/4 c. veg. oil 2 c. sugar 2 tsp. cinnamon 4 eggs 1 tsp. vanilla 4 c. shredded fresh carrots 1 c. chopped pecans Cake Directions In medium mixing bowl conbine flour, baking soda, salt, and cinnamon, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Traverse City Cherry Torte Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/cherry-torte-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/cherry-torte-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Cherry Torte Recipe is from Aunt Lucy’s kitchen. This Cherry Torte Recipe is an old standard from Traverse City and is a great dessert for any occasion.
Aunt Lucy’s Cherry Torte Ingredients Cake 2 c flour 1/2 c brown sugar 1 c chopped nuts 2 sticks butter (8 oz., 1 c) Cake Directions In large mixing bowl combine flour, brown sugar, butter, and nuts. Mix together, pack into 9″x13″ baking pan.</description></item><item><title>Irish Fluff</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/irish-fluff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/irish-fluff/</guid><description>Quick Easy Irish Fluff Recipe for St. Patrick’s Day is made with Marshmallows, Pistachio Pudding, Pineapple, and Whipped Cream. Irish Fluff will top off any St. Patrick’s Day Meal.
Irish Fluff Ingredients 1 pkg instant pistachio pudding mix 1 pkg small marshmallows 1 can crushed pineapple(do not drain) 1 small tub whipped topping Irish Fluff Directions In large mixing bowl combine dry pudding mix and pineapple with juice. Mix well,add marshmallows and whipped topping.</description></item><item><title>Fruit Fluff Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/fruit-fluff-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/fruit-fluff-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Fruit Fluff Recipe is a Wonderful Easy Recipe for a Quick Dessert when in a Hurry. Fruit Cocktail, Whipped Cream, and Strawberry Glaze make Fruit Fluff that Kids Love!
Fruit Fluff Ingredients 2 cans fruit cocktail (drained) 1 small container whipped cream 1 c strawberry glaze Fruit Fluff Directions In large mixing bowl place drained fruit cocktail, whipped cream, mix well. Swirl in strawberry glaze, serve. This recipe can also be used with fresh fruit if so desired.</description></item><item><title>Banana Kuhl Fry Recipe</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/banana-kuhl-fry-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/banana-kuhl-fry-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Banana Kuhl Fry is great for those Last Minute Desserts. Simply cut Bananas and Place in Dish with Sour Cream, Sugar and Coconut. Banana Kuhl Fry for Dessert!
Banana Kuhl fry Ingredients Bananas 1/2 c sour cream 1/4 c sugar 1/4 c shredded coconut Banana Kuhl Fry Directions Slice bananas in individual dessert dishes Mix sour cream and sugar together and pour over bananas. Sprinkle coconut on top, serve.</description></item><item><title>Dessert Recipes</title><link>/recipes/dessert-recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/dessert-recipes/</guid><description>Welcome to our Dessert Section. The Whole Family will Rave when you Prepare Delicious and Quick Desserts like Traverse City Cherry Pie, and Cherry Torte. Michigan Apple Pie with Spies. Homemade Chocolate Cakes ( even an eggless chocolate cake from scratch that takes only 5 minutes to prepare for the oven), Irish Fluff Puddings, and Scrumptious Fruit Crisps too.
Pudding Desserts Banana Kuhl fry Fruit Fluff Irish Fluff Cakes &amp;amp; Frostings Aunt Lucy’s Cherry Torte Homemade Carrot Cake, Simple and Delicious Cinnamon Caramel Sauce Cinnamon Rolls Mom’s Frosting Quick Easy Chocolate Cake Chocolate Frosting Quick No Egg Chocolate Cake Quick-e-Brownies Vanilla Frosting with Cinnamon Pies Apple Crisp Apple Pie Apple Dumplings Cherry Pie Peach Pie Blueberry Pie Cookies Chocolate Chip Cookies Real Chocolate Chip Cookies for 200 People Gingerbread Cookies Jubilee Cookies Peanut Butter Cookies Peanut Butter Yummies, Quick and Easy Monster Cookies, Quick and Easy Recipe Oatmeal Cookies Peanut Butter Oatmeal Cookies, Quick and Easy Sandy’s Allsweet Nut Cookies Sugar Cookies</description></item><item><title>Easy Homemade Bread</title><link>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/easy-homemade-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/easy-homemade-bread/</guid><description>Quick Easy Whole Wheat or White Bread Recipe is From Scratch, Makes Two Loaves, and is the same as Grandma Makes. Homemade Bread Aroma Welcomes Your Family and Guests Warmly.
Homemade Bread Ingredients 6-7 c flour ( whole wheat or white) 3 level tbsp yeast paste, or dry yeast 2 tbsp sugar 1 tbsp honey 1 tbsp salt 1 c 2% milk 1 1/4 c water warm 95℉ 2 tsp butter Homemade Bread Directions In a large mixing bowl place warm water (95℉), then yeast and mix together.</description></item><item><title>Zucchini Bread Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/zucchini-bread-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/zucchini-bread-recipe/</guid><description>Easy Zucchini Quick Bread Recipe is a favorite in the Summer after Harvesting Fresh Zucchini from the Garden. Zucchini Bread with Nuts Too, and even Dried Fruit, Just add to the Recipe.
Zucchini Bread Ingredients 3 eggs 2 1/2 c sugar 1 c oil 3 c flour 3 tsp cinnamon 1 tsp salt 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp baking soda 3 tsp vanilla extract 4 c shredded zucchini 1 c chopped nuts (walnuts or pecans) Zucchini Bread Directions Blend together eggs, oil, salt, vanilla, and zucchini.</description></item><item><title>Poppy Seed Bread Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</guid><description>Poppy Seed Bread is an old Family Favorite Quick Bread Recipe. So Easy to Prepare, Poppy Seed Bread with a Hint of Lemon is Wonderful for Breakfast or a Quick Dessert.
Poppy Seed Bread Ingredients 1 pkg. yellow cake mix 1 pkg. toasted coconut instant pudding 4 large eggs 1/2 c vegetable oil 1/4 c soaked and drained poppy seeds 1 c hot water Poppy Seed Bread Directions Mix all ingredients in large bowl, beat as for cake.</description></item><item><title>Old Fashioned Macaroni and Cheese Recipe</title><link>/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/old-fashioned-macaroni-and-cheese-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/old-fashioned-macaroni-and-cheese-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Macaroni and Cheese Recipe is made from Cheddar Cheese, Milk, and Butter, like Mom used to make. Macaroni and Cheese for Lunch or Dinner is a Winner that Kids and Adults Love.
Macaroni and Cheese Ingredients Serves 8-12
2 lb macaroni 2 lb shredded cheddar cheese (sharp) 1 1/2 c milk 2 oz. butter melted or soft salt and pepper to taste Macaroni and Cheese Directions Boil macaroni for 8 minutes, drain.</description></item><item><title>Casserole Recipes</title><link>/recipes/casserole-recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/casserole-recipes/</guid><description>Welcome To Our Quick Easy Casserole Recipes Section. Prepare These Easy Noodle Casseroles for Lunch or Dinner. Kids Will Love Our Macaroni and Cheese and Tuna Noodle Casserole as Well as All the Others. Great Comfort Foods for Those Cold days.
Casserole Recipes Creamy Scalloped Potatoes Chicken Noodle Casserole Tuna Noodle Casserole Scalloped Potatoes Old Fashioned Macaroni and Cheese Goulash</description></item><item><title>Cauliflower Broccoli Au Gratin Recipe</title><link>/recipes/casserole-recipes/cauliflower-broccoli-au-gratin-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/casserole-recipes/cauliflower-broccoli-au-gratin-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Cauliflower Broccoli Au Gratin Recipe is a nice hearty hot vegetable with cream sauce and cheese topped with bread crumbs. Cauliflower Broccoli Au Gratin will dress up any meal for a Holidayor Special Function.
Cauliflower Broccoli Au Gratin Ingredients Serves 8-12
1 lb broccoli 1 lb cauliflower 1/2 lb shredded cheddar 1 c bread or cracker crumbs 1/4 stick butter(melted) roux Cauliflower Broccoli Au Gratin Directions Cut broccoli and cauliflower in bite size pieces and boil for 2-4 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Tuna Tomato Lotus Recipe</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/tuna-tomato-lotus-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/tuna-tomato-lotus-recipe/</guid><description>Tuna Tomato Lotus, Quick Easy Recipe for a Summer Luncheon Salad. Starred Fresh Tomato Stuffed with Tuna Salad Topped with Green Pepper Strips. Tuna Tomato Lotus With a Bowl of Soup, Healthy!
Tuna Tomato Lotus Quick and Easy Recipe Serves 4
4 red ripe tomatoes 8 oz. tuna, drained 1/4 c onion, diced 1 green pepper, cut in long strips from top to bottom 1/8 c celery, diced 2 tbsp mayo salt and pepper to taste Tuna Tomato Lotus Directions In mixing bowl combine tuna, onion, celery, mayo, and spices, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Potato Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-side-dishes/potato-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-side-dishes/potato-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Red Potato Salad Recipe with Fresh Boiled Eggs, Red Potatoes, Celery, Onion, and a Mustard Mayo Sauce with Spices. Red Potato Salad makes a Great
PicnicBetter.
Potato Salad 5 lbs red potatoes, cooked 15-20 min., chunked (do not peel) 5 eggs, boiled 7 minutes, peeled, sliced 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1/2 cucumber diced (optional) 1 c salad dressing 2 tbsp mustard 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 1/2 tsp paprika Potato Salad Directions In large mixing bowl put all ingredients except potatoes.</description></item><item><title>Vegetables and Salad Recipes</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/vegetables-and-salad-recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/vegetables-and-salad-recipes/</guid><description>Prepare tasty fresh and colorful salads with garden fresh vegetables. Enjoy healthy summer eating fresh from the great outdoors.
Green Salads Ceasar Salad
Chef Salad
Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad
Pasta Salad
Strawberry Spinach Salad
Tossed Garden Salad
Garden Vegetable Salad
Mayo-based Salads Macaroni Salad
Potato Salad
Tuna Tomato Lotus
Turkey Salad, with apples, raisins, almonds.</description></item><item><title>Coney Sauce Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/coney-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/coney-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>This Quick Easy Coney Sauce is Chef Frank’s Original Recipe. Use over High Grade Hot Dogs with Vadalia Onions and make other Lunches Jealous. Coney Sauce is a great Starter for ChiliToo.
Coney Sauce Chef Frank’s Original Recipe 2 lbs ground beef chuck or sirloin 1/2 small vadalia(sweet) onion diced 1 clove garlic, peeled, crushed or 1 tbs garlic powder (more or less to taste) 2 tbs tomato paste 1/2 tsp salt 1/2 tsp white pepper 4 tbs ground cumin (cumino) Coney Sauce Directions In large frying pan brown ground beef with onions, garlic, cumin, salt and pepper, breaking up burger as it cooks.</description></item><item><title>Sloppy Joe Recipe</title><link>/recipes/sandwich-recipes/sloppy-joe-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/sandwich-recipes/sloppy-joe-recipe/</guid><description>Our Sloppy Joes are Delicious, Quick and Easy with Ground Beef, Turkey, Chicken and Pork Recipe Variations. Fresh Rosemary and Vegetables Top Off this Awesome Sandwich.
Sloppy Joe Recipe Ingredients 2 lbs fresh ground beef 1/2 sweet onion, diced 2 ribs celery, diced small 2 tbs yellow mustard 1 c ketchup 2 tbs brown sugar 1 tsp soy sauce dash white pepper 1/2 tsp garlic, granulated or fresh chopped 1 tsp molasses 2 dashes salt 1/2 tsp rosemary (optional) Sloppy Joe Directions In a skillet or elect.</description></item><item><title>Split Pea Soup With Ham Recipe</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/split-pea-soup-with-ham-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/split-pea-soup-with-ham-recipe/</guid><description>Here is a soup that will keep you warm on a cold winters day!
Quick Easy Split Pea Soup Recipe to warm up any cold day. Our split pea soup recipe has fresh carrots, onion, celery, potatoes, and ham, slow cooked for perfection. Break out the crackers.
Split Pea Soup with Ham Ingredients Serves 10+
1 lb dried split peas 1 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced 2-3 potatoes, peeled, diced 3 carrots, peeled, diced 3 tbsp chicken base 3 quarts water 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 ham bone (with 1 lb ham) Split Pea Soup Directions In large soup kettle, place all ingredients except peas.</description></item><item><title>Seafood Chowder Recipe</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/seafood-chowder-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/seafood-chowder-recipe/</guid><description>Seafood Chowder, Quick Easy Thick Creamy Soup and Chowder Recipe. Use Your Choice of Scallops, Shrimp, Crab or Lobster. Fun and Simple to Prepare. Seafood Chowder is a Great Lunch. Serve With Oyster Crackers, a Sandwichor Salad.
Seafood Chowder Ingredients Serves about 8-10
2 c assorted seafood, chopped, raw (crab, shrimp, clams, scallops) 3 potaotoes, peeled diced 1/2 onion, diced 2 ribs celery, diced 2 large carrots, diced 1 tbsp crab base 1/4 tsp white pepper 1 tsp garlic 1 oz.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Pumpkin Vegetable Soup</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-pumpkin-vegetable-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:09:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-pumpkin-vegetable-soup/</guid><description>Hot pumpkin soup is a vegetarians delight with real pumpkin, sweet potatoes, celery, and other vegetables from the garden. A chunky, filling soup that is heart warming, quick and easy to prepare.
Vegetarian Pumpkin Vegetable Soup Ingredients 10 c water 3 tbs vegetable base 3 ribs celery, diced 1 small onion, diced 1 small pumpkin cleaned, diced, enough for 5 cups 3 carrots, peeled, 1/2’d then sliced 2 small red potatoes, diced ( no need to peel) 1 large sweet potato, peeled, diced 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 small pinch nutmeg Pumpkin Soup Directions Combine all ingredients into a large soup kettle.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian Borscht Recipe</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/ukrainian-borscht-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:07:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/ukrainian-borscht-recipe/</guid><description>A Wonderful Ethnic Soup Recipe Directly from a Friendof ours from Ukraine. Katryana’s Ukrainian Borscht with Fresh Chickenwill Satisfy even a Picky Eater.
Ukrainian Borscht with Fresh Chicken Ingredients 1 whole chicken 4 beets 4 red potatoes 1 medium onion 1/2 cabbage 1 c. northern beans 1 small can tomato sauce salt and pepper to taste 1 tbsp chicken base 1/2 c. leaf basil, chopped 1/2 c. fresh parsley chopped Borscht Directions In large kettle place chicken base and chicken in 3 quarts water, boil for 1 hour.</description></item><item><title>Pumpkin Chicken Vegetable Soup</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/pumpkin-chicken-vegetable-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:03:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/pumpkin-chicken-vegetable-soup/</guid><description>Chunks of real pumpkin, sweet potato, and fall vegetables with fresh chicken, makes this recipe delicious, quick and easy. The perfect comfort soup for fall.
Pumpkin Chicken Vegetable Soup Ingredients 10 c water 3 tbs chicken base 3 ribs celery, diced 1 small onion, diced 1 small pumpkin cleaned, diced, enough for 5 cups 3 carrots, peeled, 1/2’d then sliced 2 small red potatoes, diced ( no need to peel) 1 large sweet potato, peeled, diced 1/2 chicken cut up,leg, thigh , breast, wing ( or 4 boneless chicken breasts) 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 small pinch nutmeg Pumpkin Chicken Vegetable Soup Directions Combine all ingredients into a large soup kettle.</description></item><item><title>Easy French Onion Soup Recipe</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/easy-french-onion-soup-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:59:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/easy-french-onion-soup-recipe/</guid><description>French Onion Soup, Quick and Easy Soup for Lunch With Crouton and Cheese, A Minute Under the Broiler to Brown the Cheese. Make Any Restaurant Jealous! Great with Your Favorite Sandwichor Salad.
French Onion Soup Ingredients 8 servings
2 large white or red onion, sliced, then cut in half 2 tbsp beef base 6 cups water 1 tsp garlic, chopped 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 tsp olive oil 1 c red wine (dry) Topping Ingredients 8 slices toasted bread(crust off) 8-slices swiss cheese French Onion Soup Directions In large sautee pan, medium high heat, place oil, onions, garlic and white pepper.</description></item><item><title>Cream Of Broccoli Soup Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/cream-of-broccoli-soup-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:54:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/cream-of-broccoli-soup-recipe/</guid><description>Cream of Broccoli Soup is a Hearty Quick and Easy Cream Soup Recipe For Lunch or a Meal with Your Favorite Sandwich, or Accompanying Any Salad. Cream of Broccoli is Made With Fresh Broccoli.
Cream of Broccoli Soup Ingredients Serves 8-10
4-5 cups chopped fresh broccoli 1/2 onion, diced 2 ribs celery, fine chopped 1 large carrot, 1/4’d diced roux 3 cups heavy cream 3 cups milk 1/8 tsp white pepper 1 tsp vegetable or chicken base 2 cups water Cream of Broccoli Soup Directions In large kettle, place water, carrots, onion, celery, vegetable or chicken base, and white pepper.</description></item><item><title>Clam Chowder Recipe</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/clam-chowder-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/clam-chowder-recipe/</guid><description>Clam Chowder, Quick and Easy for Your Friday Lunch or Soup and Sandwich Combo. Clam Chowder is an Easy Cream Soup Recipe and Great With Salads Too. Got Crackers?
Clam Chowder Ingredients Serves 8-10
2 c clams (canned are fine) do not drain 3 potaotoes, peeled diced 1/2 onion, diced 2 ribs celery, diced 2 large carrots, diced 1 tbsp clam base 1/4 tsp white pepper 1 tsp garlic 1 oz.</description></item><item><title>Easy Chili Con Carne</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-chili-con-carne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-chili-con-carne/</guid><description>Chili Con Carne So Quick And Easy. A Filling Meal for Lunch or Dinner. Chili Con Carne with Corn Muffins, Crackers, and A Green Leafy Salad. A Quick Easy Chili Recipe for Fall.
Chili Con Carne Ingredients 2 lbs ground beef 2 cans chili beans 1 onion, chopped 1 green pepper, chopped or diced 2 ribs celery, chopped 2 tsp garlic, chopped or granulated 2 tbsp ground cumin 1 tbsp chili powder 2 qts tomato juice 4-6 oz.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Chicken Noodle Soup Recipe</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/homemade-chicken-noodle-soup-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/homemade-chicken-noodle-soup-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Chicken Noodle Soup Recipe is made from fresh chicken meat and garden vegetables. The Noodles are from our own Recipe. Chicken Noodle Soup is a healthy lunch.
Chicken Noodle Soup Ingredients 1 lb Chicken meat, cooked, diced 3 tbsp chicken base 3 ribs celery, chopped 1 onion, diced 3 carrots, large, peeled chopped 1 tsp rubbed sage 1/4 tsp white pepper 2 tbsp dried parsley flakes 1 gallon water 1 lb egg noodles Chicken Noodle Soup Directions In large pot place all ingredients except noodles.</description></item><item><title>Beef Noodle Soup Recipe</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/beef-noodle-soup-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:35:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/beef-noodle-soup-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Noodle Soup can be made with our Homemade Noodle Recipe, and has fresh carrots, onion, celery, and diced beef. Beef Noodle Soup with salad and crackers, a very nice lunch.
Beef Noodle Soup Ingredients 1 lb Beef, diced 3 tbsp beef base 3 ribs celery, chopped 1 onion, diced 3 carrots, large, peeled chopped 1 tsp oregano 1/4 tsp white pepper 2 tbsp dried parsley flakes 1 gallon water 1 lb egg noodles Beef Noodle Soup Directions In large pot place all ingredients except noodles.</description></item><item><title>Easy Black Bean Wraps</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-black-bean-wraps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:26:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-black-bean-wraps/</guid><description>Quick Easy Black Bean Wraps Recipe is an Easy Mexican Recipe and is great for lunch or dinner. Black bean wraps are filled with black beans, vegetables, cheese and all the fixings.
Black Bean Wrap Ingredients Serves 10
10 12″ flour tortillas 2 cans black beans 1 can refried beans 2 cups rice (converted) boil with 4 c water salsa 1 diced onion 1 diced green pepper 4 diced tomatoes ( fresh) 1 lb shredded cheddar 1 tub sour cream 1 head shredded lettuce Black Bean Wrap Directions Open tortillas.</description></item><item><title>Quick Spanish Rice Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/quick-spanish-rice-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/quick-spanish-rice-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Spanish Rice is Prepped in 5 Minutes and is a Favorite Mexican Recipe too. Spanish Rice is a great Side Dish, or add Fresh Ground Beef for a Terrific Mexican Entree.
Quick Spanish Rice Ingredients 1 lb cooked ground beef optional ( for an entree) 1c converted rice 1c water 1c thick salsa 1/2 stick butter Spanish Rice Directions put all ingredients in a casserole dish, cover and place in oven at 350* for 45 min.</description></item><item><title>Easy Mexican Cheese Dip</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-mexican-cheese-dip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-mexican-cheese-dip/</guid><description>Mexican Cheese Dip with ground beef, is an easy appetizer for dipping crackers, nacho chips, and tortilla chips. This Dip is a great party staple to go with your other appetizers or for an after school snack for the kids.
Mexican Cheese Dip 1 lb soft pasteurized American cheese 1/2 c milk 1 lb ground beef, browned, drained (optional) 1/2 onion diced, sauteed 1 tbsp taco seasoning 1/2 tbsp ground cumin pepper to taste Mexican Cheese Dip Directions In large microwaveable bowl, place cheese and milk, heat for 1 minute then stir, heat again and stir add onions and seasonings and ground beef if desired.</description></item><item><title>Easy Seven Layer Dip Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-seven-layer-dip-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-seven-layer-dip-recipe/</guid><description>Great Filling Snack for Parties. Mexican Seven (7) Layer Dip with Refried Beans, Cream Cheese, Fresh Vegetables Cheese, and Salsa. Quick and Easy to make in about 10 minutes. Tortilla Chips Love Taking a Dip!
Mexican Seven (7) Layer Dip Ingredients 2 cans refried beans 1 pkg taco or burrito seasoning 8-12 oz. salsa 1 lb sour cream 8 oz. cream cheese 1 small can black olives, sliced, drained 1 fresh green pepper, diced 1 small sweet or red onion, diced 3 medium tomatoes, diced 1/2 c.</description></item><item><title>Easy Mexican Stir Fry</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-mexican-stir-fry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-mexican-stir-fry/</guid><description>Quick Easy Mexican Stir Fry Recipe, sure to become a Family Favorite Meal. Beef, Shrimp, Chicken Seasoned with fresh Vegetables. Mexican Stir Fry added to our Spanish Rice tonight. Ole’.
Mexican Stir Fry Ingredients 1 lb. beef , shrimp or chicken cut in strips (not shrimp, leave whole) 1 tbs tex-mex or chipotle seasoning 1 tsp ground cumin 1 green pepper cut in strips 1 onion cut in strips 1 c.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Grilled Shrimp Quesadillas</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/mexican-grilled-shrimp-quesadillas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/mexican-grilled-shrimp-quesadillas/</guid><description>Mexican Grilled Shrimp Quesadillas Ingredients 2-3 lbs raw peeled deveined shrimp, 21-25 size 1 c salsa 1 pkg fajita seasoning 2 c shredded cheddar 8 12″ flour tortillas 2 oz. olive oil Toppings Suggestion sliced onions and peppers (optional) sliced black olives 1 c sour cream 1/2 c jalapeno peppers 2 c shredded lettuce 2 c diced tomatoes 2 c refried beans 1 c guacamole Grilled Shrimp Quesadilla Directions Brush shrimp with olive oil and place on grill or broil until cooked, (about 2 minutes per side).</description></item><item><title>Chicken Quesadillas</title><link>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/chicken-quesadillas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:05:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/chicken-quesadillas/</guid><description>Chicken Quesadillas a Great Quick Easy Mexican Quesadilla Recipe using Fresh Chicken Breasts and Soft Tortillas. Make Fresh Salsa and Guacamole if you Desire from our Quick Easy Mexican Recipes. Quesadillas are Served for Lunch or Supper.
Quick and Easy Chicken Quesadillas Ingredients 4 boneless skinless chicken breasts cut in strips 1 c salsa 1 pkg fajita seasoning 2 c shredded cheddar 8 12″ flour tortillas Toppings Suggestion sliced onions and peppers (optional) sliced black olives 1 c sour cream 1/2 c jalapeno peppers 2 c shreeded lettuce 2 c diced tomatoes 2 c refried beans 1 c guacamole Directions In large frying pan, brown chicken until cooked then add 2 tbsp salsa and fajita seasoning to taste.</description></item><item><title>Beef Fajitas</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-fajitas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-fajitas/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Fajitas Recipe with soft tortillas and spicy beef, grilled onions, and peppers. Beef Fajitas go well with quick Spanish rice and shredded cheddar cheese.
 Beef Fajitas Ingredients 2 lb sirloin steak, cut in thin strips 1 green pepper, cut in strips 1 onion, cut in strips 2 tbsp oil 2 tbsp salsa 1 pkg fajita seasoning 1 tsp chili powder Toppings Diced tomato shredded lettuce shredded cheese sour cream salsa refried beans guacamole sliced jalapenos Beef Fajitas Directions In medium size mixing bowl, place meat, fajita seasoning, and salsa, set aside.</description></item><item><title/><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 04:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/</guid><description>Welcome to our Mexican Recipes Section. Cook and Serve Awesome Quick Mexican Recipes. Authentic Wraps, Stir Fry, Salsa, Burritos and Rice, Dips, and Sauces, All to Make You Say Ole’.
Easy Mexican Recipes   Beef Fajitas Chicken Quesadillas Steak Quesadillas Mexican Grilled Shrimp Quesadillas Guacamole Mexican Stir Fry Mexican Seven (7) Layer Dip Quick Easy Mexican Cheese Dip Quick Spanish Rice Wet Burrito Salsa Black Bean Wraps</description></item><item><title>Easy Gravy Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/easy-gravy-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 04:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/easy-gravy-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Gravy Recipes, Easily Made with Rouxand Either Chicken, Beef, Seafood, or Pork Base. Great for Mashed Potatoesand Sauces for Casserolesor Stew.
Gravy Recipe Ingredients This is a variable for beef, chicken or pork gravy.
1 tbsp Beef, chicken, seafood, or pork base / boullion (usually 1 tsp per cup of water) 3 c water 1/2 c roux Directions Boil water with base. Thicken slowly with roux to desired thickness using wire whisk.</description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/hawaiian-shrimp-brochettes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:51:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/hawaiian-shrimp-brochettes/</guid><description>Quick Easy Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes, Great for Parties and Cookouts. Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes are Festive for Any Season or Reason and Made from Garden Vegetables and Fresh Pineapple.
Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes Ingredients 1 lb shrimp, peeled deveined, raw 1 green or colored pepper, cut in 2″ squares 1 onion, large cut in 2″ pieces 1 lb. whole large mushrooms cut in 1/2 1 pint cherry tomatoes 1 fresh pineapple, cut in 2″ peices 1 pint sweet and sour sauce 1 can crushed pineapple, or pureed fresh pineapple 2 tbsp olive oil 10 skewers, metal or bamboo Hawaiian Shrimp Brochette Directions Combine crushed pineapple and sweet and sour sauce together, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp Stir Fry With Vegetables</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-stir-fry-with-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:49:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-stir-fry-with-vegetables/</guid><description>Shrimp Stir Fry Recipe is Quick And Easy with Fresh Vegetables and Shrimp, Stir Fried at 450℉ and Served over Rice or Pasta. Shrimp Stir Fry is a nice Healthy Entree for Family and Friends.
Shrimp Stir Fry Ingredients serves 10-15
3-4 lb Shrimp 21-25 count, peeled, deveined, raw 1 bunch broccoli 1 onion 2 ribs celery 1 carrot (large) 1 green pepper 4 oz. fresh pea pods 2 c cauliflower 2 c fresh bean sprouts 1 c fresh mushrooms soy sauce-to taste 2 tbsp olive oil ginger, ground or fresh grated Shrimp Stir Fry Directions Clean and cut all vegetable in about 1″ squares or strips, carrots should be sliced thin.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp Newburg</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-newburg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-newburg/</guid><description>Shrimp Newburg Directions 2 lbs shrimp,peeled, deveined, 21-25 size, raw 1/4 c small diced onion 1/4 c small diced celery 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 c roux 3 c milk 1/2 tsp paprika Shrimp Newburg Directions Prepare cream sauce by heating milk and paprika over medium heat in double boiler, or carefully in sauce pan. Stir constantly. Bring almost to light boil, add roux. Thicken with whisk to desired creaminess.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp Curry Recipe</title><link>/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-curry-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-curry-recipe/</guid><description>Curried Shrimp is a Quick Easy Seafood Recipe with Fresh Shrimp, Curry, and Vegetables. Curried Shrimp uses Different Curry Strengths to your Taste.</description></item><item><title>Pork Chops With Yellow and Green Beans</title><link>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/pork-chops-with-yellow-and-green-beans/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/pork-chops-with-yellow-and-green-beans/</guid><description>Pork with Yellow and Green Beans is a Quick Easy Recipe on the Stove. Fresh Pork, Tomato Juice, Seasonings, and Beans over Rice makes Mealtime Easy and Delicious. Grandma Served up Homemade Bread with this Meal!
Pork with Yellow and Green Beans Ingredients served over rice. Serves about 6-8 people
6 pork chops cut in bite size pieces 2 cans yellow beans, drained 2 cans green beans, drained 1/2 onion, diced 2 qts tomato juice 1/4 tsp white pepper 1/2 tsp garlic granulated or chopped 1 tbsp butter Pork With Yello and Green Beans Directions Use electric skillet or large frying pan on top of the stove, brown pork chops and onion together with butter and spices.</description></item><item><title>Pork Chops Recipe With Mushroom Gravy</title><link>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/pork-chops-recipe-with-mushroom-gravy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:33:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/pork-chops-recipe-with-mushroom-gravy/</guid><description>Pork Chops With Mushroom Gravy Is a Quick Easy Recipe for Anytime of the Week. Brown Pork Chops, then add Mushroom Soup For Gravy. Mashed Potatoes Compliment this Standard Recipe.
Pork Chops with Mushroom Gravy Ingredients Serves 4
4 pork chops 1 can cream of mushroom soup 1/4 onion diced 1 can mushroom 1 pat butter Pork Chops With Mushroom Gravy Directions In large fry pan put butter and melt medium high heat.</description></item><item><title>Southern Fried Pork Chops</title><link>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/southern-fried-pork-chops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:28:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/southern-fried-pork-chops/</guid><description>Fried Pork Chops, Quick Easy Southern Recipe Using Egg, Milk, and Spices Then Rolled in Crushed Crackers and Fried. Fried Pork Chops for Supper Tonight! How Easy is That!
Fried Pork Chops Ingredients 6 pork chops 1 sleeve saltines, crushed 2 eggs 1/2 c milk pepper to taste 1 1/2 c cooking oil Southern Fried Pork Chops Directions Put eggs and milk in a bowl and blend together. In separate bowl put flour.</description></item><item><title>Applesauce Dijon Pork Roast</title><link>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/applesauce-dijon-pork-roast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-pork-recipes/applesauce-dijon-pork-roast/</guid><description>Michigan applesauce is wonderful for this Pork loin with dijon and a little Marsala wine marinade. Break out the barbecue grill because summer grilling is recommended.
Applesauce Dijon Pork Loin Chops Ingredients 6-8# pork loin (cut into 1/2″ chops or leave whole) Marinade 2 c. applesauce 1/4 c. dijon mustard 1/4 c. brown sugar 8 oz. apple juice 2 tsp soy sauce 4 oz. marsala wine Pork Chops Mix marinade together well.</description></item><item><title>Southern Style Fried Chicken</title><link>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/southern-style-fried-chicken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/southern-style-fried-chicken/</guid><description>Quick Easy Fried Chicken Recipe Made Southern Style with Egg and Milk Batter Then Rolled in Crushed Saltines and spices. Call in the Kids, It’s Fried Chicken Tonight!
Fried Chicken Southern Style Ingredients 2 chickens cut in 1/8’s 1 sleeve saltines, crushed 2 eggs 1/2 c milk pepper to taste oil and pan for deep frying Fried Chicken Southern Style Directions Put eggs and milk in a bowl and blend together.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Chicken Strips</title><link>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/homemade-chicken-strips/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/homemade-chicken-strips/</guid><description>Quick Easy Chicken Strips Recipe Made with Real Chicken Breasts Cut in Strips, Dipped in Egg Wash, and Rolled in Crushed Crackers. Fry and Serve as Entree. Kids Love Them Too! Try Our Potato Wedgeswith Sour Cream as a Side. Fresh Vegetables with Dip Balance out This Great Lunch.
Chicken Strips Quick and Easy Ingredients 3 lbs raw chicken breast meat, cut in strips 1 sleeve saltines, crushed 2 eggs 1/2 c milk pepper to taste 1 1/2 c cooking oil Chicken Strips Directions Put eggs and milk in a bowl and blend together.</description></item><item><title>Easy Chicken Stir Fry</title><link>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/easy-chicken-stir-fry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 01:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/easy-chicken-stir-fry/</guid><description>Esy Chicken Stir Fry Recipe is a ten minute prep, served over any rice. Fresh vegetables and chicken stir fried at 450℉. Chicken Stir Fry for a Quick Easy Dinner tonight!
Chicken Stir Fry Ingredients serves 10-15
3-4 lbs chicken cooked, diced or stripped 1 bunch broccoli 1 onion 2 ribs celery 1 carrot (large) 1 green pepper 4 oz. fresh pea pods 2 c cauliflower 2 c fresh bean sprouts 1 c fresh mushrooms soy sauce-to taste 2 tbsp olive oil ginger, ground or fresh grated Chicken Stir Fry Directions Clean and cut all vegetable in about 1″ squares ir strips, carrots should be sliced thin.</description></item><item><title>How To Make Chicken Pot Pie</title><link>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/how-to-make-chicken-pot-pie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/how-to-make-chicken-pot-pie/</guid><description>Quick easy Chicken Pot Pie Recipe is made from fresh boiled chicken, vegetables, gravy, and pie crust. Chicken Pot Pie is a wonderful recipe for fall or winter.
Chicken Pot Pie Ingredients 2 pkg pie crust, 2 crusts, 9″ 1 whole chicken (fryer) 4 carrots, peeled, sliced 4 potatoes, peeled, large cut 1 onion diced 2 ribs celery, diced 1 tbsp chicken base 1 tsp rubbed sage 1/2 tsp white pepper 4 cups water 1/2 c roux Chicken Pot Pie Directions Place chicken, spices, and vegetables in large kettle.</description></item><item><title>Easy Swiss Steak Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-swiss-steak-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:37:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-swiss-steak-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Swiss Steak Recipe uses Fresh Round Steak or Sirloin, Rolled in flour, Spices, and Browned in Butter. Swiss Steak Entree and Mashed Potatoes with a Vegetable is a Satisfying Meal and Leaves Everyone Full and Happy.
Swiss Steak Ingredients serves 4
1 lb round steak or sirloin steak, cut in 4 0z portions 1 onion sliced 1 can diced tomatoes (optional) 1/2 green pepper diced 2 tsp beef base 2 cups water salt and pepper to taste 1 c flour 2 0z.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Salisbury Steak</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/homemade-salisbury-steak/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/homemade-salisbury-steak/</guid><description>Quick Easy Salisbury Steak recipe with fresh ground beef, onion, green pepper, eggs and spices. Salisbury Steak is a favorite with mashed redskin potatoes and beef mushroom gravy.
Salisbury Steak With Fresh Ground Beef Ingredients serves 8-12
3 lb ground beef 3 eggs 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1/2 sleeve saltines, crushed 1 tsp worcestershire sauce 1/2 tbsp garlic, chopped or granulated Salisbury Steak Directions In large mixing bowl place all ingredients and mix well.</description></item><item><title>Beef Pot Roast Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-roast-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-roast-recipe/</guid><description>Beef Pot Roast for a Delicious Supper is a Quick Easy Recipe with Potatoes and Carrots, and only takes 15 Minutes to Prepare, then place in Oven to Roast. Sunday we’re having Pot Roast!
Pot Roast of Beef (English cut or Chuck) Ingredients serves 8
3-4 lb roast 1 onion cut in chunks 8 potatoes peeled, cut in half 8 carrots peeled, cut in 1/4’s 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/8 tsp white pepper 1 tsp garlic (granulated or fresh) 2 c water Directions Place water and roast in roasting pan.</description></item><item><title>Baked Corned Beef Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/baked-corned-beef-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 23:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/baked-corned-beef-recipe/</guid><description>Roasted Corned Beef Recipe is Quick and Easy with a spicy mustard and honey seasoning. Roasted Corned Beef is a great Fall recipe and goes well with red potatoes and cabbage.
Baked Corned Beef Ingredients (with Honey Mustard Optional) serves 10-14
3-5 lb corned beef brisket (raw, usually contains season packet) 1 c dijon mustard 1/4 c honey 1 tsp garlic, granulated or fresh chopped (in jars at your grocers) 1/8 tsp white pepper 1/2 c apple juice Baked Corned Beef Directions Using a roaster, pour in apple juice.</description></item><item><title>Healthy Meatloaf Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/healthy-meatloaf-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/healthy-meatloaf-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Meatloaf Recipe from Mom’s Cupboard is made from Fresh Ground Beef, Onions, Celery, Eggs, Bread, and Spices. Meatloaf also makes Good Leftovers for Sandwiches or just re-heat and eat.
Meatloaf Ingredients serves4-6
2 lb. ground beef 3 eggs 1/2 onion diced 1 rib celery cut into small pieces. 1 c ketchup 1/2 tsp garlic, (chopped or granulated) 1 1/2 cups bread crumbs 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce pepper to taste season salt to taste, or1/2 tsp 1/2 c water Directions In a large mixing bowl, soak the bread in the water, then add everything but the ground beef and mix well.</description></item><item><title>Irish Steak and Dark Beer Pie</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/irish-steak-and-dark-beer-pie/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/irish-steak-and-dark-beer-pie/</guid><description>Celebrate St Patrick’s Day anytime with our Irish Steak and Dark Beer Pie Recipe. An Easy and Fun Supper to Make and Quick to Disappear. An Irish Entree Recipe Everyone will Love.
Irish Steak and Dark Beer Pie serves 6
2 pkg pie crust (or crust for two 9″ pies) 3 lbs sirloin steak, cut in 2″ long thin strips 3-4 bottles dark beer 1 bunch scallions (green onions) chopped 1 lb sliced fresh mushrooms 1/2 red onion sliced or diced 4 large red potatoes thinly sliced 4 carrots, peeled sliced thin 1 tsp beef base 2 or more tbs roux Directions For The Pie Place thinly sliced steak in frying pan to brown on high heat, (be careful not to put too much in or it could get watery).</description></item><item><title>Hamburger Gravy Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/hamburger-gravy-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/hamburger-gravy-recipe/</guid><description>Simple hamburger gravy on the nights you’re in a rush. Put over mashed potatoes and it only takes a few minutes to prepare. Goes well with salads, vegetables or breads.
Hamburger Gravy – Simple Family Dinner Recipe 1 lb. ground beef 1/2 c. chopped onion 1/2 c. flour 1 tsp beef base 3 c. water Directions Brown ground beef with onions in large frying pan. When ground beef is cooked, add beef base and sprinkle flour over ground beef and stir together over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Beef Tips And Noodles Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-tips-and-noodles-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-tips-and-noodles-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Tips and Noodles is an easy recipe to prepare and serve for supper. Beef Tips and Noodlesrecipe is made from diced beef, thick gravy, and noodles. A delicious comfort food.
Beef Tips and Noodles serves4-6
1 lb. diced beef 1/2 onion diced 1 rib celery diced small 1 lb pasta 1 lb. roux 1 tbsp beef base 1 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp garlic granulated dash pepper Directions Brown beef in pan then transfer to large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Quick Beef Stew</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/quick-beef-stew/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/quick-beef-stew/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Stew will warm your heart and tummy. Beef Stew with vegetables and thick gravy is great with biscuits and a salad or fruit. Beef Stew always makes good leftovers.
Beef Stew Recipe serves4-6
1 lb diced beef 2 large carrots 2 ribs celery 1 lg onion 3-4 lg potatoes 1 tbsp beef base garlic, salt &amp;amp; pepper to taste Directions Clean and cut vegetables into desired size.</description></item><item><title>Easy Beef Stir Fry Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-beef-stir-fry-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-beef-stir-fry-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Stir Fry with Fresh Vegetables, Served over rice with egg rolls and soy sauce. Beef Stir Fry is Healthy and easy for those in-a-hurry times.
Beef Stir Fry serves 10-15
3-4 lbs beef steak, cut in strips 1 bunch broccoli 1 onion 2 ribs celery 1 carrot (large) 1 green pepper 4 oz. fresh pea pods 2 c cauliflower 2 c fresh bean sprouts 1 c fresh mushrooms soy sauce-to taste 2 tbsp olive oil ginger, ground or fresh grated Directions Clean and cut all vegetable in about 1″ squares in strips, carrots should be sliced thin.</description></item><item><title>Beef Pot Pie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-pie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-pie-recipe/</guid><description>Beef Pot Pie is a quick and easy recipe for supper tonight. Fresh beef sirloin and vegetables in a thick gravy with a golden crust. Very delicious Beef Pot Pie.
Beef Pot Pie Recipe 2 pkg pie crust, 2 crusts, 9″ 1 lb.diced beef(sirloin) 4 carrots, peeled, sliced 4 potatoes, peeled, large cut 1 onion diced 2 ribs celery, diced 1 tbsp beef base 1/2 tsp white pepper 4 cups water 1/2 c roux Directions Place beef, spices, and vegetables in large kettle.</description></item><item><title>Tana’s Country Style Chicken Kiev Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/tanas-country-style-chicken-kiev-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/tanas-country-style-chicken-kiev-recipe/</guid><description>Tana’s Country Style Chicken Kiev Recipe is a Quick Easy way to a Wonderful Meal. For Holidays or Everyday Entrees. Serve with any Rice, Side Dish, Fruit, or Hot Vegetable.
Tana’s Country Style Chicken Kiev Recipe from Tana B.
4 chicken breast halves 1/4 c white wine, or apple juice 1/2 c sweet cream butter 1/2 to 1 c fine dry bread crumbs 1/4 c chopped green onion 1/4 c chopped fresh parsley (or dried) 2 tbs grated parmesan cheese 1 tsp basil leaves 1 tsp oregano leaves 1/2 tsp garlic salt 1/4 tsp salt Heat oven to 375℉.</description></item><item><title>Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/sandys-sausage-and-cheese-dip-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/sandys-sausage-and-cheese-dip-recipe/</guid><description>Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip Recipe is Fun for Partiesor an Easy Snack While Watching Sports or your Favorite Movie. Tortilla Chips are Best Friends with Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip.
Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip Recipe Recipe from Sandy R.
1/2 lb. ground beef 1/2 lb. pork sausage ( brand name or bulk ground) 1 lb. pkg processed soft american cheese 1 10 oz. can cr. of mushroom soup 1/2 c finely chopped onion 1/2 c picante sauce 1/2 tsp garlic powder Cook beef and sausage in large kettle until browned.</description></item><item><title>Molly’s White Chili Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/mollys-white-chili-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/mollys-white-chili-recipe/</guid><description>Molly’s White Chili Recipe is not only Easy to Make, it’s delicious and cheap. Top with Sour Cream or Thicken with Pureed Garbonzo or Northern Beans. You can Use your Imagination with this Recipe. You can add Red Pepper too!
Molly’s White Chili, Easy, Cheap, and Good Recipe from Molly P.
2 cans chicken broth 3 cans cooked chicken (or leftovers cut up) 1 jar or 3 cans northern beans 2 cans chopped green chilies 1 brick Monterey jack cheese for topping ( shredded or cut up) Directions In large soup kettle combine broth, chicken, beans, and green chilies.</description></item><item><title>Kory’s 2nd Grade Voyageur Stew</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/korys-2nd-grade-voyageur-stew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/korys-2nd-grade-voyageur-stew/</guid><description>This Recipe for Kory’s 2nd Grade Voyageur Stew is Hearty, Easy, and Fun. The Kids Love to Help Make This While Camping or at Home “Chillin” With The Family. Don’t Forget the Dutch Oven!
Kory’s 2nd Grade Voyageur Stew Recipe from Kathy F.
2 lbs. ground beef 1-2 chopped onions 1 can vegetable soup 1 can cut carrots 1 can corn 1 can peas 1 can green beans 2 cans small potatoes 1 48 oz.</description></item><item><title>Monkey Bread Coffee Cake Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/monkey-bread-coffee-cake-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:06:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/monkey-bread-coffee-cake-recipe/</guid><description>Kathy’s Monkey Bread Coffee Cake Recipe is nice for Sunday Morning Breakfast, or when your Scrap booking with Friends. Makes a Great Starter or Dessertfor Favorite Meals too! Can you Smell the Aroma?
Kathy’s Monkey Bread Coffee Cake Recipe From Kathy F.
3 cans buttermilk biscuits 1 stick margerine 3 tsp cinnamon 1 c sugar 1 c brown sugar Directions Preheat oven to 350℉
Cut each biscuit into 4 pieces.</description></item><item><title>Kathy’s Moist and Juicy Pork Chops</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/kathys-moist-and-juicy-pork-chops/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:03:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/kathys-moist-and-juicy-pork-chops/</guid><description>Kathy’s Moist and Juicy Pork Chops Recipe is so Quick and Easy to Prepare, About Ten Minutes and in the Oven it Goes! Ground Cloves, Applesauceand Brown Sugar is the Secret Revealed! Enjoy for Supper Tonight!
Kathy’s Moist and Juicy Pork Chops Recipe From Kathy F.
4-6 pork chops browned Mix:
1 c applesauce 1/3 c brown sugar 1/4 tsp ground cloves Place pork chops in baking dish.</description></item><item><title>Karen’s Grape Salad</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/karens-grape-salad/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/karens-grape-salad/</guid><description>This Wonderful Salad Made from Fresh Grapes is Great for Potluck Dinners, Holidays, Picnics and Barbecues,or Anytime, and can be Made the Night Before.
Karen’s Grape Salad Recipe From Karen A.
8 oz. cream cheese 1 c sour cream 1/2 c sugar 1 tsp vanilla Beat together until smooth Mix with 2 lbs. washed seedless grapes ( red green or both) Put into dish or 9×13 pan
Sprinkle top with 1 c brown sugar and 1 c chopped pecans</description></item><item><title>Jamie’s Mothership Tomato Salad</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/jamies-mothership-tomato-salad/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/jamies-mothership-tomato-salad/</guid><description>Jamie’s Mothership Tomato Salad is Fantastic and is Totally Delicious to Eat on it’s Own. It’s also Great Served with some Balls of Mozzerella and nice, Grilled Ciabatta Bread.
Jamie’s Mothership Tomato Salad Recipe from Jamie O.
Ingredients 2 1/4 lbs mixed ripe tomatoes, different shapes and colors sea salt and freshly ground pepper to taste a good pinch of dried oregano Red wine or balsamic vinegar extra virgin olive oil 1 clove garlic, peeled, grated 1 fresh red chili, deseeded and chopped Directions Depending on the size of your tomatoes, slice some in half and some in quarters and others into uneven chunks.</description></item><item><title>Dottie’s Salmon Patties</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/dotties-salmon-patties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/dotties-salmon-patties/</guid><description>Dottie’s Salmon Patties Recipe is Easy to Make and goes with a Spring Salad, Fresh Fruits and Vegetables, or Sandwiches. Dotties Salmon Patties are Wonderful and Versatile, use Your Imagination.
Dottie’s Salmon Patties Recipe from Dottie F.
Makes 6 Patties
1- 15oz. can salmon 16 saltine crackers 2 eggs some milk ( just enough to moisten) salt and pepper to taste 1/2 onion, diced small (optional) Directions Mix altogether, make patties, fry in pan in light oil until golden brown- makes 6 patties.</description></item><item><title>Easy Taco Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/easy-taco-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:48:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/easy-taco-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Colleen’s Taco Salad will be the Hit of any Party or Bring a Pleasant Southwest Atmosphere to any Supper Table. Fresh Ground Beef and Seasonings Make this recipe because it is easy to prepare and enjoy.
Colleen’s Taco Salad Ingredients Ground Beef Directions 1 lb. ground beef Browned 1 med. diced onion Drain off Fat 1 pkg taco seasoning mix (any kind) mix with onion and burger (prepare as directed) 1 pkg lettuce (regular or shredded) 1 can sliced black olives 3 diced roma tomatoes 1 pkg shredded cheddar cheese 1 pkg tortilla chips ( any flavor you like) 1 med.</description></item><item><title>Meatloaf Portabella Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/meatloaf-portabella-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/meatloaf-portabella-recipe/</guid><description>Ann’s Meatloaf Portabella Starts with Fresh Ground Chuck, Garden Squash, and Portabella Mushrooms. Wonderful Comfort Food Entree goes well with Mashed Potatoes, Gravy, and Hot Vegetables.
Ann’s Meatloaf Portabella Recipe from Ann L.
serves 6-8
3-4 lbs. ground chuck 8-12 oz. portabella mushrooms diced 5 eggs 1 lb colby jack cheese, shredded 1 small zucchini diced 1 small summer squash diced 3 cloves garlic fine diced 2-3 tomatoes crushed 1 small sweet onion diced 1 tbs salt-less seasoning 2 tsp course ground black pepper Directions In large bowl mix together all ingredients.</description></item><item><title>How To Make A Rainbow Cake By Angie</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/how-to-make-a-rainbow-cake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/how-to-make-a-rainbow-cake/</guid><description>Angie’s “How to Make a Rainbow Cake” Recipe is Perfect for KidsBirthdays, Easter, any Family Celebrations. Angie say’s Once your Kids Have One, they Want One Forever!Angie’s How to Make a Rainbow Cake!Once your kids have one, they want one forever!
Recipe from Angie M.
Use one box of white cake mix, follow directions on box.
Split the batter into 6 equal parts using cereal bowls.
Color and mix together each bowl as follows:</description></item><item><title>Angie’s Crescent Turkey Casserole</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/angies-crescent-turkey-casserole/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/angies-crescent-turkey-casserole/</guid><description>Angie’s Crescent Turkey Casserole is Easy to Prepare in a Slow Cooker while Away, or at Home in Time for Supper. We have to Call this Comfort Food. Serve with Salads, Fresh Vegetables or Fruits. Ready in 30 Minutes.
Angie’s Crescent Turkey Casserole 4 servings
Recipe from Angie G.
Prep/total time 30 min.
1/2 c mayonnaise (canola) 2 tbs all-purpose flour 1 tsp chicken boullion 1/8 tsp pepper 3/4 c milk (1%) 1 1/2 c cubed cooked turkey breast ( or chicken) 1 pkg ( 10 oz.</description></item><item><title>Amy’s Chocolate Scotcheroos</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/amys-chocolate-scotcheroos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/amys-chocolate-scotcheroos/</guid><description>Cure your Sweet Tooth With Amy’s Chocolate Scotcheroos and don’t forget to share. This Dessert will Please the Pickiest Eaters.
Amy’s Chocolate Scotcheroos Recipe Recipe from Amy F.
Makes 48 bars
1 c light corn syrup 1 c sugar 1 c peanut butter 6 cups crispy rice cereal 1 c semi sweet chocolate chips 1 c butterscotch chips Vegetable cooking spray Directions Place corn syrup and sugar into a large saucepan.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Spaghetti Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-spaghetti-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-spaghetti-recipe/</guid><description>Vegetarian Homemade Spaghetti Sauce with Optional TVP (textured vegetable protein) is Quick and Easy to Make. Let Simmer on the Stove, Crockpot, or in the Oven. Our Homemade Scratch Spaghetti Sauce Recipes are a Breeze for Busy People. Serve over Penne, Ravioli, Spaghetti Pasta, and Makes an Excellent Pizza Sauce too.
Vegetarian Spaghetti Sauce Ingredients **12+ servings
**
1/2 c dried tvp(textured vegetable protein) optional, but a good source of protein.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Split Pea Soup</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-split-pea-soup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-split-pea-soup/</guid><description>Vegetarian Split Pea Soup is a Quick Easy Recipe to Warm up any Cold Day. Our split pea soup recipe has fresh carrots, onion, celery, and potatoes, slow cooked for perfection. Break out the crackers.
Vegetarian Split Pea Soup Ingredients serves 10+
1 lb dried split peas 1 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced 2-3 potatoes, peeled, diced 3 carrots, peeled, diced 3 tbsp vegetable base (boullion) 8 c water 1/2 tsp white pepper Directions In large soup kettle, place all ingredients except peas.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Northern Michigan Bean Soup</title><link>/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-northern-michigan-bean-soup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-northern-michigan-bean-soup/</guid><description>Vegetarian Northern Michigan Bean Soup is a Quick and Easy Comfort Soup Recipe. Soak the Beans a Day Ahead in the Fridge. Easy Next Day Prep. Great With Sandwiches, Muffins, Crackers or Salads.
This soup is a staple for Northern Michigan and is easy to prepare!
Northern Bean Soup Ingredients serves 10+
_It is important to soak beans overnight in water, and place in fridge. Drain water before adding to vegetables and broth.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Chili Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-chili-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:22:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-chili-recipe/</guid><description>Vegetarian Mexican Chili a Quick Easy Recipe for Lunch or Dinner. Vegetarian Mexican Chili with Corn Muffins, Crackers, and A Green Leafy Salad or Sandwich. A True Comfort Food Soup.
Vegetarian Chili Ingredients 2 cans chili beans 1 onion, chopped 1 green pepper, chopped or diced 2 ribs celery, chopped 2 tsp garlic, chopped or granulated 2 tbsp ground cumin 1 tbsp chili powder 2 qts tomato juice 4-6 oz.</description></item><item><title>Easy Apple Pie</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-pie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-pie/</guid><description>Apple Pie with Michigan Apples is Quick to Prepare and Easy to Eat. Using Fresh Apples for This Apple Pie Recipe, Tops off any Meal, Top that with Vanilla Ice Cream or Cheese.
Easy Apple Pie Recipe 1 pkg Pie crust for 2 crust pie, 9″ 6-8 Michigan spies, or granny smith apples (peeled and thinly sliced) 3/4 c sugar 1 tsp lemon juice 3 1/2 tbsp quick tapioca 1/8 tsp salt 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1/8 tsp ground nutmeg 2 tbsp butter, melted Directions Press one crust in pie shell, don’t trim</description></item><item><title>How To Make An Egg Wash</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-an-egg-wash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-an-egg-wash/</guid><description>Quick Easy Egg Wash Recipe for Putting a Shine on all your Pie and Pastry Crusts. Egg Wash Takes a Minute to Prepare and adds Eye Appeal to your Pie and Pastry Recipes.
If you’re Making a Fruit Pie, Sprinkle a Little Sugar on Top of your Crust After you Brush it with Egg Wash.
Egg Wash Ingredients Enough for 2 pies
1 egg 1 oz. water Directions Whisk together.</description></item><item><title>Easy Apple Dumplings</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-dumplings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:06:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-dumplings/</guid><description>Apple Dumplings Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare for Family and Guests. Warm Apple Dumplings a Great Recipe to Top off with Ice Cream. Serve Warm Apple Dumplings for a Party Finale.
Apple Dumplings Ingredients serves 8
1 pkg pie crusts, cut in quarters 5 tart Michigan apples, peeled, diced 1/2 c sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 2 0z. butter, melted 1 tbsp quick tapioca Directions Place quartered crusts in greased muffin tin cups, leaving top open.</description></item><item><title>How To Make Roux</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-roux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-roux/</guid><description>Roux is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare for Thickening Gravies and Sauces. Use Roux in Making Cream Soup Recipes like Clam Chowder and Cream of Broccoli Soup. Stews and Desserts too.
Roux Ingredients 1 lb butter or margarine 1 lb flour Directions Heat butter in small sauce pan until it comes to a boil. Add flour, mix well and set aside. May be held for up to two weeks in fridge.</description></item><item><title>Scalloped Corn Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/scalloped-corn-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/scalloped-corn-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Scalloped Corn Recipe served at Sunday Dinner with Roast Chickenis the best! Scalloped Corn is a five minute prep and is a Delicious Hot Vegetablefor Holidays too!
Scalloped Corn Ingredients 3 cans creamed corn 3 eggs 1 1/2 sleeve saltines (crushed) 1/4 stick butter (melted) 1/8 cup milk pepper to taste (avoid salt as saltines contain enough) Directions In large mixing bowl add corn, 1 sleeve crackers (crushed), eggs, butter, and milk.</description></item><item><title>Easy Twice Baked Potato</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-twice-baked-potato/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:20:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-twice-baked-potato/</guid><description>Quick Easy Twice Baked Potatoes Recipe ia a Standard for the Holidays. Twice Baked Potatoes with Sour Cream, Chives, and Cheddar Cheese is Delicious.Simple and Delicious Twice Baked PotatoesTwice Baked Potatoes Ingredients Serves 10
5 russet baking potatoes(large) 3 oz butter 1/2 c sour cream 1 c shredded cheddar cheese salt and pepper to taste paprika Directions Bake potatoes at 375℉ for one hour. Remove from oven and let cool only long enough to cut in half.</description></item><item><title>Healthy Sweet Potato Casserole</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/healthy-sweet-potato-casserole/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/healthy-sweet-potato-casserole/</guid><description>Sweet Potato Casserole with Michigan Apples and Cranberries Compliment Porkand Chicken EntreeDishes. An easy Side Dish for Get Togethers with Family and Friends or for the Holidays.
Sweet Potato Casserole with Michigan Apples and Cranberries Ingredients serves10-12
6 large sweet potatoes( peeled cut in chunks) 1 lb fresh cranberries 3 large Michigan apples (peeled and cut bite size) 2 c apple juice or cider Directions Put ingredients in baking dish, cover, and bake 350℉ for 1 hour</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Acorn Squash Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/stuffed-acorn-squash-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/stuffed-acorn-squash-recipe/</guid><description>Quick and Easy Stuffed Acorn Squash for the Fall and Holiday Season. Use Fresh Acorn Squash in Season, it’s Easily Stuffed and Satisfying.
Stuffed Acorn Squash Ingredients 2 acorn squash cut in 1/2 (from top to bottom) remove seeds 2 lbs ground pork sausage 2 tart apples, peeled, diced small 1 c chopped walnuts 1/2 onion small diced 2 ribs celery small diced 1 tbsp rubbed sage 2 tbsp maple syrup (imitation is fine) 2 eggs 1 tbsp brown sugar Directions In large mixing bowl place all ingredients (except squash), and mix well.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Red Potatoes Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/roasted-red-potatoes-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/roasted-red-potatoes-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Roasted Red Potatoes Recipe With Fresh Summer Squash, Onion, Carrots and Rosemary, Roasted with Olive Oil and Spices. Great for The Fall Season.
Roasted Red Potatoes with Vegetables Ingredients serves 6-8
2 lbs red potatoes, rinsed, cut in 1/2 3 ribs celery, rinsed, angle cut, chunky 1 onion , peeled and quartered 4 carrots, peeled cut in chunks 1 summer squash, cut chunky 1 zucchini squash, cut chunky 2 0z.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Mashed Potatoes Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/homemade-mashed-potatoes-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/homemade-mashed-potatoes-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Mashed Potatoes Recipe can be made with Red, White, Russet or a Combination of any of these. Mashed Potatoes are an American Staple.
Mashed Potatoes Ingredients 2 lbs. potatoes, peeled and cut 2 tbsp butter 1/2 c milk dash salt Note: There are a number of kinds of potatoes you can use. russets, U.S. no.1’s, yellow, white and even sweet potatoes. You can even mix varieties.</description></item><item><title>Lobster Thermidor Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/lobster-thermidor-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:59:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/lobster-thermidor-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Lobster Thermidor Recipe is made from Maine or African Rock Lobster. An Elegant Recipe for a Special Dinner. Lobster Thermidor is easy to Prepare and Serve.
Lobster Thermidor Ingredients 3 lb lobster, steamed, cut in 1/2 6 c milk 1 c roux 1 tbsp dry mustard 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1/4 c chopped parsley 3 oz. parmesan cheese Directions Heat milk for cream sauce, thicken with roux.</description></item><item><title>Simple Green Bean Casserole</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/simple-green-bean-casserole/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/simple-green-bean-casserole/</guid><description>Quick Easy Green Bean Casserole is a standard Recipe used for Holidays and everyday meals. Green Bean Casserole topped with Fried Onions and Cheese will Shake Up your Meals!A Simple and Healthy Green Bean CasseroleGreen Bean Casserole Ingredients serves 8 -10
2 cans green beans, drained 1 can cream of mushroom soup 1/2 c shredded or diced cheddar cheese (optional) 2 tbsp melted butter French fried onions Directions Mix green beans with undiluted mushroom soup and melted butter.</description></item><item><title>Grandma’s Fried Chicken</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/grandmas-fried-chicken/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/grandmas-fried-chicken/</guid><description>I remember being at my grandmother’s house on any Sunday and smelling the aroma from her awesome cooking. Grandmas chicken that she pan fried, then placed in a slow oven. She always had scalloped corn, mashed potatoes and gravy ( made from the chicken pan), Rolls, relish tray, and three layer jello with cream cheese in the middle for dessert. I love to create similar memories for my family. I thank my grandmother for taking the time to show me some of her methods.</description></item><item><title>Easy Coq Au Vin Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-coq-au-vin-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-coq-au-vin-recipe/</guid><description>Whole Chicken cut up, Shallots, Onion, and Hearty Burgundy Wine. French Coq Au Vin is served with Wild Rice and any Side Dish Recipe.
Coq Au Vin (Chicken and Wine) Ingredients serves 4
1 whole chicken cut up 1 gallon hearty burgundy wine 1/2 c. diced shallots 1/2 stick butter 1/2 red onion diced 1 c. fresh sliced mushrooms 1 dash salt and pepper Directions Place butter in large stock pot and melt on stove.</description></item><item><title>Easy Chicken Cordon Bleu</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-chicken-cordon-bleu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-chicken-cordon-bleu/</guid><description>Quick Easy Chicken Cordon Bleu will Make Your Guests Marvel at Your Expertise. This Chicken Cordon Bleu Recipe Is From Italy and Derived form the French Cuisines. Uses Heavy Cream, Brie, and White Wine.
Chicken Cordon Bleu Ingredients serves 4 4 chicken breasts, boneless, skinless 4 slices ham 4 oz. Brie cheese 4 oz. bread crumbs 2 c flour 2-3 c heavy cream 4 oz. white dry wine 2 oz. maitre d’ butter Directions Lay chicken breast between plastic wrap.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Almondine Flambe’</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/chicken-almondine-flambe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/chicken-almondine-flambe/</guid><description>Chicken Almondine Flambe’ is a Quick Easy Recipe that is Elegant and literally on Fire! Use Chicken, Madeira Wine, Fresh Mushrooms, Onions, and Almonds to Create Chicken Almondine Flambe’.
Chicken Almondine Flambe’ Ingredients serves 4
4 chicken breasts, cut in 1″ cubes or strips 1 c. slice fresh mushrooms 1/2 onion diced 1/4 c. sliced almonds 3 oz. maitre d’ butter 1 c. madeira wine 2 c. Flour 1 tsp.</description></item><item><title>Cheese Broccoli Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/cheese-broccoli-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/cheese-broccoli-recipe/</guid><description>Broccoli and Cheese is the Perfect Hot Vegetable Recipeto Accompany Pork, Beefor Chicken Entrees. Broccoli and Cheese is Quick and Easy to Make and Serve.
Broccoli and Cheese Ingredients serves 2
2 stalks fresh broccoli, cut in sprigs 1/2 c shredded cheese 1 oz. butter 1/8 tsp salt Directions In sauce pan place water, salt, and broccoli.
Bring to boil and let slow boil for 3 minutes.
Remove from water and place on plate.</description></item><item><title>Easy Cheese Ball Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-cheese-ball-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:17:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-cheese-ball-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Cheese Balls Recipe is for the Holidays with crackers and other Appetizers. Cheese Balls take 15 minutes to prepare, and are eye appealing too!
Cheese Ball Ingredients 2 8oz. cream cheese 1lb brick cheddar cheese (shredded) 1 med onion finely chopped 3 tsp worcestershire sauce 1-2 tsp milk 1 tsp garlic (fresh or granulated) 1/2 c chopped nuts (pecans) Directions Mix all ingredients together. Form two balls evenly then roll in nuts.</description></item><item><title>Apple Sage and Walnut Stuffing Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/apple-sage-and-walnut-stuffing-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/apple-sage-and-walnut-stuffing-recipe/</guid><description>Apple Sage and Walnut Stuffing Recipe Made with Michigan Apples is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Apple Sage Walnut Stuffing for your Thanksgiving MealWill ad a Warm Charm to your Holiday Feast.
Apple Sage Walnut Stuffing Ingredients 6 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 rib celery diced 2 tbsp sage rubbed 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 Michigan tart apple peeled, diced 1 c chopped walnuts 1/2 stick butter 1/8 tsp white pepper dash garlic, granulated Directions Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Michigan Apple Sage Stuffing</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sage-stuffing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sage-stuffing/</guid><description>Apple Sage Stuffing Recipe Made with Michigan Apples is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Even Using Fresh Grown Sage. Apple Sage Stuffing for the Holidays will Enhance Your Holiday Meal.
Apple Sage Stuffing Ingredients 6 c water 2 tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 rib celery diced 2 tbsp sage rubbed 1 Michigan tart apple peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1/8 tsp white pepper dash garlic, granulated Directions Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Michigan Apple Sauce</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sauce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sauce/</guid><description>Michigan applesauce is easy to prepare on the stove, and using tart Michigan apples is the only way to go.
Michigan Apple Sauce Recipe 5 tart Michigan apples, peeled, chunked 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/2 c sugar 1/4 c water Directions Place all ingredients in sauce pan. Cook on low heat, stirring often. Applesauce is done when apples are incorporated and soft. Serve as a side dish with ham, or pork, or by itself as a snack.</description></item><item><title>Baked Acorn Squash Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/baked-acorn-squash-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/baked-acorn-squash-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Baked Acorn Squash, a staple for any holiday dinneror a great hot vegetablefor any fall meal. Baked Acorn Squash is Easy in the microwave or oven. Top your Holidays with this great recipe.
Acorn Squash 2 acorn squash 3 tbsp brown sugar 3 oz. butter, melted salt and pepper to taste Cut squash in 1/2 or 1/4’s. place on cookie sheet or baking dish. Brush melted butter over squash.</description></item><item><title>Turkey Salad With Michigan Apples</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/turkey-salad-with-michigan-apples/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:37:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/turkey-salad-with-michigan-apples/</guid><description>Quick Easy Turkey Salad Made with Michigan Apples and Lightly Blanched Almonds and Raisins. Dried Michigan cherries are nice too. Use as Side Dish Salad or a Sandwich. You can Stuff a Garden Ripe Tomato for a Great Lotus.
Turkey salad, with apples, raisins, and almonds Ingredients serves 8
1 lb cooked, diced, turkey breast 1 c mayonaise( more or less to taste) 1 rib celery, diced 1/4 onion, sweet, diced 2 tart apples, thin sliced (peeled or not is fine) 1/2 c raisins(dried cherries are good too) 1/4 tsp paprika 1/4 c.</description></item><item><title>Red Potato Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/red-potato-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/red-potato-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Red Potato Salad Recipe with Fresh Boiled Eggs, Red Potatoes, Celery, Onion, and a Mustard Mayo Sauce with Spices. Red Potato Salad makes a Great
Picnic Better.
Potato Salad Ingredients 5 lbs red potatoes, cooked 15-20 min., chunked (do not peel) 5 eggs, boiled 7 minutes, peeled, sliced 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1/2 cucumber diced (optional) 1 c salad dressing 2 tbsp mustard 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 1/2 tsp paprika Directions In large mixing bowl put all ingredients except potatoes.</description></item><item><title>Easy Macaroni Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/easy-macaroni-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:32:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/easy-macaroni-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Macaroni Salad Recipe is nice for Picnics and Summer Outings. Macaroni Salad is made with Mayo, Fresh Garden Vegetables and Elbow Macaroni.
Macaroni Salad Ingredients 1 lb macaroni, boiled, drained, cooled 1 rib celery, diced 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 c mayo 1/2 tsp season salt 1/4 tsp garlic powder dash white pepper 1 tsp vineager 2 boiled eggs, chopped Directions Mix all ingredients except macaroni.</description></item><item><title>Garden Vegetable Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-side-dishes/garden-vegetable-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-side-dishes/garden-vegetable-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Garden Vegetable Salad Recipe is a fresh salad directly from the garden or fresh vegetable stand. It’s Quick and Easy to prepare and is a nice Side Salad for back yard barbeques or picnics.
Vegetable Salad Ingredients 1 bunch broccoli 1/2 head cauliflower 1/2 vidalia onion 1 cucumber 2 tomatoes 2 ribs celery 1 green pepper 1 c italian dressing Directions Clean and cut vegetables into bite size portions.</description></item><item><title>Tossed Garden Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/tossed-garden-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/tossed-garden-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Fresh Garden Tossed Salad is Friends with your Favorite Soup or Sandwich, and is Healthy and Delicious.
Tossed Salad Ingredients 1 head iceburg or romaine lettuce, rinsed, cored, cut in salad size pieces 1 cucumber, partial peel, slice 1 green pepper, diced, or rings 2 eggs, hard boiled (7min.) peeled, sliced 1 rib celery, small cross cut 1/2 sweet onion, diced, or rings 2-4 radishes, slice thin 2 fresh tomatoes, sliced or wedged 1 c croutons Directions Remember to always rinse your fruits and vegetables under cool running water.</description></item><item><title>Strawberry Spinach Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/strawberry-spinach-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/strawberry-spinach-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Strawberry Spinach Salad Recipe is a Wonderful Summer Salad with Pine Nuts, Blueberries, Strawberries, Fresh Spinach and Strawberry Balsamic Vinaigrette Dressing.
While visiting friends, we were pleasantly surprised when they served this salad, espescially knowing they grow their own fruit.
Strawberry Spinach Ingredients Salad serves 4-6
1 lb fresh baby spinach 1 pint fresh strawberries 1/2 c pine nuts 1/2 c fresh blueberries 1/2 c balsamic vinaigrette 1/2 c cooked chopped bacon(optoinal) 1/2 c crumbled feta eggs, boiled, peeled Directions Rinse spinach, let dry and place in large salad bowl.</description></item><item><title>Pasta Salad Recipe With Fresh Garden Vegetables</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/pasta-salad-recipe-with-fresh-garden-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:22:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/pasta-salad-recipe-with-fresh-garden-vegetables/</guid><description>Quick Easy Pasta Salad Recipe using fresh broccoli, peppers, and other garden fresh vegetables. Pasta Salad is a summer favorite for picnics and luncheons with friends.
Pasta Salad Ingredients serves about 10
1 lb pasta (your choice of styles) cooked, drained, cooled under water 1/2 onion, diced 1 colored pepper, diced 1 c broccoli, chopped bite size 1/2 c cauliflower, chopped bite size 1/4 c black olives 1 tomato, diced 1 cucumber, peeled, 1/4 sliced 1 c cheese chunks 1/2 c ranch dressing 1/2 c Italian dressing 1/4 c grated parmesan cheese Directions Place all vegetables and cooked pasta in large mixing bowl and mix together.</description></item><item><title>Chef Salad Recipe With Vegetables, Eggs, Cheese, Meat</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/chef-salad-recipe-with-vegetables-eggs-cheese-meat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/chef-salad-recipe-with-vegetables-eggs-cheese-meat/</guid><description>Quick Easy Chef Salad Recipe is the perfect summer meal. Fresh vegetables, boiled egg, ham, turkey, chicken or shrimp to top it off. Chef Salad entree is healthy and delicious and great with a hot roll or soup.
Chef Salad Ingredients 1 head iceburg lettuce, rinsed, cored, cut in salad size pieces 1 cucumber, partial peel, slice 1 green pepper, diced, or rings 2 eggs, hard boiled (7min.) peeled, sliced 8 oz.</description></item><item><title>Easy Caesar Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/easy-caesar-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/easy-caesar-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Caesar Salad Recipe is Fresh Romaine Lettuce, Croutons, and Shredded Parmesan Cheese. Caesar Salad is Great Topped with Diced Chicken. Caesar Dressing is the Finale.
Caesar Salad Ingredients serves 2-4
1 head romaine lettuce, cleaned, chopped 1/2 c shredded parmesan cheese 1 cup large croutons 1/2 c ceasar dressing 1 lb Grilled chicken breast diced (optional) Directions In large salad bowl place romaine lettuce.
Top off with shredded Parmesan, croutons, and chicken.</description></item><item><title>Grilled Sirloin Steak Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/grilled-sirloin-steak-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/grilled-sirloin-steak-recipe/</guid><description>Sirloin Steak Recipe Quick and Easy for the Barbecue Grill, top with Maitre d’ butterwhile grilling. Serve with any side dish. Great for back yard Barbecues.
Sirloin Steak Ingredients 2 -3 lbs sirloin steak 1 med. onion, thick sliced 1 lb. fresh sliced mushrooms 1/2 cup beer or wine 2 tbs Maitre d’ butter Directions Place steak in a hot frying pan and seer for about 30 seconds on each side to seal in the juices.</description></item><item><title>London Broil Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/london-broil-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/london-broil-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy London Broil Recipe, Marinate Brisket in Garlic and Italian Dressing Overnight. London Broil is Excellent on the Grill or under the Broiler.
London Broil Ingredients serves 10-12
3-4 lb flank steak 1 c Italian dressing 2 tbsp garlic (fresh chopped) 1 can beer or 1 cup wine Directions Lay flank steak in pan for marinating. Sprinkle on garlic then pour over dressing and beer or wine (or both).</description></item><item><title>Beef Brochettes Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/beef-brochettes-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:02:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/beef-brochettes-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Brochettes Recipe is great in the summer for a barbecue on the patio, or inside under the broiler. Fresh Beef and Vegetables Brochettes, Marinated and Skewered.
Here’s a great recipe for your summer cookout!
Beef Brochettes Ingredients serves 4-6
2 lb sirloin steak ( cut in 1″ cubes) 1 green pepper 2 tomatoes 1 large onion 1 lb whole fresh mushrooms 1 can whole peeled potatoes 1 c italian dressing 1 tbsp oregano salt and pepper to taste 1Tsp granulated or fresh garlic Directions Note: You will need steel skewers for this recipe.</description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Chicken Brochettes Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/hawaiian-chicken-brochettes-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/hawaiian-chicken-brochettes-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Hawaiian Chicken Brochettes, a Festive Recipe with Fresh Pineapple, Vegetables and Chicken Breast, Great Brochettes for the Barbecue Grill or in the oven. It’s a Hawaiian Luau.
Hawaiian Chicken Brochettes Ingredients 1 lb chicken breast, boneless, skinless, partially cooked 1 green or colored pepper, cut in 2″ squares 1 onion, large cut in 2″ pieces 1 lb. whole large mushrooms cut in 1/2 1 pint cherry tomatoes 1 fresh pineapple, cut in 2″ pieces 1 pint sweet and sour sauce 1 can crushed pineapple, or pureed fresh pineapple 2 tbsp olive oil 10 skewers, metal or bamboo Directions Combine crushed pineapple and sweet and sour sauce together, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Teriyaki Chicken</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/honey-barbecue-teriyaki-chicken/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/honey-barbecue-teriyaki-chicken/</guid><description>Honey Barbecue Teriyaki Chicken, Quick and Easy Recipe for Summer Barbecues or Fall Meals From The Oven. Finish Under the Broiler, Serve with You Favorite Side Dishes.
Chicken Ingredients 2 whole chickens cut in 1/8’s, fresh seasoned salt to taste Honey Teriyaki Chicken Directions Method #1 In large roasting pan, place chicken, seasoning, and honey barbecue teriyaki sauce. Roast uncovered 375* for 40-60 minutes. Baste often. May be finished under the broiler.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Chicken Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/honey-barbecue-chicken-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:42:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/honey-barbecue-chicken-recipe/</guid><description>Pure Honey, Herbs, Spices, Wine, and Ketchup base combined to make Quick Honey Barbeque Sauce Recipes for Chicken on the Barbecue Grill, or it’s Easy inside in the oven. Moist and Tender. Let’s Barbecue!
Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Honey Barbecue Sauce Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Brochettes Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/chicken-brochettes-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/chicken-brochettes-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Chicken Brochettes Recipe is great in the summer on the barbeque grill, or inside under the broiler. Fresh Chicken and Vegetables Brochettes, Marinated and Skewered.
Here’s a great recipe for your summer cookout!
Chicken Brochettes Ingredients serves 4-6
2 lb boneless chicken breasts, ( cut in 1″ cubes) 1 green pepper 2 tomatoes 1 large onion 1 lb whole fresh mushrooms 1 can whole peeled potatoes 1 c Italian dressing 1 tbsp oregano salt and pepper to taste 1 tsp granulated or fresh garlic Directions Note: You will need steel skewers for this recipe.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>Try Chef Frank’s Homemade Honey Barbecue Sauce when you’re grilling outside in the summer or cooking inside when it’s not so warm out. This sauce makes your ribs, chicken, or steak come alive with the sweet taste of local honey.
Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Maitre d’ Butter</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/maitre-d-butter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 04:04:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/maitre-d-butter/</guid><description>Quick Easy Maitre d’ butter Recipe is great for Topping Steaks, Making Chicken Recipes, or for Grilling Buns for Sandwiches. Maitre d’ Butter is a must for Flambe’ Recipes too like Chicken Almondine Flambe’.
This recipe can be used to top off steaks, grill buns for sandwiches,or for use in various recipes on this site.
Maitre d’ Butter Ingredients 1 pound butter 1 bunch parsley 1 small onion 1 clove garlic Directions Have butter at room temperature.</description></item><item><title>Easy Teriyaki Sauce Recipe</title><link>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/easy-teriyaki-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 03:57:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/grilling-cookouts-and-barbecues/easy-teriyaki-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>Teriyaki sauce made with soy sauce, pineapple juice, brown sugar, and spices. Teriyaki sauce can be used with chicken, steak, and stir fry. Teriyaki sauce is great for the back yard barbecue or under the broiler of your stove.
Teriyaki Sauce Ingredients 1/2 c brown sugar 2 c pineapple juice 1/4 c soy sauce 1 tbsp veg. oil 1/4 tsp salt 1 clove minced garlic 1/4 tsp white pepper 2 tbs corn starch Directions Place ingredients (except corn starch) in sauce pan and simmer on low heat for about 20 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Fruit Tray For Special Occasions</title><link>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/fresh-fruit-tray-for-special-occasions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/fresh-fruit-tray-for-special-occasions/</guid><description>A fresh fruit tray is guaranteed to sparkle as the centerpiece of any gathering. Follow our instructions to really dress it up for a special occasion.
Ingredients Prep time: 1 hr.
Fruit used for this:
2 large watermelon 6 pineapples 3 large muskmelon 3 large cantelope 5 large oranges 3# red grapes 3# green grapes 10 kiwi 3 large pink grapefruit 10 lbs. fresh strawberries 2 pt. blackberries 2 pt.</description></item><item><title>Quick and Easy Chili Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/quick-and-easy-chili-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/quick-and-easy-chili-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Try this quick easy chili recipe for school kid’s lunch or a church function. Corn bread and shredded cheddar cheese along with a saladmake this a great meal and is very affordable as well.
Here’s the chili recipe for those of you cooking for a crowd:
Ingredients 56# chili beans(red) ( 7 no. 10 cans) 11 qts tomato juice 30# ground beef 6 large green peppers diced 4 large spanish onions diced 2 large stalks celery diced 1 c.</description></item><item><title>Spaghetti Sauce Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/spaghetti-sauce-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/spaghetti-sauce-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Our Spaghetti Sauce Recipe for 200 People will guarantee success for your large group meal. Fresh ground beef, herbs and spicesand tomato sauce make our spaghetti sauce for 200 a hit! A quick easy recipe. Simply omit the ground beef for a fantastic vegetarian recipe!
Spaghetti Sauce for 200 Ingredients 40# ground beef, cooked, drained (optional) 8- #10 cans tomato sauce 1- #10 can tomato paste 4 onions, diced 1/2 c chopped garlic,fresh or dehydrated 2 green peppers, diced 2# fresh sliced mushrooms 1 c brown sugar 1/2 c soy sauce 1 c leaf oregano 1/2 c basil, (1 cup if fresh) 2 tbsp ground rosemary 1 tbsp white pepper 20 bay leaves, whole (to be removed before serving) Directions Prepare ground beef and sauce in intervals together.</description></item><item><title>Scalloped Corn Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/scalloped-corn-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/scalloped-corn-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Scalloped Corn is quite an easy institutional recipe to prepare for large groups and accompanies many entrees. Scalloped Corn for 200 will hold for several hours in a warmer at 140℉ – 165℉.
Scalloped Corn for 200 Ingredients 8 #10 cans cans creamed corn 30 eggs 2 lbs saltines (crushed) 2 lbs butter (melted) 2 c. milk 2 tbs pepper (avoid salt as saltines contain enough) Directions In large mixing bowl add corn, 1 1/2 lbs crackers (crushed), eggs, butter, and milk.</description></item><item><title>Poppy Seed Bread Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/poppy-seed-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/poppy-seed-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Easy quick poppy seed bread recipe for dessertor as a breakfast bread. makes great muffinstoo. poppy seed bread for 200 will keep your clients tummies happy and is easy to prepare and serve.
Poppy Seed Bread for 200 Ingredients 20# yellow cake mix 8# toasted coconut instant pudding mix (vanilla pudding and add toasted coconut works too.) 20 large eggs 4 c vegetable oil 3 c soaked and drained poppy seeds 6 c hot water Directions Mix all ingredients in large mixer bowl, beat as for cake on medium speed for two minutes.</description></item><item><title>Meatloaf Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/meatloaf-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/meatloaf-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Meatloaf for 200 people is a quick easy recipe when feeding a crowd. Mashed potatoesand green beansis standard with this meatloaf recipe. Use leftovers for sandwichesor put in spaghetti sauce.
Ingredients 50# ground beef (19/79) 5# diced onions 3# diced celery 50 eggs 3 loaves bread or 3#( or any buns or leftover breads) 3 tbsp beef base 4 c ketchup 1/4 c granulated or chopped garlic 1 tbsp white pepper 2 qts water Directions In 60 qt mixer place all ingredients (except ground beef), mix well on speed #1 (low) until ingredients are blended together, then add ground beef and mix until incorporated.</description></item><item><title>Mango Sweet and Sour Chicken Arbutus</title><link>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/mango-sweet-and-sour-chicken-arbutus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/quick-and-easy-chicken-recipes/mango-sweet-and-sour-chicken-arbutus/</guid><description>Quick and Easy Institutional Recipes to Prepare for 200 People with Fresh Mangoes, and any Red Sweet and Sour Sauce. Fresh Chicken Breasts are baked with our Mango Sweet and Sour Sauce for Chicken Arbutus. This is Named after one of our Best Places in Michigan to be, and for the Special People that Reside There.
Ingredients Serves: 5
225 boneless skinless chicken breasts 20 mangoes, peeled, chopped fine chunks in processor 1 gallon oriental sweet and sour sauce (Duck Sauce can be used too) 2 oz.</description></item><item><title>Macaroni and Cheese Recipe For 200</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/macaroni-and-cheese-recipe-for-200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/macaroni-and-cheese-recipe-for-200/</guid><description>Quick Easy Institutional Macaroni and Cheddar Cheese Recipe is the Favorite of most Kids. Macaroni and Cheddar Cheese from Scratch is great with Fresh Watermelon and Salads. A Warm Roll is Nice too!
Macaroni and Cheese with Cheddar for 240 people Prep time: 30 minutes
Cook time: 30 minutes
Serves: 240
Ingredients 30# elbo macaroni 25# shredded cheddar cheese (medium or sharp) 2 lbs melted butter 1 1/2 gallons milk 2 tbsp salt 2 tbsp pepper Directions In large kettle or two kettles, place macaroni in boiling water, stir frequently to keep from sticking.</description></item><item><title>Honey Baked Ham Recipe For 200</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/honey-baked-ham-recipe-for-200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 15:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/honey-baked-ham-recipe-for-200/</guid><description>Delicious honey baked ham for 200 with a quick 15 minute prep time and 1 hour cook time is easy for large group meals. Honey baked ham recipe has honey, clove, brown sugar, and applesauce, very delicious!
Honey Baked Ham for 200 Recipe Ingredients 45# whole ham (flat buffet)sliced 1/4 inch thick 5 tsp ground clove 4 c honey 10 c applesauce 8 c brown sugar Directions In shallow hotel pans, shingle ham.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate Chip Cookies Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Real Chocolate Chip Cookies are Quick and Easy Scratch Cookies to make for Gatherings, Large Groups, Camps, or Schools. Kids love them and will want them again! Quick Easy Institutional Recipe.
Real Chocolate Chip Cookies Recipe for 200 People Ingredients 4 lbs. butter softened 16 eggs 6 c. brown sugar 6 c. sugar 20 c. flour 2 tbs vanilla 2 tbs baking powder 2 tbs baking soda 2 tsp salt 24 c.</description></item><item><title>Banana Bread And Muffins Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Banana Bread Recipe For 200 Quick Easy Banana Bread or Muffins for 280 People. This Quick Easy Institutional Scratch Recipe will keep your clients happy. Use the same Quick Easy Banana Bread Recipe for Muffins.
Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Banana Bread Ingredients 60 ripe peeled bananas 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda Banana Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description></item><item><title>Easy Apple Pudding Recipe For 200 People</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/easy-apple-pudding-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/easy-apple-pudding-for-200-people/</guid><description>Delicious apple pudding for 200 people is a very popular dessertin the fall or for any season. Great for schools, churches and special functions.
Apple Pudding for 200 People Ingredients Apple Base Ingredients 8 – #10 cans sliced waterpack apples 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tsp salt 8 tbs cinnamon Topping Ingredients 12 c. flour 5# butter, melted 5 c. brown sugar 2 tbs cinnamon 6 c.</description></item><item><title>Apple Crisp For 200</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</guid><description>Kids and adults love apple crisp for dessert. So easy to make and goes with any meal. Schools, camps, and churches love this recipe.
Apple Crisp for 200 People Apple Ingredients 8 #10 cans sliced apples (water pack) 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tbs cinnamon 8- 2″ full size hotel pans Apple Directions place 1 can apples, (do not drain) in each pan and even out.</description></item><item><title>Apple Bread For 200 Recipe</title><link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</guid><description>Our apple bread recipe is easy to make about a 15 minute prep time. This recipe from scratch will keep your clients happy. Apple quick bread for 200 will enhance any breakfast and makes great muffins too.
Apple Bread Or Muffins For 200 Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Apple Bread Ingredients 2 #10 cans sliced apples (chop up to marble size pieces) 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 2 tbsp cinnamon 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda Apple Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description></item><item><title>Puff Pastry Wrap Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/puff-pastry-wrap-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:32:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/puff-pastry-wrap-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Puff Pastry Wraps Recipes are great for Appetizers or Desserts. Simple instructions on how to make Puff Pastry Wraps for any Holiday or Party. Happy New Year Appetizers.
Puff Pastry Wrap Ingredients Puff pastry sheets can be purchased at any commercial food store.
1 sheet puff pastry dough(makes about 12 servings or so) 12 mini smoked sausages leftover mashed potatoes 1 c shredded cheese 1/2 c fresh chopped chives bowl water and pastry brush( this acts as the glue to make pastry stick together).</description></item><item><title>Kids’ Pita Pizza Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/kids-pita-pizza-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/kids-pita-pizza-recipe/</guid><description>Kids Pita Pizza Recipe is Perfect for Birthday Parties, Pic-nics and Special Events. Kids can help make Pita Pizza, it’s fun!
Pita Pizza Ingredients (for individual pizzas) serves 10 10 pita breads (flat breads) 2 c pizza sauce 1 1/2 lb mozzerella cheese( shredded) 1/2 onion, diced 1 green pepper, diced 2 c mushrooms, sliced 1/2 c black olives, sliced 8 oz. sliced pepperoni 8 oz. ham, diced 8 oz.</description></item><item><title>Seafood Sauce Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/seafood-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/seafood-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>Festive Holiday Seafood Sauce Recipe is made from ketchup, lemon, and horse radish. Easy to prepare and is best with Shrimp Cocktail or Fried Shrimp, Clams or Fish. Seafood Sauce is a must.
Seafood Sauce Ingredients 2 c ketchup 1-2 tbsp horseradish 2 tbsp lemon juice Directions In mixing bowl combine ingredients together, cover refrigerate.
Note: This sauce is good with shrimp, scallops, fish , and Bacon Wrapped Steak</description></item><item><title>Hot Mustard Sauce Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/hot-mustard-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/hot-mustard-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>Quick easy Hot Mustard Sauce Recipe is a favorite at parties for dipping egg rolls, wings, or other puff pastry appetizers. Hot mustard on warm pretzels is comforting and satisfying.
Hot Mustard Sauce Recipe 1/2 c dry mustard 1 tsp sugar 1/4 tsp salt 1 tbsp butter, melted 1 tsp vinegar 1/2 c boiling water(only use enough to make thick sauce) Directions Mix ingredients together. Add boiling water to make thick sauce.</description></item><item><title>Easy Drawn Butter – Clarified Butter Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/easy-drawn-butter-clarified-butter-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/easy-drawn-butter-clarified-butter-recipe/</guid><description>Drawn butter, or some call it clarified butter, is used over broiled fish, lobster, and many different seafood entrees whether on the grill or under a broiler.
Drawn Butter 1/2 lb butter Directions Melt butter in small sauce pan very slowly. do not stir or boil. Whan butter has melted, skim away salt layer on top. Than ladle the clear hot butter into a small “drawn butter cup”, or a small custard dish does well.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Barbecue Sauce Recipe With Red Wine</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/homemade-barbecue-sauce-recipe-with-red-wine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/homemade-barbecue-sauce-recipe-with-red-wine/</guid><description>Prepare this wonderful barbecue sauce on the stove. Great for grilling outside or in. Use our sauce for chicken, ribs, pork, or barbecue sandwiches. Chef Frank finishes this recipe off with red wine for an added kick!
Barbecue Sauce Recipe 2 c ketchup 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Orange Gelatin Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/orange-gelatin-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/orange-gelatin-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Orange Gelatin Salad is a special Holiday Treat at the end of a great meal. Orange Gelatin Salad has pineapple, manderin oranges and whipped cream. A wonderful dessert.
Holiday Orange Gelatin 1 small pkg orange gelatin 1 c orange pop 1 c hot water 120*(to dissolve gelatin) 1 pkg dry whip cream mix 1 can drained pineapple 1 can drained mandarin oranges Directions Mix gelatin and hot water, then add pop.</description></item><item><title>Festive Holiday Cheese Balls</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/festive-holiday-cheese-balls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/festive-holiday-cheese-balls/</guid><description>Quick Easy Cheese Balls Recipe is for the Holidays with crackers and other Appetizers. Cheese Balls take 15 minutes to prepare, and are eye appealing too!
Cheese Ball Recipe 2 8oz. cream cheese 1lb brick cheddar cheese (shredded) 1 med onion finely chopped 3 tsp worcestershire sauce 1-2 tsp milk 1 tsp garlic (fresh or granulated) 1/2 c chopped nuts (pecans) Cheese Ball Directions Mix all ingredients together. Form two balls evenly then roll in nuts.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo Style Hot Wings Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/buffalo-style-hot-wings-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/buffalo-style-hot-wings-recipe/</guid><description>Buffalo Style Hot Wings Make a Great Appetizer. Serve at birthday parties, Holiday gatherings or any social event.
Hot Wings Recipe   5# wings 4 oz butter 1 1/2 c hot sauce Buffalo Style Hot Wings Directions Cut wings at joint, throw end tip away. Deep fry in 2 qt oil at 350* for ten minutes. You may have to fry 4 batches.
Melt butter in sauce pan, add hot sauce and whisk together.</description></item><item><title>Black Bean Wrap Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/black-bean-wrap-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/black-bean-wrap-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Black Bean Wraps Recipe is an Easy Mexican Recipe and is great for lunch or dinner. Black bean wraps are filled with black beans, vegetables, cheese and all the fixings.
Black Bean Wrap Recipe serves 10 10 12″ flour tortillas 2 cans black beans 1 can refried beans 2 cups rice (converted) boil with 4 c water salsa 1 diced onion 1 diced green pepper 4 diced tomatoes ( fresh) 1 lb shredded cheddar 1 tub sour cream 1 head shredded lettuce Directions Open tortillas.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Mexican Salsa Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/fresh-mexican-salsa-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:53:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/fresh-mexican-salsa-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Mexican Salsa Recipe is made from Fresh Peppers, Tomatoes, Onions, and Spices. Use Mexican Salsa for any Mexican Recipe as a Topper or Dip.
Salsa Ingedients 1 diced onion 2 diced green pepper 6 diced tomatoes (fresh) 2 rib celery small diced 3 cups tomato juice hot sauce to taste 1 tbsp chili powder 1/2 c sliced jalapeno (optional) Salsa Direction In small sauce pan, bring tomato juice to boil.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Seven Layer Dip Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/mexican-seven-layer-dip-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/mexican-seven-layer-dip-recipe/</guid><description>Great Filling Snack for Parties. Mexican Seven (7) Layer Dip with Refried Beans, Cream Cheese, Fresh Vegetables Cheese, and Salsa. Quick and Easy to make in about 10 minutes. Tortilla Chips Love Taking a Dip!
Mexican Seven Layer Dip Recipe 2 cans refried beans 1 pkg taco or burrito seasoning 8-12 oz. salsa 1 lb sour cream 8 oz. cream cheese 1 small can black olives, sliced, drained 1 fresh freen papper, diced 1 small sweet or red onion, diced 3 medium tomatoes, diced 1/2 c.</description></item><item><title>Scratch Guacamole Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/scratch-guacamole-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/scratch-guacamole-recipe/</guid><description>Scratch Mexican Guacamole is a favorite with Nachos, burritos, tacosand quesadillas. Oh, and fajitastoo. It’s simple to prepare with fresh avocados, real lemon juice, garlic and spices. If you make too much, it’s easy to freeze until your next Mexican meal.
Mexican Guacamole Recipe serves 6-10 2 avocados, peeled, mashed 2 tsp lemon juice 1/2 tsp salt 3 tbsp minced onion 1 tsp chopped garlic 1/3 c tomato , finely chopped Directions Mix all ingredients together, chill.</description></item><item><title>Authentic Steak Quesadilla Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/authentic-steak-quesadilla-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/authentic-steak-quesadilla-recipe/</guid><description>Steak Quesadillas a Great Quick Easy Mexican Quesadilla Recipe using Fresh Sirloin Steak and Soft Tortillas. Make Fresh Salsa and Guacamole if you Desire from our Quick Easy Mexican Recipes. Quesadillas are Served for Lunch or Supper.
Steak Quesadillas Recipe 2-3 lbs Sirloin Steak cut in strips 1 c salsa 1 pkg fajita seasoning 2 c shredded cheddar 8 12″ flour tortillas Steak Quesadilla Toppings sliced onions and peppers (optional) sliced black olives 1 c sour cream 1/2 c jalapeno peppers 2 c shredded lettuce 2 c diced tomatoes 2 c refried beans 1 c guacamole Directions In large frying pan, brown steak until cooked then add 2 tbsp salsa and fajita seasoning to taste.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Quesadilla Recipe</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/mexican-quesadilla-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/mexican-quesadilla-recipe/</guid><description>Chicken Quesadillas – a Great Quick Easy Mexican Quesadilla Recipe using Fresh Chicken Breasts and Soft Tortillas. Make Fresh Salsa and Guacamole if you Desire from our Quick Easy Mexican Recipes. Quesadillas are Served for Lunch or Supper.
Chicken Quesadillas Recipe 4 boneless skinless chicken breasts cut in strips 1 c salsa 1 pkg fajita seasoning 2 c shredded cheddar 8 12″ flour tortillas Toppings sliced onions and peppers (optional) sliced black olives 1 c sour cream 1/2 c jalapeno peppers 2 c shreeded lettuce 2 c diced tomatoes 2 c refried beans 1 c guacamole Directions In large frying pan, brown chicken until cooked then add 2 tbsp salsa and fajita seasoning to taste.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Cheese Dip</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/mexican-cheese-dip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/mexican-cheese-dip/</guid><description>Mexican Cheese Dip with ground beef, is an easy appetizerfor dipping crackers, nacho chips, and tortilla chips. This Dip is a great party staple to go with your other appetizers or for an after school snack for the kids.
Mexican Cheese Dip Recipe 1 lb soft pasteurized American cheese 1/2 c milk 1 lb ground beef, browned, drained (optional) 1/2 onion diced, sauteed 1 tbsp taco seasoning 1/2 tbsp ground cumin pepper to taste Directions In large microwaveable bowl, place cheese and milk, heat for 1 minute then stir, heat again and stir add onions and seasonings and ground beef if desired.</description></item><item><title>People Chow – Kids and Adults Snack</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/people-chow-kids-and-adults-snack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/people-chow-kids-and-adults-snack/</guid><description>Quick Easy People Chow Recipe is a favorite among kids and adults alike. People Chow has chocolate and peanut butter goodness. A great Birthday treat!
People Chow Recipe 1 c margerine or butter 1 c peanut butter 1 bag chocolate chips 1 box rice chex cereal 1 c powdered sugar Directions Mix all ingredients except powdered sugar in a large bowl. Once all is mixed, place in large paper bag with powdered sugar, fold closed and shake vigorously.</description></item><item><title>Microwave Caramel Corn</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/microwave-caramel-corn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/microwave-caramel-corn/</guid><description>This quick and easy microwave caramel corn recipe is a hit with kids and adults alike. Microwave caramel corn is a fun project to do with kids on those cold winter days.
Microwave Caramel Corn Recipe 3-5 qts. popped corn. Place in non-stick sprayed paper grocery bag. Caramel Recipe 1/4 c corn syrup 1 c brown sugar 1 stick butter 1 tsp vanilla 1/2 tsp baking soda Direction Melt and cook in microwave for 4 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Easy Cinnamon Crunchies</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/easy-cinnamon-crunchies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/easy-cinnamon-crunchies/</guid><description>Quick Easy Cinnamon Crunchies are an Easy Recipe for after school snacks or a kids party. Easy Cinnamon Crunchies from pie crust, butter, cinnamon, and sugar. Eat them warm.
Skippy loves kids and wants you to learn to cook these great foods! There’s more recipes to come!
Cinnamon Crunchies Ingredients 1 pkg pie crust 1/4 c butter, melted 1 tbsp cinnamon 1/2 c sugar Cinnamon Crunchies Directions Open pie crust and lay out on cookie sheet.</description></item><item><title>Focaccia Pizza, Vegetarian Pita Bread and Fresh Mozzarella</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/focaccia-pizza-vegetarian-pita-bread-and-fresh-mozzarella/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/focaccia-pizza-vegetarian-pita-bread-and-fresh-mozzarella/</guid><description>Vegetarians will be Excited with this Pita Facaccia Pizza. Fresh Mozzarella, Basil, Vegetables, and Homemade Pesto is a Quick Easy Lunch or Dinner. Top off with any salad or fruit.
Focaccia Pizza on Pita with Fresh Mozzarella and Pesto one pita per serving pita bread sliced 1/2″ fresh mozzarella 3 roasted garlic cloves 2 oz. fresh basil 1/2 c olive oil 4 oz. tomato sauce thin sliced fresh tomatoes thin sliced green or colored peppers thin sliced sweet onion Pesto Directions To make pesto: Combine olive oil, garlic and basil in food prossesor and chop until incorporated together.</description></item><item><title>Bacon Wrapped Steak</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/bacon-wrapped-steak/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/bacon-wrapped-steak/</guid><description>Quick Easy Bacon Wrapped Steak Recipe is a great Appetizer for parties. Bacon Wrapped Steak dipped in Seafood Sauce is nice on your New Year’s Eve Party.
Bacon Wrapped Steak serves 15 2 lb steak, cut in 1″ squares 1 lb bacon, cut strips in 1/2 toothpicks deep frying kettle with oil Bacon Wrapped Steak Directions Wrap bacon around steak and secure with a toothpick. Deep fry at 350* for 3-5 minutes or until desired doneness is achieved.</description></item><item><title>Bacon Wrapped Pineapple</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/bacon-wrapped-pineapple/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/bacon-wrapped-pineapple/</guid><description>Quick and Easy Bacon Wrapped Pineapple make an Excellent Appetizer for Parties and Get Togethers. Serve for Holidays and Special events.
Bacon Wrapped Pineapple 1 fresh pineapple Cut into wedges 1 lb thick cut bacon, cut in half round toothpicks Bacon Wrapped Pineapple Directions Wrap bacon around Pineapple. Skewer with toothpick. Place on cookie sheet. bake 375* 12-15 minutes or until desired doneness. Serve.</description></item><item><title>Bacon Wrapped Olives Appetizer</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/bacon-wrapped-olives-appetizer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/bacon-wrapped-olives-appetizer/</guid><description>Quick easy Bacon Wrapped Olives Make a great Appetizer for parties and get togethers. Bacon Wrapped Olives are festive too, and make a great Christmas or New Years Eve Snack.
Bacon Wrapped Olives Ingredients 1 jar olives (stuffed with pimento) regular size 1 lb bacon cut in 1/2 (thick bacon works best) round toothpicks Bacon Wrapped Olives Directions Wrap bacon around olives. skewer with toothpick. Place on cookie sheet.</description></item><item><title>Appetizers</title><link>/recipes/appetizers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 23:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/appetizers/</guid><description>Celebrate Holidays and special events with these quick, wonderful and eye appealing appetizers. Chef Frank’s appetizers are fun to prepare and bring a festive flair to your event without keeping you cooped up in the kitchen.
Festive Holiday Appetizers
Easy Bacon Wrapped Olives
Bacon Wrapped Pineapple
Bacon Wrapped Steak
Focaccia Pita with Fresh Mozzarella and Basil
Cinnamon Crunchies
Microwave Caramel Corn
People Chow
Quick Easy Mexican Cheese Dip
Chicken Quesadillas</description></item><item><title>Fresh Summer Cucumber Salad</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/fresh-summer-cucumber-salad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:43:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/fresh-summer-cucumber-salad/</guid><description>Fresh from the garden comes this wonderful cucumber salad with fresh summer garden tomato, and onion. Simple and delicious for steak or rib cookouts and family meals.
Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad Ingredients 1 large seedless cucumber 1/2 large sweet onion 1 fresh tomato 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 c. apple cider vineager 1 tbsp sugar 1/2 c. water Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad Directions Cut vegetables into large chunks (bite size) and place into right sized bowl.</description></item><item><title>Tartar Sauce For Fish</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tartar-sauce-for-fish/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tartar-sauce-for-fish/</guid><description>Quick Easy Tartar Sauce Recipe makes fish meals complete. With a touch of lemon, Tartar Sauce is great with Fried Clams or Walleye, and Fish and Chips.
Tartar Sauce Ingredients 1 c mayonaise or salad dressing 1/2 c sweet pickle relish 1 -2 tbsp lemon juice 1/2 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning Tartar Sauce Directions Mix ingredients together well, serve with fish and other seafoods. Refrigerate, covered.
Note: Did you know that by adding1/4 c ketchup to this recipe you have a great Thousand Island sauce.</description></item><item><title>Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Our honey teriyaki barbecue sauce will become a staple in your recipe file. It’s easy to prepare on the stove and great for the barbecue grillfor ribs, chicken, chops and steaks.
Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 2 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 c pineapple juice ( or 1 c, pureed fresh pineapple) 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses 2 tbsp grape jelly Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour or until reduced, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Goulash With Ground Beef</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:35:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</guid><description>Quick Easy Goulash Recipe with Fresh Ground Beef and Elbow Macaroni, Tomato Sauce and Fresh Cut Vegetables with Cheese. Goulash is a Great Casserole for Lunch or Supper.
Goulash serves 8
1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 lb ground beef, cooked, drained 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 can tomato sauce 1 can diced tomatoes 2 oz. melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp chili powder 1 c shredded cheddar cheese(optional) Combine all ingredients in large mixing bowl.</description></item><item><title>Scalloped Potatoes – Grandma’s Comfort Food</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:32:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</guid><description>Quick Easy Scalloped Potatoes is Grandma’s recipe and will satisfy any appetite. Add ham to this Scalloped Potato recipe for a wonderful comfort food a cold winter day.
Scalloped Potatoes Ingredients Scalloped Potatoes 6 potatoes, peeled, thin sliced 1/2 onion, diced 2 rib celery, diced 4 oz. butter, melted 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 cups flour 3 cups milk Scalloped Potatoes Directions In large casserole dish, place a layer of potatoes in bottom.</description></item><item><title>Tuna Noodle Casserole</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:25:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Tuna Noodle Casserole is a Family Favorite and is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Our Creamy Tuna Noodle Casserole is Comfort Food for those Cold Winter Days.
Tuna Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
8 oz, tuna, drained 1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Tuna Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Noodle Casserole</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Chicken Noodle Casserole, Quick Easy Recipe for Lunch or Dinner Entree. Chicken Noodle Casserole is True Comfort Food and goes with any Salad, Fruit, and Warm Bread.
Chicken Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
1 lb cooked chicken meat cut up1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Chicken Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Creamy Scalloped Potatoes</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</guid><description>Quick Easy Creamy Scalloped Potatoes, Great Comfort Food Entree on those Cold Winter Days. Warm up the House with a Creamy Scalloped Potato Aroma.
Creamy Scalloped Potatoes serves 8
3# red potatoes, sliced 1/4″ 1/2 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced small 3 c milk 1 c roux 1 tsp chicken base 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. butter Creamy Scalloped Potatoes Directions Boil potatoes in medium size pot for about 20 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Pork Loin Recipe</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</guid><description>Stuffed pork loin with fresh raspberry sauce is a wonderful Holiday or Fall entree. The stuffing can be made with either walnuts or pecans. for presentation, slice and shingle onto a platter or tray.
Stuffed Pork Loin With Raspberry Sauce Stuffing: 4 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 ribs celery diced 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tbsp sage 2 apples, peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1 c chopped pecans Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Pork Roast with Michigan Apples</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</guid><description>Slow cooked pork roast with fresh Michigan apples and spices. Tender and juicy and served with stuffing or potatoes, salad and of course, our satisfying desserts.
Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Ingredients Serves 5 – 8
3 lb pork shoulder roast or fresh ham 1 medium onion 2 Michigan apples, peeled cut in chunks 1/2 c applesauce 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage 1/2 tsp black pepper 1 c water Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Directions Place roast in roasting pan, place all ingredients on top of roast.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Country Ribs</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</guid><description>Chef Frank’s honey barbecue country ribs are slow cooked until tender and will wow your family and friends at your back yard Barbecue.
Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Ingredients 3 lb country pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 to 2 c honey barbecue sauce 1/2 c water Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</guid><description>Chef Frank’s Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs are so delicious and easy to prepare in the oven or on the barbecue grill. Great with roasted red potatoesand salador fruit.
Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Ingredients 3 lb or more baby back pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 c honey barbecue sauce 1 c barbecue sauce (if you prefer regular barbecue sauce without honey) 1/2 c water Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description></item><item><title>Thyme Chicken Breast Entree</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</guid><description>Thyme chicken breast is prepared with fresh thyme, herbs and spices, then baked in the oven. It makes a good partner to wild rice, or roasted red potatoes, corn bread, salad or fruit.
Thyme Chicken Breast Ingredients serves 4
4 Chicken breasts, boneless 1 tbsp crushed thyme 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. Maitre d’ butter
(Click link or see recipe below) Thyme Chicken Breast Directions ### Oven Method: Place chicken breasts on greased sheet pan.</description></item><item><title>Delicious Homemade Teriyaki Chicken</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</guid><description>Teriyaki chicken with homemade sauce contains pineapple, garlic, brown sugar and soy sauce. It’s great for the barbecue grill outside, or inside under your broiler. Teriyaki chicken can be served with wild rice, salads or fruits or all the above.
Great on the barbecue grill!
Teriyaki Chicken Ingredients serves 4-6
2 whole chickens cut in 1/8’s, fresh 2 c Teriyaki sauce (see recipe below) 1 tbs. Chef Frank’s Seasoning Method #1 In large roasting pan, place chicken, seasoning, and teriyaki sauce.</description></item><item><title>Simple Lime Chicken Entree</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-lime-chicken-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-lime-chicken-entree/</guid><description>Delicious lime chicken, southwest style, made from cut up chicken or boneless breasts. Fresh lime and zest with Chef Frank’s Seasoning, puts it over the top!
Lime Chicken Ingredients 1 chicken cut in 1/8’s or ( 8 chicken breasts) boneless skinless 4 limes or 4 tbsp lime juice 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp southwest or tex mex seasoning 1 tsp paprika 2 tbsp melted butter 1 lime for lime zest (peel skin and slice very thin, place over chicken before cooking) Lime Chicken Directions Baking Method Place chicken in baking dish.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</guid><description>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Ingredients Serves 4
1 lb shrimp, raw, peeled, deveined, (size of your choice) 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 lb fresh sliced mushrooms 1 tsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 onion, diced 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tsp olive oil 2 lbs. angel hair pasta Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Directions Place pan of water on stove med. high heat to boil water, add a small amount of salt.</description></item><item><title>Scallops Newburg With Buttery Cream Sauce</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scallops-newburg-with-buttery-cream-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scallops-newburg-with-buttery-cream-sauce/</guid><description>Make scallops newburg with large Sea Scallops and a buttery cream sauce. Then place over rice and serve with Broccoli and cheese and a Salad. A nice mellow white wine compliments this meal.
Scallops Newburg Ingredients 2 lbs scallops (large size is better) 1/4 c small diced onion 1/4 c small diced celery 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 c roux 3 c milk 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning Scallops Newburg Directions Prepare cream sauce by heating milk and paprika over medium heat in double boiler, or carefully in sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Lake Michigan Broiled Whitefish</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/lake-michigan-broiled-whitefish/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/lake-michigan-broiled-whitefish/</guid><description>Let’s have broiled whitefish from Lake Michigan. Simply place on foil pie pan, butter, season, and broil. Serve with drawn butter or tartar sauce. Serve with any side dish, salad, rice, or potato.
Broiled Whitefish Ingredients 1 disposable. pie tin 9″-10″ 2 fresh whitefish (preferred from Lake Michigan) 2oz. butter melted couple shakes of Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 lemon 2 oz. water Broiled Whitefish Directions Place whitefish in pan, then add water (do not spray pan as skin will come off when cooked).</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Prepare this vegetarian honey barbecue sauce recipe when you’re grilling outside or cooking inside. It makes your vegetarian burgers, and ribs taste amazing.
Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Simple Vegetarian Goulash</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-vegetarian-goulash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-vegetarian-goulash/</guid><description>&amp;lt;vegetarian goulash is a delicious recipe made with tomato sauce, pasta, fresh cut vegetables and cheese. Great for Lunch or Supper and can be served with salads, vegetables, fruit, and hot rolls with honey butter./p&amp;gt;
Vegetarian Goulash Ingredients Serves 8
1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 tsp. olive oil 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 rib celery, diced small 1 12oz. can tomato sauce 1 12oz.</description></item><item><title>Simple and Tasty Potato Wedges</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-and-tasty-potato-wedges/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-and-tasty-potato-wedges/</guid><description>Try these easy potato wedges made from red, russet, or sweet potatoes. Simply cut wedges, butter, season, and bake. Potato wedges are a great snack or side dish for any main entree.
Potato Wedges Ingredients serves 6-10
4 large potatoes 1/4 c butter, melted 1/4 c grated Parmesan cheese Chef Frank’s Seasoning to taste garlic to taste(granulated or fresh chopped) Potato Wedges Directions Cut potatoes the long way into wedges(about 3-4 per halve).</description></item><item><title>Quick and Easy Egg Noodle Recipe</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/quick-and-easy-egg-noodle-recipe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/quick-and-easy-egg-noodle-recipe/</guid><description>Our quick egg noodle recipe is great for homemade soups or casseroles. Add fresh chopped herbs in the flour for flavored noodles, and use whole wheat flour for better nutrition.
Egg Noodles Ingredients 4 whole eggs pinch salt or Chef Frank’s Seasoning 4 cups flour (whole wheat flour for more nutrition) optional fresh chopped herbs can be mixed with flour like sage, thyme, oregano, marjoram, etc. 2 tsp ice water Egg Noodles Directions combine flour, eggs and salt, in mixer with dough hook.</description></item><item><title>Slow Roasted Cornish Game Hen</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/slow-roasted-cornish-game-hen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/slow-roasted-cornish-game-hen/</guid><description>Wonderful Cornish game hen, slow roasted and stuffed with apple walnut sage stuffing, or plain roasted served with wild rice. This recipe makes Holidays or any day special.
Slow Roasted Cornish Game Hen Ingredients non stuffed method: 1 Cornish game hen per serving as follows: 2 tbs melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp rubbed sage pepper to taste thoroughly rinse with cold water, pat dry, then place game hens in roasting pan back side down.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Turkey Recipes For The Holidays</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>Fill your house with the aroma of our festive oven roasted turkey. Wonderful for family celebrations and Holiday meals.
Oven Roasted Turkey Ingredients 20-25 lb turkey (Thawed if frozen 2-3 days in fridge) rinse under cold water before cooking 3 tbs rubbed sage 3 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 tbsp melted butter 2 c water Roasted Turkey Directions In large roasting pan place turkey, breast side up. Brush with melted butter, then rub with sage.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Chicken Entree</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-chicken-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-chicken-entree/</guid><description>Roast chicken is a quick recipe for a nice supper. All of our side dish recipes are compatible, and hot rolls with butter tops it off.
Roasted Chicken For 4 1 whole chicken (rinsed) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage (rubbed) black pepper to taste 1 tsp garlic (granulated or fresh chopped) 3 tbsp butter (melted) Roasted Chicken Directions Place chicken breast side up in roaster pan.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Prime Rib Roast with Au Jus</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</guid><description>Celebrate the Holidays with our very special Prime Rib Roast recipe. It includes an awesome Au Jus recipe. Follow the links to festive side dishes too.
Prime Rib Roast Ingredients 15-19 lb rib roast 1/4 c garlic, fresh chopped 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 c water Prime Rib Directions Place rib roast in large roasting pan, bone down, add water and seasonings. Cover and place in oven at 275* and roast for 5 hours then check with thermometer.</description></item><item><title>Sausage Gravy For Biscuits</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/sausage-gravy-for-biscuits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/sausage-gravy-for-biscuits/</guid><description>Delicious homemade sausage gravy for biscuits is simple and takes about 15 minutes to prepare. Also click the link to our homemade biscuits.
Sausage Gravy For Biscuits Ingredients 1 lb. ground pork sausage 1 tsp. rubbed sage 1/4 c. diced onions 1/2 tsp. chicken base 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 c. flour 2 c. milk Sausage Gravy For Biscuits Directions Place sausage in large frying with onions and sage.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Homemade Biscuits</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fresh-homemade-biscuits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:26:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fresh-homemade-biscuits/</guid><description>Our homemade biscuits are a light and fluffy quick bread recipe. Less than 10 minutes to prepare, and in the oven for about ten minutes. These biscuits go excellent with strawberry short cake, sausage gravy, stews, and topped with honey butter.
Biscuits Ingredients 2 c flour 2 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 tsp salt 1/3 c veg. shortening 3/4 c milk or buttermilk (if you don’t have buttermilk, just add 1 tsp vineager to milk before mixing).</description></item><item><title>Banana Muffins</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/banana-muffins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:22:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/banana-muffins/</guid><description>Homemade banana muffins, like the bread recipe, is foolproof and only takes 10 (ten) minutes to prepare. Serve while still warm and enjoy with your favorite beverage.
Banana Muffins Ingredients 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/4 tsp salt 1 tsp vanilla 2 eggs 3 bananas 1/4 c butter, melted 1 c sugar 1/2 c milk Directions In mixing bowl combine flour, b. soda, b.</description></item><item><title>Fool Proof Banana Bread</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</guid><description>Homemade banana bread is truly foolproof and will only take a few minutes to prepare. Take advantage of variations to this recipe by adding nuts of your choice. 1 Hour in the oven and everyone is enjoying warm banana bread!
Banana Bread Recipe 3 ripe bananas 2 eggs 1 c sugar 1/2 c oil 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/4 tsp salt dash milk 1 tsp vanills ext.</description></item><item><title>Apple Bread</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/apple-bread/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/apple-bread/</guid><description>Everyone loves apple bread made from Michigan apples for breakfast. Apple muffins too, and company will love it. Add raisins or dried cherries in the mix if you wish.
2 cups flour 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 tsp vanilla ext. 1/2 tsp salt 1/4 c milk 1/2 c sugar 1/2 c brown sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 1/2 c vegetable oil 2 eggs 4 Michigan apples, tart, peeled, diced, (canned can be used, packed in water) about 3 cups (this can also be form Michigan Apples).</description></item><item><title>Delicious French Toast</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/delicious-french-toast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 13:48:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/delicious-french-toast/</guid><description>Delicious french toast is so simple to make and goes with any breakfast side dish, and served with real maple syrup, its awesome. Use any kind of bread you wish, just use your imagination.
**_French Toast
_** 2 eggs
1/2 c. milk
1 tsp vanilla
Bread (cinnamon, white, whole wheat, etc.)
In mixing bowl scramble the eggs, add milk, and vanilla. Place on pre-heated flat top grill about 375℉. Grill evenly on both sides until golden brown and toast starts to swell.</description></item><item><title>Cinnamon French Toast</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/cinnamon-french-toast/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/cinnamon-french-toast/</guid><description>Cinnamon French Toast for 4 servings 6 eggs 5 oz. milk 2 teaspoons vanilla 1 tablespoon cinnamon Directions Break the eggs into a mixing bowl and blend with whisk. Add the milk, vanilla, cinnamon and whisk briskly. Have a heated and lightly greased pan or electric skillet at 375℉ . Dip your choice of bread into the mixture and place in pan. Cook for about 3-4 minutes on each side or until nice and brown on both sides.</description></item><item><title>Easy Breakfast Recipes</title><link>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 14:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/</guid><description>Breakfast is the most important meal of the day and it gets your metabolism going. A good thing to do first thing in the morning is to drink an 8 oz glass of water with two tablespoons of lemon juice added. This will help kick start your metabolism. Then, have a protein rich breakfast that includes 20 grams of carbs from fruits or whole grains.
Chef Frank’s Easy Breakfast Recipes Cinnamon French Toast</description></item><item><title>How To Make An Easy Wet Burrito</title><link>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-wet-burrito/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-mexican-recipes/easy-wet-burrito/</guid><description>Wet Burrito topped with fresh vegetables, shredded cheese, sour cream. An easy way to make a wet burrito</description></item></channel></rss>