<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Easy Breakfast Recipes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Easy Breakfast Recipes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sausage Gravy For Biscuits</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/sausage-gravy-for-biscuits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/sausage-gravy-for-biscuits/</guid><description>Delicious homemade sausage gravy for biscuits is simple and takes about 15 minutes to prepare. Also click the link to our homemade biscuits.
Sausage Gravy For Biscuits Ingredients 1 lb. ground pork sausage 1 tsp. rubbed sage 1/4 c. diced onions 1/2 tsp. chicken base 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 c. flour 2 c. milk Sausage Gravy For Biscuits Directions Place sausage in large frying with onions and sage.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Homemade Biscuits</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fresh-homemade-biscuits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:26:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fresh-homemade-biscuits/</guid><description>Our homemade biscuits are a light and fluffy quick bread recipe. Less than 10 minutes to prepare, and in the oven for about ten minutes. These biscuits go excellent with strawberry short cake, sausage gravy, stews, and topped with honey butter.
Biscuits Ingredients 2 c flour 2 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 tsp salt 1/3 c veg. shortening 3/4 c milk or buttermilk (if you don’t have buttermilk, just add 1 tsp vineager to milk before mixing).</description></item><item><title>Banana Muffins</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/banana-muffins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:22:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/banana-muffins/</guid><description>Homemade banana muffins, like the bread recipe, is foolproof and only takes 10 (ten) minutes to prepare. Serve while still warm and enjoy with your favorite beverage.
Banana Muffins Ingredients 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/4 tsp salt 1 tsp vanilla 2 eggs 3 bananas 1/4 c butter, melted 1 c sugar 1/2 c milk Directions In mixing bowl combine flour, b. soda, b.</description></item><item><title>Fool Proof Banana Bread</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 14:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</guid><description>Homemade banana bread is truly foolproof and will only take a few minutes to prepare. Take advantage of variations to this recipe by adding nuts of your choice. 1 Hour in the oven and everyone is enjoying warm banana bread!
Banana Bread Recipe 3 ripe bananas 2 eggs 1 c sugar 1/2 c oil 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/4 tsp salt dash milk 1 tsp vanills ext.</description></item><item><title>Apple Bread</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/apple-bread/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/apple-bread/</guid><description>Everyone loves apple bread made from Michigan apples for breakfast. Apple muffins too, and company will love it. Add raisins or dried cherries in the mix if you wish.
2 cups flour 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 tsp vanilla ext. 1/2 tsp salt 1/4 c milk 1/2 c sugar 1/2 c brown sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 1/2 c vegetable oil 2 eggs 4 Michigan apples, tart, peeled, diced, (canned can be used, packed in water) about 3 cups (this can also be form Michigan Apples).</description></item><item><title>Delicious French Toast</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/delicious-french-toast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 13:48:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/delicious-french-toast/</guid><description>Delicious french toast is so simple to make and goes with any breakfast side dish, and served with real maple syrup, its awesome. Use any kind of bread you wish, just use your imagination.
**_French Toast
_** 2 eggs
1/2 c. milk
1 tsp vanilla
Bread (cinnamon, white, whole wheat, etc.)
In mixing bowl scramble the eggs, add milk, and vanilla. Place on pre-heated flat top grill about 375℉. Grill evenly on both sides until golden brown and toast starts to swell.</description></item><item><title>Cinnamon French Toast</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/cinnamon-french-toast/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/cinnamon-french-toast/</guid><description>Cinnamon French Toast for 4 servings 6 eggs 5 oz. milk 2 teaspoons vanilla 1 tablespoon cinnamon Directions Break the eggs into a mixing bowl and blend with whisk. Add the milk, vanilla, cinnamon and whisk briskly. Have a heated and lightly greased pan or electric skillet at 375℉ . Dip your choice of bread into the mixture and place in pan. Cook for about 3-4 minutes on each side or until nice and brown on both sides.</description></item><item><title>Easy Breakfast Recipes</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 14:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/easy-breakfast-recipes/</guid><description>Breakfast is the most important meal of the day and it gets your metabolism going. A good thing to do first thing in the morning is to drink an 8 oz glass of water with two tablespoons of lemon juice added. This will help kick start your metabolism. Then, have a protein rich breakfast that includes 20 grams of carbs from fruits or whole grains.
Chef Frank’s Easy Breakfast Recipes Cinnamon French Toast</description></item></channel></rss>