<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes For Special Occasions and Events on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title>
    <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes For Special Occasions and Events on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 12:58:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalloped Corn Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/scalloped-corn-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/scalloped-corn-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Scalloped Corn Recipe served at Sunday Dinner with Roast Chickenis the best! Scalloped Corn is a five minute prep and is a Delicious Hot Vegetablefor Holidays too!
Scalloped Corn Ingredients  3 cans creamed corn 3 eggs 1 1/2 sleeve saltines (crushed) 1/4 stick butter (melted) 1/8 cup milk pepper to taste (avoid salt as saltines contain enough)  Directions In large mixing bowl add corn, 1 sleeve crackers (crushed), eggs, butter, and milk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Twice Baked Potato</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-twice-baked-potato/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-twice-baked-potato/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Twice Baked Potatoes Recipe ia a Standard for the Holidays. Twice Baked Potatoes with Sour Cream, Chives, and Cheddar Cheese is Delicious.Simple and Delicious Twice Baked PotatoesTwice Baked Potatoes Ingredients Serves 10
 5 russet baking potatoes(large) 3 oz butter 1/2 c sour cream 1 c shredded cheddar cheese salt and pepper to taste paprika  Directions  Bake potatoes at 375℉ for one hour. Remove from oven and let cool only long enough to cut in half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Sweet Potato Casserole</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/healthy-sweet-potato-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/healthy-sweet-potato-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Potato Casserole with Michigan Apples and Cranberries Compliment Porkand Chicken EntreeDishes. An easy Side Dish for Get Togethers with Family and Friends or for the Holidays.
Sweet Potato Casserole with Michigan Apples and Cranberries Ingredients serves10-12
 6 large sweet potatoes( peeled cut in chunks) 1 lb fresh cranberries 3 large Michigan apples (peeled and cut bite size) 2 c apple juice or cider  Directions Put ingredients in baking dish, cover, and bake 350℉ for 1 hour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed Acorn Squash Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/stuffed-acorn-squash-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/stuffed-acorn-squash-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick and Easy Stuffed Acorn Squash for the Fall and Holiday Season. Use Fresh Acorn Squash in Season, it’s Easily Stuffed and Satisfying.
Stuffed Acorn Squash Ingredients  2 acorn squash cut in 1/2 (from top to bottom) remove seeds 2 lbs ground pork sausage 2 tart apples, peeled, diced small 1 c chopped walnuts 1/2 onion small diced 2 ribs celery small diced 1 tbsp rubbed sage 2 tbsp maple syrup (imitation is fine) 2 eggs 1 tbsp brown sugar  Directions  In large mixing bowl place all ingredients (except squash), and mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Red Potatoes Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/roasted-red-potatoes-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/roasted-red-potatoes-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Roasted Red Potatoes Recipe With Fresh Summer Squash, Onion, Carrots and Rosemary, Roasted with Olive Oil and Spices. Great for The Fall Season.
Roasted Red Potatoes with Vegetables Ingredients serves 6-8
 2 lbs red potatoes, rinsed, cut in 1/2 3 ribs celery, rinsed, angle cut, chunky 1 onion , peeled and quartered 4 carrots, peeled cut in chunks 1 summer squash, cut chunky 1 zucchini squash, cut chunky 2 0z.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Mashed Potatoes Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/homemade-mashed-potatoes-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/homemade-mashed-potatoes-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Mashed Potatoes Recipe can be made with Red, White, Russet or a Combination of any of these. Mashed Potatoes are an American Staple.
Mashed Potatoes Ingredients  2 lbs. potatoes, peeled and cut 2 tbsp butter 1/2 c milk dash salt  Note: There are a number of kinds of potatoes you can use. russets, U.S. no.1’s, yellow, white and even sweet potatoes. You can even mix varieties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lobster Thermidor Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/lobster-thermidor-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/lobster-thermidor-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Lobster Thermidor Recipe is made from Maine or African Rock Lobster. An Elegant Recipe for a Special Dinner. Lobster Thermidor is easy to Prepare and Serve.
Lobster Thermidor Ingredients  3 lb lobster, steamed, cut in 1/2 6 c milk 1 c roux 1 tbsp dry mustard 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1/4 c chopped parsley 3 oz. parmesan cheese  Directions  Heat milk for cream sauce, thicken with roux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Green Bean Casserole</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/simple-green-bean-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/simple-green-bean-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Green Bean Casserole is a standard Recipe used for Holidays and everyday meals. Green Bean Casserole topped with Fried Onions and Cheese will Shake Up your Meals!A Simple and Healthy Green Bean CasseroleGreen Bean Casserole Ingredients serves 8 -10
 2 cans green beans, drained 1 can cream of mushroom soup 1/2 c shredded or diced cheddar cheese (optional) 2 tbsp melted butter French fried onions  Directions Mix green beans with undiluted mushroom soup and melted butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma’s Fried Chicken</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/grandmas-fried-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/grandmas-fried-chicken/</guid>
      <description>I remember being at my grandmother’s house on any Sunday and smelling the aroma from her awesome cooking. Grandmas chicken that she pan fried, then placed in a slow oven. She always had scalloped corn, mashed potatoes and gravy ( made from the chicken pan), Rolls, relish tray, and three layer jello with cream cheese in the middle for dessert. I love to create similar memories for my family. I thank my grandmother for taking the time to show me some of her methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Coq Au Vin Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-coq-au-vin-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-coq-au-vin-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Whole Chicken cut up, Shallots, Onion, and Hearty Burgundy Wine. French Coq Au Vin is served with Wild Rice and any Side Dish Recipe.
Coq Au Vin (Chicken and Wine) Ingredients serves 4
 1 whole chicken cut up 1 gallon hearty burgundy wine 1/2 c. diced shallots 1/2 stick butter 1/2 red onion diced 1 c. fresh sliced mushrooms 1 dash salt and pepper  Directions  Place butter in large stock pot and melt on stove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Chicken Cordon Bleu</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-chicken-cordon-bleu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-chicken-cordon-bleu/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Chicken Cordon Bleu will Make Your Guests Marvel at Your Expertise. This Chicken Cordon Bleu Recipe Is From Italy and Derived form the French Cuisines. Uses Heavy Cream, Brie, and White Wine.
Chicken Cordon Bleu Ingredients serves 4 4 chicken breasts, boneless, skinless 4 slices ham 4 oz. Brie cheese 4 oz. bread crumbs 2 c flour 2-3 c heavy cream 4 oz. white dry wine 2 oz. maitre d’ butter  Directions  Lay chicken breast between plastic wrap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Almondine Flambe’</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/chicken-almondine-flambe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/chicken-almondine-flambe/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Almondine Flambe’ is a Quick Easy Recipe that is Elegant and literally on Fire! Use Chicken, Madeira Wine, Fresh Mushrooms, Onions, and Almonds to Create Chicken Almondine Flambe’.
Chicken Almondine Flambe’ Ingredients serves 4
 4 chicken breasts, cut in 1″ cubes or strips 1 c. slice fresh mushrooms 1/2 onion diced 1/4 c. sliced almonds 3 oz. maitre d’ butter 1 c. madeira wine 2 c. Flour 1 tsp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheese Broccoli Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/cheese-broccoli-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/cheese-broccoli-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Broccoli and Cheese is the Perfect Hot Vegetable Recipeto Accompany Pork, Beefor Chicken Entrees. Broccoli and Cheese is Quick and Easy to Make and Serve.
Broccoli and Cheese Ingredients serves 2
 2 stalks fresh broccoli, cut in sprigs 1/2 c shredded cheese 1 oz. butter 1/8 tsp salt  Directions In sauce pan place water, salt, and broccoli.
Bring to boil and let slow boil for 3 minutes.
Remove from water and place on plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Cheese Ball Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-cheese-ball-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/easy-cheese-ball-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Cheese Balls Recipe is for the Holidays with crackers and other Appetizers. Cheese Balls take 15 minutes to prepare, and are eye appealing too!
Cheese Ball Ingredients  2 8oz. cream cheese 1lb brick cheddar cheese (shredded) 1 med onion finely chopped 3 tsp worcestershire sauce 1-2 tsp milk 1 tsp garlic (fresh or granulated) 1/2 c chopped nuts (pecans)  Directions Mix all ingredients together. Form two balls evenly then roll in nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Sage and Walnut Stuffing Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/apple-sage-and-walnut-stuffing-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/apple-sage-and-walnut-stuffing-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Apple Sage and Walnut Stuffing Recipe Made with Michigan Apples is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Apple Sage Walnut Stuffing for your Thanksgiving MealWill ad a Warm Charm to your Holiday Feast.
Apple Sage Walnut Stuffing Ingredients  6 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 rib celery diced 2 tbsp sage rubbed 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 Michigan tart apple peeled, diced 1 c chopped walnuts 1/2 stick butter 1/8 tsp white pepper dash garlic, granulated  Directions Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Apple Sage Stuffing</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sage-stuffing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sage-stuffing/</guid>
      <description>Apple Sage Stuffing Recipe Made with Michigan Apples is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Even Using Fresh Grown Sage. Apple Sage Stuffing for the Holidays will Enhance Your Holiday Meal.
Apple Sage Stuffing Ingredients  6 c water 2 tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 rib celery diced 2 tbsp sage rubbed 1 Michigan tart apple peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1/8 tsp white pepper dash garlic, granulated  Directions Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Apple Sauce</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/michigan-apple-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Michigan applesauce is easy to prepare on the stove, and using tart Michigan apples is the only way to go.
Michigan Apple Sauce Recipe  5 tart Michigan apples, peeled, chunked 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/2 c sugar 1/4 c water  Directions Place all ingredients in sauce pan. Cook on low heat, stirring often. Applesauce is done when apples are incorporated and soft. Serve as a side dish with ham, or pork, or by itself as a snack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Acorn Squash Recipe</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/baked-acorn-squash-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/baked-acorn-squash-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Baked Acorn Squash, a staple for any holiday dinneror a great hot vegetablefor any fall meal. Baked Acorn Squash is Easy in the microwave or oven. Top your Holidays with this great recipe.
 Acorn Squash 2 acorn squash 3 tbsp brown sugar 3 oz. butter, melted salt and pepper to taste  Cut squash in 1/2 or 1/4’s. place on cookie sheet or baking dish. Brush melted butter over squash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Fruit Tray For Special Occasions</title>
      <link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/fresh-fruit-tray-for-special-occasions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipes-for-special-occasions-and-events/fresh-fruit-tray-for-special-occasions/</guid>
      <description>A fresh fruit tray is guaranteed to sparkle as the centerpiece of any gathering. Follow our instructions to really dress it up for a special occasion.
Ingredients Prep time: 1 hr.
Fruit used for this:
 2 large watermelon 6 pineapples 3 large muskmelon 3 large cantelope 5 large oranges 3# red grapes 3# green grapes 10 kiwi 3 large pink grapefruit 10 lbs. fresh strawberries 2 pt. blackberries 2 pt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>