<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beef Dishes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/</link><description>Recent content in Beef Dishes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 21:59:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/recipes/beef-dishes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beef Fajitas</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-fajitas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-fajitas/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Fajitas Recipe with soft tortillas and spicy beef, grilled onions, and peppers. Beef Fajitas go well with quick Spanish rice and shredded cheddar cheese.
 Beef Fajitas Ingredients 2 lb sirloin steak, cut in thin strips 1 green pepper, cut in strips 1 onion, cut in strips 2 tbsp oil 2 tbsp salsa 1 pkg fajita seasoning 1 tsp chili powder Toppings Diced tomato shredded lettuce shredded cheese sour cream salsa refried beans guacamole sliced jalapenos Beef Fajitas Directions In medium size mixing bowl, place meat, fajita seasoning, and salsa, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Easy Swiss Steak Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-swiss-steak-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:37:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-swiss-steak-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Swiss Steak Recipe uses Fresh Round Steak or Sirloin, Rolled in flour, Spices, and Browned in Butter. Swiss Steak Entree and Mashed Potatoes with a Vegetable is a Satisfying Meal and Leaves Everyone Full and Happy.
Swiss Steak Ingredients serves 4
1 lb round steak or sirloin steak, cut in 4 0z portions 1 onion sliced 1 can diced tomatoes (optional) 1/2 green pepper diced 2 tsp beef base 2 cups water salt and pepper to taste 1 c flour 2 0z.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Salisbury Steak</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/homemade-salisbury-steak/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/homemade-salisbury-steak/</guid><description>Quick Easy Salisbury Steak recipe with fresh ground beef, onion, green pepper, eggs and spices. Salisbury Steak is a favorite with mashed redskin potatoes and beef mushroom gravy.
Salisbury Steak With Fresh Ground Beef Ingredients serves 8-12
3 lb ground beef 3 eggs 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1/2 sleeve saltines, crushed 1 tsp worcestershire sauce 1/2 tbsp garlic, chopped or granulated Salisbury Steak Directions In large mixing bowl place all ingredients and mix well.</description></item><item><title>Beef Pot Roast Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-roast-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-roast-recipe/</guid><description>Beef Pot Roast for a Delicious Supper is a Quick Easy Recipe with Potatoes and Carrots, and only takes 15 Minutes to Prepare, then place in Oven to Roast. Sunday we’re having Pot Roast!
Pot Roast of Beef (English cut or Chuck) Ingredients serves 8
3-4 lb roast 1 onion cut in chunks 8 potatoes peeled, cut in half 8 carrots peeled, cut in 1/4’s 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/8 tsp white pepper 1 tsp garlic (granulated or fresh) 2 c water Directions Place water and roast in roasting pan.</description></item><item><title>Baked Corned Beef Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/baked-corned-beef-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 23:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/baked-corned-beef-recipe/</guid><description>Roasted Corned Beef Recipe is Quick and Easy with a spicy mustard and honey seasoning. Roasted Corned Beef is a great Fall recipe and goes well with red potatoes and cabbage.
Baked Corned Beef Ingredients (with Honey Mustard Optional) serves 10-14
3-5 lb corned beef brisket (raw, usually contains season packet) 1 c dijon mustard 1/4 c honey 1 tsp garlic, granulated or fresh chopped (in jars at your grocers) 1/8 tsp white pepper 1/2 c apple juice Baked Corned Beef Directions Using a roaster, pour in apple juice.</description></item><item><title>Healthy Meatloaf Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/healthy-meatloaf-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/healthy-meatloaf-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Meatloaf Recipe from Mom’s Cupboard is made from Fresh Ground Beef, Onions, Celery, Eggs, Bread, and Spices. Meatloaf also makes Good Leftovers for Sandwiches or just re-heat and eat.
Meatloaf Ingredients serves4-6
2 lb. ground beef 3 eggs 1/2 onion diced 1 rib celery cut into small pieces. 1 c ketchup 1/2 tsp garlic, (chopped or granulated) 1 1/2 cups bread crumbs 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce pepper to taste season salt to taste, or1/2 tsp 1/2 c water Directions In a large mixing bowl, soak the bread in the water, then add everything but the ground beef and mix well.</description></item><item><title>Irish Steak and Dark Beer Pie</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/irish-steak-and-dark-beer-pie/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/irish-steak-and-dark-beer-pie/</guid><description>Celebrate St Patrick’s Day anytime with our Irish Steak and Dark Beer Pie Recipe. An Easy and Fun Supper to Make and Quick to Disappear. An Irish Entree Recipe Everyone will Love.
Irish Steak and Dark Beer Pie serves 6
2 pkg pie crust (or crust for two 9″ pies) 3 lbs sirloin steak, cut in 2″ long thin strips 3-4 bottles dark beer 1 bunch scallions (green onions) chopped 1 lb sliced fresh mushrooms 1/2 red onion sliced or diced 4 large red potatoes thinly sliced 4 carrots, peeled sliced thin 1 tsp beef base 2 or more tbs roux Directions For The Pie Place thinly sliced steak in frying pan to brown on high heat, (be careful not to put too much in or it could get watery).</description></item><item><title>Hamburger Gravy Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/hamburger-gravy-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/hamburger-gravy-recipe/</guid><description>Simple hamburger gravy on the nights you’re in a rush. Put over mashed potatoes and it only takes a few minutes to prepare. Goes well with salads, vegetables or breads.
Hamburger Gravy – Simple Family Dinner Recipe 1 lb. ground beef 1/2 c. chopped onion 1/2 c. flour 1 tsp beef base 3 c. water Directions Brown ground beef with onions in large frying pan. When ground beef is cooked, add beef base and sprinkle flour over ground beef and stir together over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Beef Tips And Noodles Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-tips-and-noodles-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-tips-and-noodles-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Tips and Noodles is an easy recipe to prepare and serve for supper. Beef Tips and Noodlesrecipe is made from diced beef, thick gravy, and noodles. A delicious comfort food.
Beef Tips and Noodles serves4-6
1 lb. diced beef 1/2 onion diced 1 rib celery diced small 1 lb pasta 1 lb. roux 1 tbsp beef base 1 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp garlic granulated dash pepper Directions Brown beef in pan then transfer to large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Quick Beef Stew</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/quick-beef-stew/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/quick-beef-stew/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Stew will warm your heart and tummy. Beef Stew with vegetables and thick gravy is great with biscuits and a salad or fruit. Beef Stew always makes good leftovers.
Beef Stew Recipe serves4-6
1 lb diced beef 2 large carrots 2 ribs celery 1 lg onion 3-4 lg potatoes 1 tbsp beef base garlic, salt &amp;amp; pepper to taste Directions Clean and cut vegetables into desired size.</description></item><item><title>Easy Beef Stir Fry Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-beef-stir-fry-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/easy-beef-stir-fry-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Beef Stir Fry with Fresh Vegetables, Served over rice with egg rolls and soy sauce. Beef Stir Fry is Healthy and easy for those in-a-hurry times.
Beef Stir Fry serves 10-15
3-4 lbs beef steak, cut in strips 1 bunch broccoli 1 onion 2 ribs celery 1 carrot (large) 1 green pepper 4 oz. fresh pea pods 2 c cauliflower 2 c fresh bean sprouts 1 c fresh mushrooms soy sauce-to taste 2 tbsp olive oil ginger, ground or fresh grated Directions Clean and cut all vegetable in about 1″ squares in strips, carrots should be sliced thin.</description></item><item><title>Beef Pot Pie Recipe</title><link>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-pie-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/beef-dishes/beef-pot-pie-recipe/</guid><description>Beef Pot Pie is a quick and easy recipe for supper tonight. Fresh beef sirloin and vegetables in a thick gravy with a golden crust. Very delicious Beef Pot Pie.
Beef Pot Pie Recipe 2 pkg pie crust, 2 crusts, 9″ 1 lb.diced beef(sirloin) 4 carrots, peeled, sliced 4 potatoes, peeled, large cut 1 onion diced 2 ribs celery, diced 1 tbsp beef base 1/2 tsp white pepper 4 cups water 1/2 c roux Directions Place beef, spices, and vegetables in large kettle.</description></item></channel></rss>