<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Institutional Recipes For 200 on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title>
    <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Institutional Recipes For 200 on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:37:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick and Easy Chili Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/quick-and-easy-chili-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/quick-and-easy-chili-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Try this quick easy chili recipe for school kid’s lunch or a church function. Corn bread and shredded cheddar cheese along with a saladmake this a great meal and is very affordable as well.
Here’s the chili recipe for those of you cooking for a crowd:
Ingredients  56# chili beans(red) ( 7 no. 10 cans) 11 qts tomato juice 30# ground beef 6 large green peppers diced 4 large spanish onions diced 2 large stalks celery diced 1 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti Sauce Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/spaghetti-sauce-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/spaghetti-sauce-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Our Spaghetti Sauce Recipe for 200 People will guarantee success for your large group meal. Fresh ground beef, herbs and spicesand tomato sauce make our spaghetti sauce for 200 a hit! A quick easy recipe. Simply omit the ground beef for a fantastic vegetarian recipe!
Spaghetti Sauce for 200 Ingredients  40# ground beef, cooked, drained (optional) 8- #10 cans tomato sauce 1- #10 can tomato paste 4 onions, diced 1/2 c chopped garlic,fresh or dehydrated 2 green peppers, diced 2# fresh sliced mushrooms 1 c brown sugar 1/2 c soy sauce 1 c leaf oregano 1/2 c basil, (1 cup if fresh) 2 tbsp ground rosemary 1 tbsp white pepper 20 bay leaves, whole (to be removed before serving)  Directions Prepare ground beef and sauce in intervals together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalloped Corn Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/scalloped-corn-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/scalloped-corn-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Scalloped Corn is quite an easy institutional recipe to prepare for large groups and accompanies many entrees. Scalloped Corn for 200 will hold for several hours in a warmer at 140℉ – 165℉.
Scalloped Corn for 200 Ingredients  8 #10 cans cans creamed corn 30 eggs 2 lbs saltines (crushed) 2 lbs butter (melted) 2 c. milk 2 tbs pepper (avoid salt as saltines contain enough)  Directions In large mixing bowl add corn, 1 1/2 lbs crackers (crushed), eggs, butter, and milk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Seed Bread Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/poppy-seed-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/poppy-seed-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Easy quick poppy seed bread recipe for dessertor as a breakfast bread. makes great muffinstoo. poppy seed bread for 200 will keep your clients tummies happy and is easy to prepare and serve.
Poppy Seed Bread for 200 Ingredients  20# yellow cake mix 8# toasted coconut instant pudding mix (vanilla pudding and add toasted coconut works too.) 20 large eggs 4 c vegetable oil 3 c soaked and drained poppy seeds 6 c hot water  Directions Mix all ingredients in large mixer bowl, beat as for cake on medium speed for two minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meatloaf Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/meatloaf-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/meatloaf-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Meatloaf for 200 people is a quick easy recipe when feeding a crowd. Mashed potatoesand green beansis standard with this meatloaf recipe. Use leftovers for sandwichesor put in spaghetti sauce.
Ingredients  50# ground beef (19/79) 5# diced onions 3# diced celery 50 eggs 3 loaves bread or 3#( or any buns or leftover breads) 3 tbsp beef base 4 c ketchup 1/4 c granulated or chopped garlic 1 tbsp white pepper 2 qts water  Directions In 60 qt mixer place all ingredients (except ground beef), mix well on speed #1 (low) until ingredients are blended together, then add ground beef and mix until incorporated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macaroni and Cheese Recipe For 200</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/macaroni-and-cheese-recipe-for-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/macaroni-and-cheese-recipe-for-200/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Institutional Macaroni and Cheddar Cheese Recipe is the Favorite of most Kids. Macaroni and Cheddar Cheese from Scratch is great with Fresh Watermelon and Salads. A Warm Roll is Nice too!
Macaroni and Cheese with Cheddar for 240 people Prep time: 30 minutes
Cook time: 30 minutes
Serves: 240
Ingredients  30# elbo macaroni 25# shredded cheddar cheese (medium or sharp) 2 lbs melted butter 1 1/2 gallons milk 2 tbsp salt 2 tbsp pepper  Directions In large kettle or two kettles, place macaroni in boiling water, stir frequently to keep from sticking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Baked Ham Recipe For 200</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/honey-baked-ham-recipe-for-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 15:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/honey-baked-ham-recipe-for-200/</guid>
      <description>Delicious honey baked ham for 200 with a quick 15 minute prep time and 1 hour cook time is easy for large group meals. Honey baked ham recipe has honey, clove, brown sugar, and applesauce, very delicious!
Honey Baked Ham for 200 Recipe Ingredients  45# whole ham (flat buffet)sliced 1/4 inch thick 5 tsp ground clove 4 c honey 10 c applesauce 8 c brown sugar  Directions In shallow hotel pans, shingle ham.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Chip Cookies Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Real Chocolate Chip Cookies are Quick and Easy Scratch Cookies to make for Gatherings, Large Groups, Camps, or Schools. Kids love them and will want them again! Quick Easy Institutional Recipe.
Real Chocolate Chip Cookies Recipe for 200 People Ingredients  4 lbs. butter softened 16 eggs 6 c. brown sugar 6 c. sugar 20 c. flour 2 tbs vanilla 2 tbs baking powder 2 tbs baking soda 2 tsp salt 24 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread And Muffins Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Banana Bread Recipe For 200 Quick Easy Banana Bread or Muffins for 280 People. This Quick Easy Institutional Scratch Recipe will keep your clients happy. Use the same Quick Easy Banana Bread Recipe for Muffins.
Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Banana Bread Ingredients  60 ripe peeled bananas 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda  Banana Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Apple Pudding Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/easy-apple-pudding-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/easy-apple-pudding-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Delicious apple pudding for 200 people is a very popular dessertin the fall or for any season. Great for schools, churches and special functions.
Apple Pudding for 200 People Ingredients Apple Base Ingredients  8 – #10 cans sliced waterpack apples 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tsp salt 8 tbs cinnamon  Topping Ingredients  12 c. flour 5# butter, melted 5 c. brown sugar 2 tbs cinnamon 6 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Crisp For 200</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</guid>
      <description>Kids and adults love apple crisp for dessert. So easy to make and goes with any meal. Schools, camps, and churches love this recipe.
Apple Crisp for 200 People Apple Ingredients  8 #10 cans sliced apples (water pack) 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tbs cinnamon 8- 2″ full size hotel pans  Apple Directions place 1 can apples, (do not drain) in each pan and even out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Bread For 200 Recipe</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 14:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Our apple bread recipe is easy to make about a 15 minute prep time. This recipe from scratch will keep your clients happy. Apple quick bread for 200 will enhance any breakfast and makes great muffins too.
Apple Bread Or Muffins For 200 Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Apple Bread Ingredients  2 #10 cans sliced apples (chop up to marble size pieces) 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 2 tbsp cinnamon 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda  Apple Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
