<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Easy Vegetarian Dinner Recipes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Easy Vegetarian Dinner Recipes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cream Of Broccoli Soup Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/cream-of-broccoli-soup-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/cream-of-broccoli-soup-recipe/</guid><description>Cream of Broccoli Soup is a Hearty Quick and Easy Cream Soup Recipe For Lunch or a Meal with Your Favorite Sandwich, or Accompanying Any Salad. Cream of Broccoli is Made With Fresh Broccoli.
Cream of Broccoli Soup Ingredients Serves 8-10
4-5 cups chopped fresh broccoli 1/2 onion, diced 2 ribs celery, fine chopped 1 large carrot, 1/4’d diced roux 3 cups heavy cream 3 cups milk 1/8 tsp white pepper 1 tsp vegetable or chicken base 2 cups water Cream of Broccoli Soup Directions In large kettle, place water, carrots, onion, celery, vegetable or chicken base, and white pepper.</description></item><item><title>Easy Apple Dumplings</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-dumplings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-dumplings/</guid><description>Apple Dumplings Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare for Family and Guests. Warm Apple Dumplings a Great Recipe to Top off with Ice Cream. Serve Warm Apple Dumplings for a Party Finale.
Apple Dumplings Ingredients serves 8
1 pkg pie crusts, cut in quarters 5 tart Michigan apples, peeled, diced 1/2 c sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 2 0z. butter, melted 1 tbsp quick tapioca Directions Place quartered crusts in greased muffin tin cups, leaving top open.</description></item><item><title>Easy Apple Pie</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/easy-apple-pie/</guid><description>Apple Pie with Michigan Apples is Quick to Prepare and Easy to Eat. Using Fresh Apples for This Apple Pie Recipe, Tops off any Meal, Top that with Vanilla Ice Cream or Cheese.
Easy Apple Pie Recipe 1 pkg Pie crust for 2 crust pie, 9″ 6-8 Michigan spies, or granny smith apples (peeled and thinly sliced) 3/4 c sugar 1 tsp lemon juice 3 1/2 tbsp quick tapioca 1/8 tsp salt 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1/8 tsp ground nutmeg 2 tbsp butter, melted Directions Press one crust in pie shell, don’t trim</description></item><item><title>How To Make An Egg Wash</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-an-egg-wash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-an-egg-wash/</guid><description>Quick Easy Egg Wash Recipe for Putting a Shine on all your Pie and Pastry Crusts. Egg Wash Takes a Minute to Prepare and adds Eye Appeal to your Pie and Pastry Recipes.
If you’re Making a Fruit Pie, Sprinkle a Little Sugar on Top of your Crust After you Brush it with Egg Wash.
Egg Wash Ingredients Enough for 2 pies
1 egg 1 oz. water Directions Whisk together.</description></item><item><title>How To Make Roux</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-roux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/how-to-make-roux/</guid><description>Roux is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare for Thickening Gravies and Sauces. Use Roux in Making Cream Soup Recipes like Clam Chowder and Cream of Broccoli Soup. Stews and Desserts too.
Roux Ingredients 1 lb butter or margarine 1 lb flour Directions Heat butter in small sauce pan until it comes to a boil. Add flour, mix well and set aside. May be held for up to two weeks in fridge.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Chili Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-chili-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-chili-recipe/</guid><description>Vegetarian Mexican Chili a Quick Easy Recipe for Lunch or Dinner. Vegetarian Mexican Chili with Corn Muffins, Crackers, and A Green Leafy Salad or Sandwich. A True Comfort Food Soup.
Vegetarian Chili Ingredients 2 cans chili beans 1 onion, chopped 1 green pepper, chopped or diced 2 ribs celery, chopped 2 tsp garlic, chopped or granulated 2 tbsp ground cumin 1 tbsp chili powder 2 qts tomato juice 4-6 oz.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Spaghetti Recipe</title><link>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-spaghetti-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/easy-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/vegetarian-spaghetti-recipe/</guid><description>Vegetarian Homemade Spaghetti Sauce with Optional TVP (textured vegetable protein) is Quick and Easy to Make. Let Simmer on the Stove, Crockpot, or in the Oven. Our Homemade Scratch Spaghetti Sauce Recipes are a Breeze for Busy People. Serve over Penne, Ravioli, Spaghetti Pasta, and Makes an Excellent Pizza Sauce too.
Vegetarian Spaghetti Sauce Ingredients **12+ servings
**
1/2 c dried tvp(textured vegetable protein) optional, but a good source of protein.</description></item></channel></rss>