<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chef's Blog on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Chef's Blog on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 02:18:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/quick-e-recipes-hugo/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello world!</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 02:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</description></item><item><title>Onion Smell Tips</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/onion-smell-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:39:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/onion-smell-tips/</guid><description>Having a hard time getting the onion smell off your hands? Try running your hands in cool water for a few seconds, then grasp the neck of the faucet and slide you hands quickly back and forth on the chrome causing some friction. Rinse and Voila! No smell.</description></item><item><title>Clean As You Go!</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/clean-as-you-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/clean-as-you-go/</guid><description>I keep a sink full of soapy hot water hand so I can wash dishes between tasks. This helps keep your area free of clutter, and if guests are coming they don’t see a big mess.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Crowd Me!</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/dont-crowd-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/dont-crowd-me/</guid><description>I was thinking about crowding the other day as I sat on bleachers in the gym waiting to hear our grandson sing for his class Christmas concert. It was uncomfortable and hot, with little room to relax your arms or stretch your legs. It was all worth it when our grandson was on stage singing and shyly smiling as he noticed us in the audience. After the concert I started thinking about food crowding and how it challenges the quality of a recipe.</description></item><item><title>Why I Became A Cook</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/why-i-became-a-cook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/why-i-became-a-cook/</guid><description>&lt;p>I remember as a small child of 4or5 years old sitting in front of our black and white TV. On the screen was a lady pouring in a powdery substance, then adding a liquid. She started stirring the mixture up and all of a sudden it was something totally different, a doughy mound. ” Wow”, I thought, ” I wish I could do that”. I can’t explain why I was so mesmerized by something so simple, but I knew I wanted to what that lady did on TV.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chef’s Blog</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:36:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/blog/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>