<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes From Friends on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/</link><description>Recent content in Recipes From Friends on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/recipes/recipes-from-friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vegetables and Salad Recipes</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/vegetables-and-salad-recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/vegetables-and-salad-recipes/</guid><description>Prepare tasty fresh and colorful salads with garden fresh vegetables. Enjoy healthy summer eating fresh from the great outdoors.
Green Salads Ceasar Salad
Chef Salad
Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad
Pasta Salad
Strawberry Spinach Salad
Tossed Garden Salad
Garden Vegetable Salad
Mayo-based Salads Macaroni Salad
Potato Salad
Tuna Tomato Lotus
Turkey Salad, with apples, raisins, almonds.</description></item><item><title>Tana’s Country Style Chicken Kiev Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/tanas-country-style-chicken-kiev-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/tanas-country-style-chicken-kiev-recipe/</guid><description>Tana’s Country Style Chicken Kiev Recipe is a Quick Easy way to a Wonderful Meal. For Holidays or Everyday Entrees. Serve with any Rice, Side Dish, Fruit, or Hot Vegetable.
Tana’s Country Style Chicken Kiev Recipe from Tana B.
4 chicken breast halves 1/4 c white wine, or apple juice 1/2 c sweet cream butter 1/2 to 1 c fine dry bread crumbs 1/4 c chopped green onion 1/4 c chopped fresh parsley (or dried) 2 tbs grated parmesan cheese 1 tsp basil leaves 1 tsp oregano leaves 1/2 tsp garlic salt 1/4 tsp salt Heat oven to 375℉.</description></item><item><title>Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/sandys-sausage-and-cheese-dip-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/sandys-sausage-and-cheese-dip-recipe/</guid><description>Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip Recipe is Fun for Partiesor an Easy Snack While Watching Sports or your Favorite Movie. Tortilla Chips are Best Friends with Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip.
Sandy’s Sausage and Cheese Dip Recipe Recipe from Sandy R.
1/2 lb. ground beef 1/2 lb. pork sausage ( brand name or bulk ground) 1 lb. pkg processed soft american cheese 1 10 oz. can cr. of mushroom soup 1/2 c finely chopped onion 1/2 c picante sauce 1/2 tsp garlic powder Cook beef and sausage in large kettle until browned.</description></item><item><title>Molly’s White Chili Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/mollys-white-chili-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/mollys-white-chili-recipe/</guid><description>Molly’s White Chili Recipe is not only Easy to Make, it’s delicious and cheap. Top with Sour Cream or Thicken with Pureed Garbonzo or Northern Beans. You can Use your Imagination with this Recipe. You can add Red Pepper too!
Molly’s White Chili, Easy, Cheap, and Good Recipe from Molly P.
2 cans chicken broth 3 cans cooked chicken (or leftovers cut up) 1 jar or 3 cans northern beans 2 cans chopped green chilies 1 brick Monterey jack cheese for topping ( shredded or cut up) Directions In large soup kettle combine broth, chicken, beans, and green chilies.</description></item><item><title>Kory’s 2nd Grade Voyageur Stew</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/korys-2nd-grade-voyageur-stew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/korys-2nd-grade-voyageur-stew/</guid><description>This Recipe for Kory’s 2nd Grade Voyageur Stew is Hearty, Easy, and Fun. The Kids Love to Help Make This While Camping or at Home “Chillin” With The Family. Don’t Forget the Dutch Oven!
Kory’s 2nd Grade Voyageur Stew Recipe from Kathy F.
2 lbs. ground beef 1-2 chopped onions 1 can vegetable soup 1 can cut carrots 1 can corn 1 can peas 1 can green beans 2 cans small potatoes 1 48 oz.</description></item><item><title>Monkey Bread Coffee Cake Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/monkey-bread-coffee-cake-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:06:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/monkey-bread-coffee-cake-recipe/</guid><description>Kathy’s Monkey Bread Coffee Cake Recipe is nice for Sunday Morning Breakfast, or when your Scrap booking with Friends. Makes a Great Starter or Dessertfor Favorite Meals too! Can you Smell the Aroma?
Kathy’s Monkey Bread Coffee Cake Recipe From Kathy F.
3 cans buttermilk biscuits 1 stick margerine 3 tsp cinnamon 1 c sugar 1 c brown sugar Directions Preheat oven to 350℉
Cut each biscuit into 4 pieces.</description></item><item><title>Kathy’s Moist and Juicy Pork Chops</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/kathys-moist-and-juicy-pork-chops/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 23:03:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/kathys-moist-and-juicy-pork-chops/</guid><description>Kathy’s Moist and Juicy Pork Chops Recipe is so Quick and Easy to Prepare, About Ten Minutes and in the Oven it Goes! Ground Cloves, Applesauceand Brown Sugar is the Secret Revealed! Enjoy for Supper Tonight!
Kathy’s Moist and Juicy Pork Chops Recipe From Kathy F.
4-6 pork chops browned Mix:
1 c applesauce 1/3 c brown sugar 1/4 tsp ground cloves Place pork chops in baking dish.</description></item><item><title>Karen’s Grape Salad</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/karens-grape-salad/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/karens-grape-salad/</guid><description>This Wonderful Salad Made from Fresh Grapes is Great for Potluck Dinners, Holidays, Picnics and Barbecues,or Anytime, and can be Made the Night Before.
Karen’s Grape Salad Recipe From Karen A.
8 oz. cream cheese 1 c sour cream 1/2 c sugar 1 tsp vanilla Beat together until smooth Mix with 2 lbs. washed seedless grapes ( red green or both) Put into dish or 9×13 pan
Sprinkle top with 1 c brown sugar and 1 c chopped pecans</description></item><item><title>Jamie’s Mothership Tomato Salad</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/jamies-mothership-tomato-salad/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/jamies-mothership-tomato-salad/</guid><description>Jamie’s Mothership Tomato Salad is Fantastic and is Totally Delicious to Eat on it’s Own. It’s also Great Served with some Balls of Mozzerella and nice, Grilled Ciabatta Bread.
Jamie’s Mothership Tomato Salad Recipe from Jamie O.
Ingredients 2 1/4 lbs mixed ripe tomatoes, different shapes and colors sea salt and freshly ground pepper to taste a good pinch of dried oregano Red wine or balsamic vinegar extra virgin olive oil 1 clove garlic, peeled, grated 1 fresh red chili, deseeded and chopped Directions Depending on the size of your tomatoes, slice some in half and some in quarters and others into uneven chunks.</description></item><item><title>Dottie’s Salmon Patties</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/dotties-salmon-patties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/dotties-salmon-patties/</guid><description>Dottie’s Salmon Patties Recipe is Easy to Make and goes with a Spring Salad, Fresh Fruits and Vegetables, or Sandwiches. Dotties Salmon Patties are Wonderful and Versatile, use Your Imagination.
Dottie’s Salmon Patties Recipe from Dottie F.
Makes 6 Patties
1- 15oz. can salmon 16 saltine crackers 2 eggs some milk ( just enough to moisten) salt and pepper to taste 1/2 onion, diced small (optional) Directions Mix altogether, make patties, fry in pan in light oil until golden brown- makes 6 patties.</description></item><item><title>Easy Taco Salad Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/easy-taco-salad-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:48:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/easy-taco-salad-recipe/</guid><description>Colleen’s Taco Salad will be the Hit of any Party or Bring a Pleasant Southwest Atmosphere to any Supper Table. Fresh Ground Beef and Seasonings Make this recipe because it is easy to prepare and enjoy.
Colleen’s Taco Salad Ingredients Ground Beef Directions 1 lb. ground beef Browned 1 med. diced onion Drain off Fat 1 pkg taco seasoning mix (any kind) mix with onion and burger (prepare as directed) 1 pkg lettuce (regular or shredded) 1 can sliced black olives 3 diced roma tomatoes 1 pkg shredded cheddar cheese 1 pkg tortilla chips ( any flavor you like) 1 med.</description></item><item><title>Meatloaf Portabella Recipe</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/meatloaf-portabella-recipe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/meatloaf-portabella-recipe/</guid><description>Ann’s Meatloaf Portabella Starts with Fresh Ground Chuck, Garden Squash, and Portabella Mushrooms. Wonderful Comfort Food Entree goes well with Mashed Potatoes, Gravy, and Hot Vegetables.
Ann’s Meatloaf Portabella Recipe from Ann L.
serves 6-8
3-4 lbs. ground chuck 8-12 oz. portabella mushrooms diced 5 eggs 1 lb colby jack cheese, shredded 1 small zucchini diced 1 small summer squash diced 3 cloves garlic fine diced 2-3 tomatoes crushed 1 small sweet onion diced 1 tbs salt-less seasoning 2 tsp course ground black pepper Directions In large bowl mix together all ingredients.</description></item><item><title>How To Make A Rainbow Cake By Angie</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/how-to-make-a-rainbow-cake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/how-to-make-a-rainbow-cake/</guid><description>Angie’s “How to Make a Rainbow Cake” Recipe is Perfect for KidsBirthdays, Easter, any Family Celebrations. Angie say’s Once your Kids Have One, they Want One Forever!Angie’s How to Make a Rainbow Cake!Once your kids have one, they want one forever!
Recipe from Angie M.
Use one box of white cake mix, follow directions on box.
Split the batter into 6 equal parts using cereal bowls.
Color and mix together each bowl as follows:</description></item><item><title>Angie’s Crescent Turkey Casserole</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/angies-crescent-turkey-casserole/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 22:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/angies-crescent-turkey-casserole/</guid><description>Angie’s Crescent Turkey Casserole is Easy to Prepare in a Slow Cooker while Away, or at Home in Time for Supper. We have to Call this Comfort Food. Serve with Salads, Fresh Vegetables or Fruits. Ready in 30 Minutes.
Angie’s Crescent Turkey Casserole 4 servings
Recipe from Angie G.
Prep/total time 30 min.
1/2 c mayonnaise (canola) 2 tbs all-purpose flour 1 tsp chicken boullion 1/8 tsp pepper 3/4 c milk (1%) 1 1/2 c cubed cooked turkey breast ( or chicken) 1 pkg ( 10 oz.</description></item><item><title>Amy’s Chocolate Scotcheroos</title><link>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/amys-chocolate-scotcheroos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recipes/recipes-from-friends/amys-chocolate-scotcheroos/</guid><description>Cure your Sweet Tooth With Amy’s Chocolate Scotcheroos and don’t forget to share. This Dessert will Please the Pickiest Eaters.
Amy’s Chocolate Scotcheroos Recipe Recipe from Amy F.
Makes 48 bars
1 c light corn syrup 1 c sugar 1 c peanut butter 6 cups crispy rice cereal 1 c semi sweet chocolate chips 1 c butterscotch chips Vegetable cooking spray Directions Place corn syrup and sugar into a large saucepan.</description></item></channel></rss>