<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chef Frank’s Seasoning Recipes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Chef Frank’s Seasoning Recipes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:19:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fresh Summer Cucumber Salad</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/fresh-summer-cucumber-salad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:43:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/fresh-summer-cucumber-salad/</guid><description>Fresh from the garden comes this wonderful cucumber salad with fresh summer garden tomato, and onion. Simple and delicious for steak or rib cookouts and family meals.
Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad Ingredients 1 large seedless cucumber 1/2 large sweet onion 1 fresh tomato 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 c. apple cider vineager 1 tbsp sugar 1/2 c. water Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad Directions Cut vegetables into large chunks (bite size) and place into right sized bowl.</description></item><item><title>Tartar Sauce For Fish</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tartar-sauce-for-fish/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tartar-sauce-for-fish/</guid><description>Quick Easy Tartar Sauce Recipe makes fish meals complete. With a touch of lemon, Tartar Sauce is great with Fried Clams or Walleye, and Fish and Chips.
Tartar Sauce Ingredients 1 c mayonaise or salad dressing 1/2 c sweet pickle relish 1 -2 tbsp lemon juice 1/2 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning Tartar Sauce Directions Mix ingredients together well, serve with fish and other seafoods. Refrigerate, covered.
Note: Did you know that by adding1/4 c ketchup to this recipe you have a great Thousand Island sauce.</description></item><item><title>Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Our honey teriyaki barbecue sauce will become a staple in your recipe file. It’s easy to prepare on the stove and great for the barbecue grillfor ribs, chicken, chops and steaks.
Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 2 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 c pineapple juice ( or 1 c, pureed fresh pineapple) 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses 2 tbsp grape jelly Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour or until reduced, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Goulash With Ground Beef</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:35:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</guid><description>Quick Easy Goulash Recipe with Fresh Ground Beef and Elbow Macaroni, Tomato Sauce and Fresh Cut Vegetables with Cheese. Goulash is a Great Casserole for Lunch or Supper.
Goulash serves 8
1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 lb ground beef, cooked, drained 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 can tomato sauce 1 can diced tomatoes 2 oz. melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp chili powder 1 c shredded cheddar cheese(optional) Combine all ingredients in large mixing bowl.</description></item><item><title>Scalloped Potatoes – Grandma’s Comfort Food</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:32:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</guid><description>Quick Easy Scalloped Potatoes is Grandma’s recipe and will satisfy any appetite. Add ham to this Scalloped Potato recipe for a wonderful comfort food a cold winter day.
Scalloped Potatoes Ingredients Scalloped Potatoes 6 potatoes, peeled, thin sliced 1/2 onion, diced 2 rib celery, diced 4 oz. butter, melted 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 cups flour 3 cups milk Scalloped Potatoes Directions In large casserole dish, place a layer of potatoes in bottom.</description></item><item><title>Tuna Noodle Casserole</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:25:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Tuna Noodle Casserole is a Family Favorite and is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Our Creamy Tuna Noodle Casserole is Comfort Food for those Cold Winter Days.
Tuna Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
8 oz, tuna, drained 1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Tuna Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Noodle Casserole</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Chicken Noodle Casserole, Quick Easy Recipe for Lunch or Dinner Entree. Chicken Noodle Casserole is True Comfort Food and goes with any Salad, Fruit, and Warm Bread.
Chicken Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
1 lb cooked chicken meat cut up1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Chicken Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Creamy Scalloped Potatoes</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</guid><description>Quick Easy Creamy Scalloped Potatoes, Great Comfort Food Entree on those Cold Winter Days. Warm up the House with a Creamy Scalloped Potato Aroma.
Creamy Scalloped Potatoes serves 8
3# red potatoes, sliced 1/4″ 1/2 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced small 3 c milk 1 c roux 1 tsp chicken base 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. butter Creamy Scalloped Potatoes Directions Boil potatoes in medium size pot for about 20 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Pork Loin Recipe</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</guid><description>Stuffed pork loin with fresh raspberry sauce is a wonderful Holiday or Fall entree. The stuffing can be made with either walnuts or pecans. for presentation, slice and shingle onto a platter or tray.
Stuffed Pork Loin With Raspberry Sauce Stuffing: 4 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 ribs celery diced 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tbsp sage 2 apples, peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1 c chopped pecans Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Pork Roast with Michigan Apples</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</guid><description>Slow cooked pork roast with fresh Michigan apples and spices. Tender and juicy and served with stuffing or potatoes, salad and of course, our satisfying desserts.
Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Ingredients Serves 5 – 8
3 lb pork shoulder roast or fresh ham 1 medium onion 2 Michigan apples, peeled cut in chunks 1/2 c applesauce 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage 1/2 tsp black pepper 1 c water Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Directions Place roast in roasting pan, place all ingredients on top of roast.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Country Ribs</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</guid><description>Chef Frank’s honey barbecue country ribs are slow cooked until tender and will wow your family and friends at your back yard Barbecue.
Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Ingredients 3 lb country pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 to 2 c honey barbecue sauce 1/2 c water Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</guid><description>Chef Frank’s Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs are so delicious and easy to prepare in the oven or on the barbecue grill. Great with roasted red potatoesand salador fruit.
Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Ingredients 3 lb or more baby back pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 c honey barbecue sauce 1 c barbecue sauce (if you prefer regular barbecue sauce without honey) 1/2 c water Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description></item><item><title>Thyme Chicken Breast Entree</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</guid><description>Thyme chicken breast is prepared with fresh thyme, herbs and spices, then baked in the oven. It makes a good partner to wild rice, or roasted red potatoes, corn bread, salad or fruit.
Thyme Chicken Breast Ingredients serves 4
4 Chicken breasts, boneless 1 tbsp crushed thyme 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. Maitre d’ butter
(Click link or see recipe below) Thyme Chicken Breast Directions ### Oven Method: Place chicken breasts on greased sheet pan.</description></item><item><title>Delicious Homemade Teriyaki Chicken</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</guid><description>Teriyaki chicken with homemade sauce contains pineapple, garlic, brown sugar and soy sauce. It’s great for the barbecue grill outside, or inside under your broiler. Teriyaki chicken can be served with wild rice, salads or fruits or all the above.
Great on the barbecue grill!
Teriyaki Chicken Ingredients serves 4-6
2 whole chickens cut in 1/8’s, fresh 2 c Teriyaki sauce (see recipe below) 1 tbs. Chef Frank’s Seasoning Method #1 In large roasting pan, place chicken, seasoning, and teriyaki sauce.</description></item><item><title>Simple Lime Chicken Entree</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-lime-chicken-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-lime-chicken-entree/</guid><description>Delicious lime chicken, southwest style, made from cut up chicken or boneless breasts. Fresh lime and zest with Chef Frank’s Seasoning, puts it over the top!
Lime Chicken Ingredients 1 chicken cut in 1/8’s or ( 8 chicken breasts) boneless skinless 4 limes or 4 tbsp lime juice 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp southwest or tex mex seasoning 1 tsp paprika 2 tbsp melted butter 1 lime for lime zest (peel skin and slice very thin, place over chicken before cooking) Lime Chicken Directions Baking Method Place chicken in baking dish.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</guid><description>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Ingredients Serves 4
1 lb shrimp, raw, peeled, deveined, (size of your choice) 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 lb fresh sliced mushrooms 1 tsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 onion, diced 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tsp olive oil 2 lbs. angel hair pasta Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Directions Place pan of water on stove med. high heat to boil water, add a small amount of salt.</description></item><item><title>Scallops Newburg With Buttery Cream Sauce</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scallops-newburg-with-buttery-cream-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scallops-newburg-with-buttery-cream-sauce/</guid><description>Make scallops newburg with large Sea Scallops and a buttery cream sauce. Then place over rice and serve with Broccoli and cheese and a Salad. A nice mellow white wine compliments this meal.
Scallops Newburg Ingredients 2 lbs scallops (large size is better) 1/4 c small diced onion 1/4 c small diced celery 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 c roux 3 c milk 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning Scallops Newburg Directions Prepare cream sauce by heating milk and paprika over medium heat in double boiler, or carefully in sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Lake Michigan Broiled Whitefish</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/lake-michigan-broiled-whitefish/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/lake-michigan-broiled-whitefish/</guid><description>Let’s have broiled whitefish from Lake Michigan. Simply place on foil pie pan, butter, season, and broil. Serve with drawn butter or tartar sauce. Serve with any side dish, salad, rice, or potato.
Broiled Whitefish Ingredients 1 disposable. pie tin 9″-10″ 2 fresh whitefish (preferred from Lake Michigan) 2oz. butter melted couple shakes of Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 lemon 2 oz. water Broiled Whitefish Directions Place whitefish in pan, then add water (do not spray pan as skin will come off when cooked).</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Prepare this vegetarian honey barbecue sauce recipe when you’re grilling outside or cooking inside. It makes your vegetarian burgers, and ribs taste amazing.
Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Simple Vegetarian Goulash</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-vegetarian-goulash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-vegetarian-goulash/</guid><description>&amp;lt;vegetarian goulash is a delicious recipe made with tomato sauce, pasta, fresh cut vegetables and cheese. Great for Lunch or Supper and can be served with salads, vegetables, fruit, and hot rolls with honey butter./p&amp;gt;
Vegetarian Goulash Ingredients Serves 8
1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 tsp. olive oil 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 rib celery, diced small 1 12oz. can tomato sauce 1 12oz.</description></item><item><title>Simple and Tasty Potato Wedges</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-and-tasty-potato-wedges/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-and-tasty-potato-wedges/</guid><description>Try these easy potato wedges made from red, russet, or sweet potatoes. Simply cut wedges, butter, season, and bake. Potato wedges are a great snack or side dish for any main entree.
Potato Wedges Ingredients serves 6-10
4 large potatoes 1/4 c butter, melted 1/4 c grated Parmesan cheese Chef Frank’s Seasoning to taste garlic to taste(granulated or fresh chopped) Potato Wedges Directions Cut potatoes the long way into wedges(about 3-4 per halve).</description></item><item><title>Quick and Easy Egg Noodle Recipe</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/quick-and-easy-egg-noodle-recipe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/quick-and-easy-egg-noodle-recipe/</guid><description>Our quick egg noodle recipe is great for homemade soups or casseroles. Add fresh chopped herbs in the flour for flavored noodles, and use whole wheat flour for better nutrition.
Egg Noodles Ingredients 4 whole eggs pinch salt or Chef Frank’s Seasoning 4 cups flour (whole wheat flour for more nutrition) optional fresh chopped herbs can be mixed with flour like sage, thyme, oregano, marjoram, etc. 2 tsp ice water Egg Noodles Directions combine flour, eggs and salt, in mixer with dough hook.</description></item><item><title>Slow Roasted Cornish Game Hen</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/slow-roasted-cornish-game-hen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/slow-roasted-cornish-game-hen/</guid><description>Wonderful Cornish game hen, slow roasted and stuffed with apple walnut sage stuffing, or plain roasted served with wild rice. This recipe makes Holidays or any day special.
Slow Roasted Cornish Game Hen Ingredients non stuffed method: 1 Cornish game hen per serving as follows: 2 tbs melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp rubbed sage pepper to taste thoroughly rinse with cold water, pat dry, then place game hens in roasting pan back side down.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Turkey Recipes For The Holidays</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>Fill your house with the aroma of our festive oven roasted turkey. Wonderful for family celebrations and Holiday meals.
Oven Roasted Turkey Ingredients 20-25 lb turkey (Thawed if frozen 2-3 days in fridge) rinse under cold water before cooking 3 tbs rubbed sage 3 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 tbsp melted butter 2 c water Roasted Turkey Directions In large roasting pan place turkey, breast side up. Brush with melted butter, then rub with sage.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Chicken Entree</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-chicken-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-chicken-entree/</guid><description>Roast chicken is a quick recipe for a nice supper. All of our side dish recipes are compatible, and hot rolls with butter tops it off.
Roasted Chicken For 4 1 whole chicken (rinsed) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage (rubbed) black pepper to taste 1 tsp garlic (granulated or fresh chopped) 3 tbsp butter (melted) Roasted Chicken Directions Place chicken breast side up in roaster pan.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Prime Rib Roast with Au Jus</title><link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</guid><description>Celebrate the Holidays with our very special Prime Rib Roast recipe. It includes an awesome Au Jus recipe. Follow the links to festive side dishes too.
Prime Rib Roast Ingredients 15-19 lb rib roast 1/4 c garlic, fresh chopped 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 c water Prime Rib Directions Place rib roast in large roasting pan, bone down, add water and seasonings. Cover and place in oven at 275* and roast for 5 hours then check with thermometer.</description></item></channel></rss>