<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Seafood Dishes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/</link><description>Recent content in Seafood Dishes on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:45:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tuna Tomato Lotus Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/tuna-tomato-lotus-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/tuna-tomato-lotus-recipe/</guid><description>Tuna Tomato Lotus, Quick Easy Recipe for a Summer Luncheon Salad. Starred Fresh Tomato Stuffed with Tuna Salad Topped with Green Pepper Strips. Tuna Tomato Lotus With a Bowl of Soup, Healthy!
Tuna Tomato Lotus Quick and Easy Recipe Serves 4
4 red ripe tomatoes 8 oz. tuna, drained 1/4 c onion, diced 1 green pepper, cut in long strips from top to bottom 1/8 c celery, diced 2 tbsp mayo salt and pepper to taste Tuna Tomato Lotus Directions In mixing bowl combine tuna, onion, celery, mayo, and spices, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Seafood Chowder Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/seafood-chowder-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/seafood-chowder-recipe/</guid><description>Seafood Chowder, Quick Easy Thick Creamy Soup and Chowder Recipe. Use Your Choice of Scallops, Shrimp, Crab or Lobster. Fun and Simple to Prepare. Seafood Chowder is a Great Lunch. Serve With Oyster Crackers, a Sandwichor Salad.
Seafood Chowder Ingredients Serves about 8-10
2 c assorted seafood, chopped, raw (crab, shrimp, clams, scallops) 3 potaotoes, peeled diced 1/2 onion, diced 2 ribs celery, diced 2 large carrots, diced 1 tbsp crab base 1/4 tsp white pepper 1 tsp garlic 1 oz.</description></item><item><title>Clam Chowder Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/clam-chowder-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/clam-chowder-recipe/</guid><description>Clam Chowder, Quick and Easy for Your Friday Lunch or Soup and Sandwich Combo. Clam Chowder is an Easy Cream Soup Recipe and Great With Salads Too. Got Crackers?
Clam Chowder Ingredients Serves 8-10
2 c clams (canned are fine) do not drain 3 potaotoes, peeled diced 1/2 onion, diced 2 ribs celery, diced 2 large carrots, diced 1 tbsp clam base 1/4 tsp white pepper 1 tsp garlic 1 oz.</description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/hawaiian-shrimp-brochettes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:51:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/hawaiian-shrimp-brochettes/</guid><description>Quick Easy Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes, Great for Parties and Cookouts. Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes are Festive for Any Season or Reason and Made from Garden Vegetables and Fresh Pineapple.
Hawaiian Shrimp Brochettes Ingredients 1 lb shrimp, peeled deveined, raw 1 green or colored pepper, cut in 2″ squares 1 onion, large cut in 2″ pieces 1 lb. whole large mushrooms cut in 1/2 1 pint cherry tomatoes 1 fresh pineapple, cut in 2″ peices 1 pint sweet and sour sauce 1 can crushed pineapple, or pureed fresh pineapple 2 tbsp olive oil 10 skewers, metal or bamboo Hawaiian Shrimp Brochette Directions Combine crushed pineapple and sweet and sour sauce together, set aside.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp Stir Fry With Vegetables</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-stir-fry-with-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:49:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-stir-fry-with-vegetables/</guid><description>Shrimp Stir Fry Recipe is Quick And Easy with Fresh Vegetables and Shrimp, Stir Fried at 450℉ and Served over Rice or Pasta. Shrimp Stir Fry is a nice Healthy Entree for Family and Friends.
Shrimp Stir Fry Ingredients serves 10-15
3-4 lb Shrimp 21-25 count, peeled, deveined, raw 1 bunch broccoli 1 onion 2 ribs celery 1 carrot (large) 1 green pepper 4 oz. fresh pea pods 2 c cauliflower 2 c fresh bean sprouts 1 c fresh mushrooms soy sauce-to taste 2 tbsp olive oil ginger, ground or fresh grated Shrimp Stir Fry Directions Clean and cut all vegetable in about 1″ squares or strips, carrots should be sliced thin.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp Newburg</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-newburg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-newburg/</guid><description>Shrimp Newburg Directions 2 lbs shrimp,peeled, deveined, 21-25 size, raw 1/4 c small diced onion 1/4 c small diced celery 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 c roux 3 c milk 1/2 tsp paprika Shrimp Newburg Directions Prepare cream sauce by heating milk and paprika over medium heat in double boiler, or carefully in sauce pan. Stir constantly. Bring almost to light boil, add roux. Thicken with whisk to desired creaminess.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp Curry Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-curry-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/seafood-dishes/shrimp-curry-recipe/</guid><description>Curried Shrimp is a Quick Easy Seafood Recipe with Fresh Shrimp, Curry, and Vegetables. Curried Shrimp uses Different Curry Strengths to your Taste.</description></item></channel></rss>