<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipe Basics and Sauces on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/</link><description>Recent content in Recipe Basics and Sauces on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:30:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Au Jus</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/quick-au-jus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/quick-au-jus/</guid><description>Au Jus, Quick and Easy on the Stove or From Drippings, Great for Prime RibDuring Holidays or Special Function Dinners. This Quick and Easy Au Jus is Made With a Touch of Wine!
Au Jus Recipe 4 c water 4 tsp beef base 1 c red wine 1/2 onion(remove after finished) 1 tsp garlic, chopped 1/4 tsp white pepper Au Jus Directions In sauce pan place water, beef base, garlic, white pepper, and wine.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Barbecue Sauce</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Prepare this wonderful barbecue sauce on the stove. Great for grillingoutside or in. Use our sauce for chicken, ribs, pork, or barbecue sandwiches. Chef Frank finishes this recipe off with red wine for an added kick!
Barbecue Sauce Recipe 2 c ketchup 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Barbecue Sauce Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Coney Sauce Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/coney-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/coney-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>This Quick Easy Coney Sauce is Chef Frank’s Original Recipe. Use over High Grade Hot Dogs with Vadalia Onions and make other Lunches Jealous. Coney Sauce is a great Starter for ChiliToo.
Coney Sauce Chef Frank’s Original Recipe 2 lbs ground beef chuck or sirloin 1/2 small vadalia(sweet) onion diced 1 clove garlic, peeled, crushed or 1 tbs garlic powder (more or less to taste) 2 tbs tomato paste 1/2 tsp salt 1/2 tsp white pepper 4 tbs ground cumin (cumino) Coney Sauce Directions In large frying pan brown ground beef with onions, garlic, cumin, salt and pepper, breaking up burger as it cooks.</description></item><item><title>Easy Gravy Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/easy-gravy-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 04:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/easy-gravy-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Easy Gravy Recipes, Easily Made with Rouxand Either Chicken, Beef, Seafood, or Pork Base. Great for Mashed Potatoesand Sauces for Casserolesor Stew.
Gravy Recipe Ingredients This is a variable for beef, chicken or pork gravy.
1 tbsp Beef, chicken, seafood, or pork base / boullion (usually 1 tsp per cup of water) 3 c water 1/2 c roux Directions Boil water with base. Thicken slowly with roux to desired thickness using wire whisk.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe</title><link>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>/quick-e-recipes-hugo/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>Try Chef Frank’s Homemade Honey Barbecue Sauce when you’re grilling outside in the summer or cooking inside when it’s not so warm out. This sauce makes your ribs, chicken, or steak come alive with the sweet taste of local honey.
Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item></channel></rss>