<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homemade Soups on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</title>
    <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homemade Soups on Quick E Recipes - Everyday Family Meals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Joe Grey Soup</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/joe-grey-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 02:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/joe-grey-soup/</guid>
      <description>Traditional Gypsy Stew Joe Grey is a traditional Gypsy stew often made with sausage and bacon but can be modified to fit whatever flavor profile, or ingredients in your refrigerator, that you might desire.
Joe Grey History A popular dish in the Romany community, no one is sure of its origins. This recipe takes its inspiration from the wondering nature of the people who created it. It has a superb umami flavor due to the combination of meats and tomatoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split Pea Soup With Ham Recipe</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/split-pea-soup-with-ham-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/split-pea-soup-with-ham-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Here is a soup that will keep you warm on a cold winters day!
Quick Easy Split Pea Soup Recipe to warm up any cold day. Our split pea soup recipe has fresh carrots, onion, celery, potatoes, and ham, slow cooked for perfection. Break out the crackers.
Split Pea Soup with Ham Ingredients Serves 10+
 1 lb dried split peas 1 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced 2-3 potatoes, peeled, diced 3 carrots, peeled, diced 3 tbsp chicken base 3 quarts water 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 ham bone (with 1 lb ham)  Split Pea Soup Directions In large soup kettle, place all ingredients except peas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Pumpkin Vegetable Soup</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-pumpkin-vegetable-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-pumpkin-vegetable-soup/</guid>
      <description>Hot pumpkin soup is a vegetarians delight with real pumpkin, sweet potatoes, celery, and other vegetables from the garden. A chunky, filling soup that is heart warming, quick and easy to prepare.
Vegetarian Pumpkin Vegetable Soup Ingredients  10 c water 3 tbs vegetable base 3 ribs celery, diced 1 small onion, diced 1 small pumpkin cleaned, diced, enough for 5 cups 3 carrots, peeled, 1/2’d then sliced 2 small red potatoes, diced ( no need to peel) 1 large sweet potato, peeled, diced 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 small pinch nutmeg  Pumpkin Soup Directions Combine all ingredients into a large soup kettle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Borscht Recipe</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/ukrainian-borscht-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/ukrainian-borscht-recipe/</guid>
      <description>A Wonderful Ethnic Soup Recipe Directly from a Friendof ours from Ukraine. Katryana’s Ukrainian Borscht with Fresh Chickenwill Satisfy even a Picky Eater.
Ukrainian Borscht with Fresh Chicken Ingredients  1 whole chicken 4 beets 4 red potatoes 1 medium onion 1/2 cabbage 1 c. northern beans 1 small can tomato sauce salt and pepper to taste 1 tbsp chicken base 1/2 c. leaf basil, chopped 1/2 c. fresh parsley chopped  Borscht Directions In large kettle place chicken base and chicken in 3 quarts water, boil for 1 hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Chicken Vegetable Soup</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/pumpkin-chicken-vegetable-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/pumpkin-chicken-vegetable-soup/</guid>
      <description>Chunks of real pumpkin, sweet potato, and fall vegetables with fresh chicken, makes this recipe delicious, quick and easy. The perfect comfort soup for fall.
Pumpkin Chicken Vegetable Soup Ingredients  10 c water 3 tbs chicken base 3 ribs celery, diced 1 small onion, diced 1 small pumpkin cleaned, diced, enough for 5 cups 3 carrots, peeled, 1/2’d then sliced 2 small red potatoes, diced ( no need to peel) 1 large sweet potato, peeled, diced 1/2 chicken cut up,leg, thigh , breast, wing ( or 4 boneless chicken breasts) 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 small pinch nutmeg  Pumpkin Chicken Vegetable Soup Directions Combine all ingredients into a large soup kettle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy French Onion Soup Recipe</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/easy-french-onion-soup-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/easy-french-onion-soup-recipe/</guid>
      <description>French Onion Soup, Quick and Easy Soup for Lunch With Crouton and Cheese, A Minute Under the Broiler to Brown the Cheese. Make Any Restaurant Jealous! Great with Your Favorite Sandwichor Salad.
French Onion Soup Ingredients 8 servings
 2 large white or red onion, sliced, then cut in half 2 tbsp beef base 6 cups water 1 tsp garlic, chopped 1/2 tsp white pepper 1 tsp olive oil 1 c red wine (dry)  Topping Ingredients  8 slices toasted bread(crust off) 8-slices swiss cheese  French Onion Soup Directions In large sautee pan, medium high heat, place oil, onions, garlic and white pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Chicken Noodle Soup Recipe</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/homemade-chicken-noodle-soup-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/homemade-chicken-noodle-soup-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Chicken Noodle Soup Recipe is made from fresh chicken meat and garden vegetables. The Noodles are from our own Recipe. Chicken Noodle Soup is a healthy lunch.
Chicken Noodle Soup Ingredients  1 lb Chicken meat, cooked, diced 3 tbsp chicken base 3 ribs celery, chopped 1 onion, diced 3 carrots, large, peeled chopped 1 tsp rubbed sage 1/4 tsp white pepper 2 tbsp dried parsley flakes 1 gallon water 1 lb egg noodles  Chicken Noodle Soup Directions In large pot place all ingredients except noodles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Noodle Soup Recipe</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/beef-noodle-soup-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 14:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/beef-noodle-soup-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Beef Noodle Soup can be made with our Homemade Noodle Recipe, and has fresh carrots, onion, celery, and diced beef. Beef Noodle Soup with salad and crackers, a very nice lunch.
Beef Noodle Soup Ingredients  1 lb Beef, diced 3 tbsp beef base 3 ribs celery, chopped 1 onion, diced 3 carrots, large, peeled chopped 1 tsp oregano 1/4 tsp white pepper 2 tbsp dried parsley flakes 1 gallon water 1 lb egg noodles  Beef Noodle Soup Directions In large pot place all ingredients except noodles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Split Pea Soup</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-split-pea-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-split-pea-soup/</guid>
      <description>Vegetarian Split Pea Soup is a Quick Easy Recipe to Warm up any Cold Day. Our split pea soup recipe has fresh carrots, onion, celery, and potatoes, slow cooked for perfection. Break out the crackers.
Vegetarian Split Pea Soup Ingredients serves 10+
 1 lb dried split peas 1 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced 2-3 potatoes, peeled, diced 3 carrots, peeled, diced 3 tbsp vegetable base (boullion) 8 c water 1/2 tsp white pepper  Directions In large soup kettle, place all ingredients except peas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Northern Michigan Bean Soup</title>
      <link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-northern-michigan-bean-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/demo/recipes/homemade-soups/vegetarian-northern-michigan-bean-soup/</guid>
      <description>Vegetarian Northern Michigan Bean Soup is a Quick and Easy Comfort Soup Recipe. Soak the Beans a Day Ahead in the Fridge. Easy Next Day Prep. Great With Sandwiches, Muffins, Crackers or Salads.
This soup is a staple for Northern Michigan and is easy to prepare!
Northern Bean Soup Ingredients serves 10+
_It is important to soak beans overnight in water, and place in fridge. Drain water before adding to vegetables and broth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
